<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>./Addams Family, The (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Addams Family, The</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Addams Family, The (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>The game takes place towards the end of the movie: the Addams Family has been evicted from their home by a court order issued by a backstabbing attorney (there's one for the books), Tully Alford. Even worse, the other Addamses: Morticia, Pugsley, Wednesday, Granny and Lurch have gone missing.

As Gomez, you must tour the Addams mansion in search of your lost family, battling out mysterious monsters and evading traps, and eventually face your nemesis, Tully.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Flying Edge</developer>
    <publisher>Ocean</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>From the award winning animated TV series comes the most action-packed Batman adventure yet! The Dark Knight returns with Robin to battle the forces of evil. But wait... the iceman cometh!!! Mr. Freeze is about to unleash his super-powered ice cannon and has teamed up with the most notorious criminals to help him turn Gotham City into a diabolical winter wonderland!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Clockworks Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Aladdin (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Aladdin</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Aladdin (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>The game from Virgin based on the 1992 animated Disney film is a side-scrolling platformer.

The player controls Aladdin, who must make his way through several levels based on locations from the movie: from the streets and rooftops of Agrabah, the Cave of Wonders and the Sultan's dungeon to the final confrontation in Grand Vizier Jafar's palace. The Sultan's guards and also animals of the desert want to hinder Aladdin in his way. He can defend himself with his sword or by throwing apples. Next to apples, Aladdin can also collect gems which can be traded for lives and continues with a traveling trader. Finding Genie or Abu icons enables bonus rounds. The Genie bonus round is a game of luck played for apples, gems or extra lives. In Abu's bonus round, the player controls the little monkey who has to catch bonus items that fall from the sky, but without touching any of the unwanted objects like rocks and pots.

The game's humorous animations were created by Walt Disney Feature Animation.
</desc>
    <releasedate>19931111T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Virgin</developer>
    <publisher>Sega - Virgin</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Alien Soldier (Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Alien Soldier</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Alien Soldier (Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Alien Soldier is a side-scrolling action game in which the player takes the role of Epsilon-Eagle, the former leader of the Scarlet mutant group. The mutants are now lead by the evil Xi-Tiger who had turned them to terrorism, and one of their goals is to kill Epsilon-Eagle...

At the start of the game the player chooses four out of six weapons - each with special advantages or disadvantages against certain enemies. As mutant Epsilon-Eagle also has other special powers, e.g. teleporting across the screen or (with full health) morphing into a powerful phoenix destroying everything in his way.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Treasure</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Beyond Oasis (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Beyond Oasis</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Beyond Oasis (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>On the mystical island of Oasis, Prince Ali embarks on a crusade against evil. The warrior prince must unleash the powers of the four Wild Spirits to stop the resurrection of a ruthless sorcerer and save the empire! As Ali, you can call on the powers of the four wild spirits to battle the evil minions of Agito. Fight off enemies with Ali's weapons, punches and kicks... or dig deeper to discover the Hidden Super Moves...a Sega first! Flip switches, trigger plates, and use what's left of your brain to solve mind-boggling puzzles that lead to Huge Bosses... like the Fire-breathing Red Dragon!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950315T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Ancient - Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Bubble and Squeak (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Bubble and Squeak</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Bubble and Squeak (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Bubble and Squeak starts off similarly to many other platform games. Controlling a bald child, you move through a scrolling array of ledges, avoiding contact with nasties who release coins when shot. There are hidden areas to find as well.

Halfway through the first of the 30 levels, you meet Squeak and the full nature of the game starts. Squeak is a blue alien, who must also be guided through the levels. As he can't jump as high as you, he must sometimes be instructed to wait while you flick a switch or otherwise solve the puzzle of how to guide him through. If you stand on top of Squeak you can be launched into an extra-high jump.

Bubble Mode is an equivalent of Super Mario mode - it allows you to jump higher, run faster and shoot more lethal weaponry (bubbles in this case). It is activated by placing a coin into a Bubblegum machine, and then jumping on Squeak's back.

In between the main platform levels there are side-view shoot 'em up sections taking place underwater &#8211; completing these earns bonuses.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Fox Williams</developer>
    <publisher>Audiogenic</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The search is on! Mickey is on the trail of a wicked Witch named Mizrabel, who has kidnapped Minnie. Mickey must find seven gems hidden in the fantastic chambers of Mizrabel's Castle of Illusion and use them to save Minnie. Can Mickey find them? It's up to you.

Be on your guard! Behind every door lurks an enchanted land of beauty and danger. You must defeat angry chess knights, overcome the evil haunted trees, and do battle with ghoulish ghosts and a deadly dragon. No place is safe -- even the library is fraught with danger. Playing three levels in the practice mode will prepare you for the challenge you will face. Then, just when you think you've mastered the Illusions, you come face to face with the most dangerous of them all -- Witch Mizrabel!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Castlevania : Bloodlines</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Time refuses to forget the Belmont family's horrifying, bloody destiny. And in 1917 two of its descendants are summoned by fate into epic battle. Their enemy? The most evil incarnation of Castlevania legacy to ever rise from the grave, the vampiress Countess Bartley. This spine-tingling, 6-stage fear-fest overflows with graphic sights and sounds from your worst nightmares. As John Morris, the whip wielding vampire hunter, or Eric Lecarde, master lanceman, you'll pursue the demonic Countess all across Europe before she resurrects Dracula for a final reign of global terror. Alas, her trail of doom is laden with zombies, hideous mutants, grotesque giants, ghouls and ghastly creatures. Taste the sweat dripping into your mouth as you try rescuing yourself from diabolical traps. Feel the torturous strain on every muscle as you wield again and again sacred weapon power-ups such as Holy Water, the Battle Axe, the Crystal Blade Boomerang and the Mirror of Truth. But in the end, make sure you've saved enough strength to scream!</desc>
    <releasedate>19940317T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Chiki Chiki Boys (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Chiki Chiki Boys</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Chiki Chiki Boys (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>This platform-based action game was converted from a Capcom arcade game, and set in the land of Alurea. The idyllic life of the Alurean people was shattered when the King is killed by a dragon, and a range of nasties inhabit the lands. Fortunately his twin sons have come to the rescue, and you must take control of one or the other to put the world right.

The boys have differing skills - one is more skilled in sword-fighting (which you are always armed with), the other in magic (available in limited amounts on each level). You collect coins as the game goes on, and spend these in the shop on extra magic, extra lives and enhanced swords.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Comix Zone (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Comix Zone</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Comix Zone (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>ENTER THE COMIX ZONE: THE FIRST TRULY INTERACTIVE COMIC BOOK! Play as Sketch Turner, a street-wise comic book artist who gets trapped in the comic book world of his own creation. Warp into the Comix Zone with all the action and adventure of your favorite comics! Battle panel by panel through full comic book pages drawn by real comic book artists! Sharpen your fighting skills to defeat mutant enemies drawn in by Mortus, public enemy no. 1. Rip up the page with superhero power-ups and tons of intense fighting moves!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950802T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Contra - Hard Corps (USA, Korea).zip</path>
    <name>Contra : Hard Corps</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Contra - Hard Corps (USA, Korea).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Kickin' cyborg butt... That's what it's all about, dude. Jack into this game of genetic engineering gone bad. Real bad. It's five years after the mother of all wars ended - and things still aren't right. Your job is to fix it. The ever-popular Contra series makes its Sega Genesis debut with a pulse-pounding new storyline. At 16 megs, HARD CORPS pushes the technology to bring you over ten gut-wrenching levels with huge boss characters, great graphics and dynamic sound. Find high powered weapons such as the homing gun, crush gun, needle laser or mine setter. Do you think you can handle it? Trust me, you can't. You still here? Okay, then get ready for the fight of your life. Pick one of the four heroes and begin your search across many dark levels of doom. The ending changes, depending on the paths you choose - but every pass crosses boss characters that will blow you away. Literally!</desc>
    <releasedate>19940808T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Shoot'em up / Horizontal, Shooter, Shooter / Run and Gun</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Cool Spot (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Cool Spot</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Cool Spot (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>Cool Spot is a solid, colorful platform game featuring the 7-up mascot in the hero position. The game objective is fairly simple; you have to collect enough number of bonuses throughout each level in order to find the trapped Spots.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940218T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Virgin</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Crusader of Centy (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Crusader of Centy</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Crusader of Centy (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Millions of years ago, heinous creatures that lurked in the shadows and darkness that blanketed the planet inhabited the Earth. When light finally broke through, only a few beasts were able to survive by burrowing into deep caverns. Over time, they multiplied, evolved, and patiently waited for the right time to emerge and rule the Earth once again. You are Corona, and you've just celebrated your 14th birthday. By law of the king, you must now go seek out these creatures of the dark and destroy them. As you travel in search of your destiny, you'll make animal allies that will prove invaluable on your quest. Each level will offer mind-bending puzzles and challenges that will help you get one step closer to completing your mission.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940616T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Atlus - Nextech - Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Dr. Robotnik has hatched a plan to ensure that no music or fun remains on Mobius. To do this, he kidnaps the jolly citizens of Beanville and stuffs them into a giant robotising machine called the Mean Bean-Steaming Machine (hence the name, Mean Bean Machine), so that they become devious little robot slaves, as well as getting rid of them. The instruction manual states that the disappearing Beans are sent to the Mean Bean Machine, regardless of which character does this. The game ends after a face-off with Robotnik.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Compile</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Dune - The Battle for Arrakis (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Dune : The Battle for Arrakis</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Dune - The Battle for Arrakis (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Westwood Studios' real-time strategy classic Dune II received a major overhaul when ported to the Sega Genesis. While the basic concept remains the same, the game features all-new graphics, streamlined controls, changes to the tech tree as well as completely new levels.

As in the original game, the player controls the troops of one of three noble Houses, called by the Emperor to mine the Spice Melange on the planet Arrakis, also known as Dune. A series of consecutive battles must be won by mining spice, constructing a base and building units to attack the enemy.

The rather complex menu-based controls of the original game have been replaced by a context-sensitive cursor system, where a unit reacts according to what is below the cursor - either moving to a destination or attacking an enemy unit, for example.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Virgin</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin - Westwood Studios</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Dynamite Headdy (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Dynamite Headdy</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Dynamite Headdy (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Hot-headed Headdy gets into some real head-banging to thwart the Dark Demon's devious deeds. This wacky headcase is up to his neck in surprises! Switch heads to match the job! Over 15 heads to choose from! Bash heavy objects with Slammer Head! Suck up foes with Vacuum Head! Stick it to your enemies with Spike Head! Headdy's spring-loaded head gets him where he's gotta go! Use it to swing over ledges, grab onto objects and shoot hoops in the basketball bonus round. Use your head to whiz through a radical variety of play! Action, shooting and strategy speed you on to a surprise ending!</desc>
    <releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Treasure</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Earthworm Jim (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Earthworm Jim</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Earthworm Jim (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The storyline involves many colorful characters. Jim (voiced by TenNapel) was at first an ordinary earthworm who did very earthworm-like things such as flee from crows and eat dirt. One day, in the space above Earth, the evil Psy-Crow had cornered a rebel spaceship pilot who had stolen an "Ultra-high-tech-indestructible-super-space-cyber-suit" built by Professor Monkey-for-a-Head. The suit had been commissioned by the evil Queen Pulsating, Bloated, Festering, Sweaty, Pus-filled, Malformed, Slug-for-a-Butt so that she could further conquer the galaxy. In the ensuing space fight, the suit was dropped to Earth, and fell on Jim. By a stroke of luck, Jim managed to land within the collar of the suit, and it ended up mutating him into the large and intelligent (at least by earthworm standards) superhero he is today.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940802T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Shiny Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Shiny Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Earthworm Jim 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Two times the fun! Two times the excitement! Two times two is four. Too much to list, but keep reading: From Evil the Cat's 'Circus of the Scars' to the planet of Meat, join Jim on a madcap chase across the galaxy. Saving cows, thwarting lawyers and outsmarting Psy-Crow are all in a day's work for Jim. Are you up to the challenge? Can you handle the awesome new weapons? Excellent! Then stop reading this. Take it up to the front counter and try it at home! Trust no one, play it yourself... or EAT DIRT!</desc>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Playmates</developer>
    <publisher>Shiny Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ecco - The Tides of Time (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ecco : The Tides of Time</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ecco - The Tides of Time (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Ecco is older, stronger and engulfed by dangers! The evil Vortex has shattered the mystical Asterite. Ecco and Trellia, a beautiful dolphin of the future, cross 100 million years of time to save the dolphins and all life on Earth! Ecco morphs! Charge a metasphere to become a shark with all its fighting power! Change into a seagull and fly! Safely swim past dangers as a jellyfish! Over 40 levels of spectacular aquatic adventure, with password save. Five levels of challenging 3-D travel, through the vast waters of the open ocean!</desc>
    <releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Novotrade International</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ecco Jr. (USA, Australia).zip</path>
    <name>Ecco Jr.</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ecco Jr. (USA, Australia).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <desc>Ecco Jr. is a prequel to Ecco the Dolphin, set during his childhood. Together with his friends Tara the Whale and Kitney the Dolphin, Ecco goes looking for the legendary blue whale. Released after the two main Ecco games, this title is geared towards younger children with simplified gameplay, lacking the difficulty of the other Ecco games. The game also contains a number of educational facts about dolphins.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Novotrade International</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ecco the Dolphin (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Ecco the Dolphin</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ecco the Dolphin (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>You are Ecco, a powerful young dolphin. A mysterious storm has swept your family from the sea. The search to find them will take you through vast underwater realms of treachery, beauty and adventure. Use your sonar to discover hidden caverns and unlock the secrets of crystal glyphs. Charge packs of bloodthirsty sharks. Dive deep... but don't linger too long, because you're a mammal and need air to breathe. In your quest, you'll discover that more than your family's safety is at stake. The fate of the whole world rests on your wits and fins. Explore over 25 giant levels of solving puzzles and fighting denizens of the sea. Knife through the waters, flip above the waves, with motions created from real dolphins.</desc>
    <releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Novotrade International</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Elemental Master (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Elemental Master</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Elemental Master (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Gyra has usurped the throne, and his minions are pillaging and plundering throughout the countryside. The kingdom is doomed unless someone can stop this madness and restore order to the land. You are the ELEMENTAL MASTER, and you're the only person with the power to put an end to Gyra's reign of terror. Harnessing the power of the elements fire, water, wind, and the earth you use them as your very own weapons to fight all that is evil in the world. You'll be up against Gyra's most ruthless henchmen as you battle through eight levels of intense action. But you've got the power of magic on your side, and if you can master the five spells at your disposal, you'll be a nearly unstoppable force. Of course, when you're single-handedly taking on an entire army, the odds are stacked against you. But with the power of the elements, you're the only one who can stop Gyra and his army.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technosoft</developer>
    <publisher>Technosoft</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./ESWAT - City Under Siege (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>ESWAT : City Under Siege</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/ESWAT - City Under Siege (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <desc>The city is besieged by wanted criminals, and as a police officer it is your duty to stop them. The first criminals in the wanted list can be stopped with your service weapon an some fast reactions, but once you're facing the toughest criminals in town you'll need to use the cyber suit, which provides additional protection and higher firepower.

Unlike other versions of this game, this Genesis cartridge doesn't follow the layout of the arcade game. The levels, rather than being linear, feature some platform elements, and the enemies in the first levels are no longer bank robbers or hit-men, but soldiers and robots instead. And the setting is no longer your typical American city, but a futuristic megalopolis.</desc>
    <releasedate>19901001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Various</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Eternal Champions (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Eternal Champions</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Eternal Champions (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>From various time periods of past, present and future, nine fighters killed in an unjust manner find themselves given a second chance for life. An alien being, known only as the Eternal Champion, brings back the fighters into a competition for one reason: to find one among them worthy of being resurrected, giving them a chance to avert their death and tip the balance between good and evil.

The fighters range from different eras of Earth's History: Larcen, the cat burglar. Jetta, the circus acrobat. Blade, the futuristic bounty hunter. Midknight, the vampiric bio-chemist. Rax, the cyborg. Shadow, the corporate assassin. Slash, the neanderthal. Trident, a Atlantean warrior. And Xavier, a warlock and alchemist.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Flashback - The Quest for Identity (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Flashback : The Quest for Identity</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Flashback - The Quest for Identity (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <desc>The year is 2142. The player takes control of Conrad B. Hart, a man who has lost his memory. After barely escaping from hostile aliens, Conrad's bike crashes on an unknown planet. Conrad finds himself in the jungle, and from that moment on his quest for survival and his lost identity begins.

Flashback: The Quest for Identity incorporates elements of platforming, shooting, and problem-solving. The game can be described as a "cinematic platformer" (commonly referred to as Prince of Persia-style), following a design philosophy that was also manifested in Delphine Software's previous work, Another World. Compared to that game, Flashback focuses more on platforming and exploration of large levels.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
    <publisher>Delphine Software International</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Flink (Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Flink</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Flink (Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Flink (released in North America as The Misadventures of Flink), is a 2D scrolling platform video game developed by Psygnosis.

The Amiga CD32 and Sega CD versions are reliant on CD-ROM media to store large levels, highly detailed graphics, and high-quality music. The Mega Drive version is a cut-down version.

Flink is one of the few Amiga CD32 titles not to see a release for the Amiga home computer system, on which the CD32's hardware was based. The majority of titles released for the CD32 were essentially the versions developed for Amiga home computers, taking only minor advantage of the CD-ROM medium with extra levels, CD audio, and/or FMV sequences.

The creators, Erwin Kloibhofer and Henk Nieborg, were also responsible for the games The Adventures of Lomax and Lionheart.</desc>
    <releasedate>19941111T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sony</developer>
    <publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Gaiares (Japan, USA).zip</path>
    <name>Gaiares</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Gaiares (Japan, USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>It's the year 300x. The Earth has been ravaged by careless humans, leaving an uninhabitable, polluted wasteland. The space terrorists, Gulfer, plan to harvest the pollution to make some sort of garbage weapon. The good guys, the Leezaluth, aren't happy about that, so they decide they have to blow up the Earth before Gulfer gets at it. They give Earth an ultimatum: destroy Gulfer or Leezaluth destroys Earth. To help them out, Leezaluth gives Earth's last hero, Dan, a special weapon: the TOZ system.

Why don't the Leezaluth just stop Gulfer themselves? It's not exactly clear.

So, we have the premise for a side scrolling shooter. The star attraction here is the TOZ system. The TOZ is an orb that follows your ship around, and can be shot at enemy ships to absorb their weapons. Using the TOZ, Dan will fight through 8 stages filled with lots of enemies and really large bosses.</desc>
    <releasedate>19901226T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Telenet</developer>
    <publisher>Renovation</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./General Chaos (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>General Chaos</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/General Chaos (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Command the armies of General Chaos against General Havoc's troops in this multi-player action game of brute strength and awesome firepower! 1-4 player head-to-head and co-op play. Over 50 different battlefields. Four squads to choose from: the Assault Team, the Commandos, the Demolition Squad and the Brute Force Troop. Brutal hand-to-hand combat. Five unique weapon types: flame throwers, machine guns, bazookas, grenades, and dynamite.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940113T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Game Refuge</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Golden Axe II (World).zip</path>
    <name>Golden Axe II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Golden Axe II (World).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The three playable characters from the first Golden Axe, Ax Battler, Tyris Flare, and Gilius Thunderhead, return in Golden Axe II to fight the new evil forces led by Dark Guild. The game features a total of seven levels: six scrolling levels and a final end of game boss battle against Dark Guild.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Golden Axe III (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Golden Axe III</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Golden Axe III (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Damud Hellbringer, the Prince of Darkness, has taken away the Golden Axe and put an evil curse over all the warriors. However, one of the heroes has their curse relieved and is sent to set things straight - lift the curse off the others, defeat the villain and return with the Golden Axe.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Gunstar Heroes (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Gunstar Heroes</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Gunstar Heroes (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Gunstar Heroes is a side scrolling shooter. The player has four weapons to choose from, and they can be combined in various pairs to create a total of 14 unique weapons. In addition to the weapons, the player can engage enemies in close quarters combat. It is possible to grab and toss enemies, perform sliding and jumping attacks and a long-range skid.

Unlike most games in the genre, the player has a life total calculated in numbers. Death to a player requires multiple hits but just one death will issue the option to continue from the start of the level or to end the game. Players have unlimited continues.

The main highlight of the game are its boss encounters, which often feature large enemies made up of multiple sprites allowing for fluid movement.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930909T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Treasure</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Haunting Starring Polterguy (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Haunting Starring Polterguy</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Haunting Starring Polterguy (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Scare the evil, greedy Sardinis out of their houses by turning everyday household objects into something scary, funny or just plain gross. Or use your special spells to really send 'em shrieking. But you gotta hurry, 'cause your ectoplasm may run out! 16 megs of cool graphics, gross special effects and blood-curdling sounds. Unique 3/4 view perspective. Over 400 scary, funny or gross fright items, each causing something different to happen. Five special spells: Zom-B-Ize, Supr-Scare, Boo-Doo, Ecto-Xtra and Dog-Off. "Killer" dungeon with 12 different paths!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Various, Simulation</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Hellfire (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Hellfire</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Hellfire (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>In the year 2998, humanity has finally reached the stars, and was able to build a prosperous, peaceful society. However, a space matter known as the Black Nebula began to spread, threatening to engulf the galaxies controlled by humans. It turned out that a robotic dictator named Super Mech was behind this occurrence. The Earth sends Captain Lancer, a skillful pilot navigating the powerful CNCS1 aircraft, equipped with the most powerful weapon: the Hellfire...</desc>
    <releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Toaplan</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Fight</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Herzog Zwei (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Herzog Zwei</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Herzog Zwei (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>"Eins! Zwei! Drei!" In the murky dawn the tyrant's troops scuffle towards foxholes and tanks. Taking battle position, they quickly check their equipment and load cannons. Then they hunker down, awaiting the cry: "Attacke!" "Hup! Two! Three! Four!" On your order, rebel soldiers race to their war machines! Jets blast into the dawn, afterburners roaring. Convoys rumble toward the advance bases. Their single purpose: attack! War! You and your opponent face off for control of the world! You're equally matched, man for man, weapon for weapon. You sweat as you order out heavy metal, mobilize troops, and plot the attack! You collide in dogfights, ground frays, and naval clashes! At last, you advance to their home base. Now! Crush the enemy - and become Supreme Commander of the free world!</desc>
    <releasedate>19881231T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technosoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Jungle Strike (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Jungle Strike : The Sequel to Desert Strike</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Jungle Strike (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Some time after Operation Desert Strike, Ibn Kilbaba, son of Kilbaba S.R, threatens to annihilate America. After his father was killed, the people who were under his control, sent his son running off, along with his father's money and nuclear weapons program. Kilbaba, more ruthless than his father, longs for revenge of his father's death and decides to shed the blood of those who killed him, the Americans. Already armed, Kilbaba hires Carlos Ortega to help him set up his Nuclear Weapons program, deep in South America. Carlos Ortega, the world's most notorious druglord, also yearns to seek revenge. With his own private army, armed with the most hi-tech weapons, he's ready to fight America at all costs. 

Because of this threat, you're hired again to battle these two characters, following their paths in the jungles of South America. Armed with the Commache, numerous other vehicles, and destructive weapons, you must take out their private army. Blow up the enemy with your hellfires, hydras, chain guns. Use the watercraft to launch mines at enemy ships. Pull off a drive-by on the enemy with guns on the side. Take out the evil duo and forever rid this threat.....in the jungle!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>High Score Productions</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Kid Chameleon (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Kid Chameleon</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Kid Chameleon (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>A new virtual reality arcade game arrived in town and every kid played it. Nothing seemed out of the ordinary until kids began to disappear. The game's boss, Heady Metal, had freed himself from his scripted AI. He was using his new freedom to kidnap every kid who could not beat the game, which was all of them, until now. A boy named Casey who calls himself "Kid Chameleon" enters the game and must defeat every level, every boss and Heady Metal himself if he wants to save the others.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920301T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Adventure</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Landstalker (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Landstalker</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Landstalker (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Eons ago, evil King Nole tyrannized the mythical island of Melcatle. With an insatiable greed for power and wealth, he crushed the people with heavy taxes while destroying their freedom. At last, in fury, the enslaved citizens stormed the palace. But King Nole was gone! And with him, the vast treasure, stolen from his subjects!

Now Nigel, the Landstalker, journeys to this fantastic realm in search of the legendary fortune and power to reunite a divided kingdom!</desc>
    <releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Climax Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Lemmings 2 - The Tribes (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Lemmings 2 : The Tribes</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Lemmings 2 - The Tribes (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>The sequel to one of the most famous games ever now has a much more significant plot. The Lemmings have split into 12 distinct tribes, each of which has their own landscape and their own cultural identity - they include Egyptian, Circus and Highland. However, Lemming Island is now in danger, and you must complete 10 levels for each tribe in order for them to reunite and reassemble the Talisman from the 12 pieces.

Across the 120 levels there are over 60 skills, although no more than 10 are in use on each screen. The Classic tribe has the ones form the original and is perhaps the best option for first-time players.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>DMA Design</developer>
    <publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Light Crusader (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Light Crusader</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Light Crusader (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Fight your way through a dungeon of evil! Innocent people are vanishing, victims of horrifying magic. You, a master swordsman, are challenged to save them. Only your sword and razor sharp mind will help you survive the lethal labyrinth, rescue the people, and save the kingdom!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950525T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Treasure</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Lightening Force - Quest for the Darkstar (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Lightening Force : Quest for the Darkstar</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Lightening Force - Quest for the Darkstar (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>You must lead the battle against the evil Lohun Empire. Their computer system is poised to destroy your Galaxy Federation's defenses. Lead the attack on their heavily defended military planet. Knock out the planet's command center to pave the way for the invasion force. Take the fight underwater to destroy massive marine battlecruisers. Launch magnetically-charged photon blasts at alien bio-machines. Twist through the labyrinthine structure of the enemy's Bio-Base. There you'll meet your final objective, the destructive regenerating computer. Cut loose with the Thunder Sword, your most powerful energy beam, as you battle this ultimate weapon!</desc>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technosoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Lost Vikings, The (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Lost Vikings, The</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Lost Vikings, The (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>In the game, the three Vikings get kidnapped by Tomator, emperor of the alien Croutonian empire, for an inter-galactic zoo and become lost in various periods of time. The purpose of the game is to control the three characters (who all have separate abilities) in order to solve puzzles to escape and get back home.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Silicon &amp; Synapse</developer>
    <publisher>Interplay</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Platform, Strategy</genre>
    <players>3</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Madden NFL 95 (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Madden NFL 95</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Madden NFL 95 (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>John Madden's back in the 1995 version of Madden NFL.

Play exhibition, Super Bowl, playoffs or full season with any of the 1994 teams or all Madden teams.

This time around, you can select whether or not to include weather conditions, new player animations (high steppin', QB slides), a bigger field and over 100 injuries.

Also includes windowless passing, all new Madden-designed strategies and team match-up that shows how your players stack up to the other team in their position.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>High Score Productions</developer>
    <publisher>EA Sports</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Marvel Land (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Marvel Land</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Marvel Land (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>A young lad named Talmit is called upon to rescue Wondra the princess, and free the Fairies from King Mole. Marvel Land consists of five worlds with seven stages each, and the game plays in platform style, in which you need to run through the level, killing enemies, and find the exit door. More often than not, you have to go through a bullseye to reach it. If you hit the bullseye at its center, you are awarded more points than you do by hitting it above or below.</desc>
    <releasedate>19911001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Plate-Forme</developer>
    <publisher>Plate-Forme</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Bomberman (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Bomberman</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Bomberman (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>The inhabitants of Bomber Planet lived in peace, protected by five spirits, until the evil Bagular and his robot army invaded. The Spirit Pictures, the source of the Spirits' magical power, were destroyed, splitting Bomber Planet into five pieces. Bomberman arrives to restore the Spirit Pictures and reassemble Bomber Planet.</desc>
    <releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Westone</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Turrican (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Turrican</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Turrican (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>After many generations of peace, the Dark Forces have assembled again, and as a member of the USS Freedom Forces, it is your job to defeat them once again. This means you will have to complete numerous large levels always searching for secrets to pick up and enemies to shoot. To do this, you can pick up three different, upgradeable shots: a multiple, a laser and a rebound. You can also go into wheel-mode (as long as you have enough special energy) or use a rope. In wheel-mode, you are invincible and can lay mines or explore previously unreachable areas.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940607T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Factor 5</developer>
    <publisher>Data East</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Micro Machines (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Micro Machines</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Micro Machines (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>If you're bored of racing Formula 1 cars, rally cars or MotoGP bikes in their natural habitats, the Micro Machines series could be for you. It involves racing miniatures representing particular vehicle types across a particular terrain found around the house. The Sports Cars race on the desktop, 4x4s in the sandpit, Formula 1 cars on a snooker table, and so on.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930914T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Codemasters</developer>
    <publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Micro Machines 2 - Turbo Tournament (Europe) (J-Cart).zip</path>
    <name>Micro Machines 2 : Turbo Tournament</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Micro Machines 2 - Turbo Tournament (Europe) (J-Cart).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>16 crazy characters to choose from! Bigger, Better, Faster, Meaner, More! They're back! Codemasters brings you Micro Machines 2 - Turbo Tournament, packing more micro power than ever before. Hovering, tracking, biking, the game has exploded in every aspect. Interactive courses, rain, wild jumps and much much more. - Head to Head, Challenge, Knockouts, Super League. - Over 37 interactive courses with animated hazards. - Up to 8 people can play in a tournament. - Wild music and FX. - 12 all-new incredible vehicles to drive!</desc>
    <releasedate>19941125T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Codemasters</developer>
    <publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>8</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Micro Machines Military (Europe) (J-Cart).zip</path>
    <name>Micro Machines : Military</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Micro Machines Military (Europe) (J-Cart).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Micro Machines Military is a Driving game, developed by Supersonic Software and published by Codemasters, which was released in Europe in 1996.</desc>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Supersonic Software</developer>
    <publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>8</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Micro Machines Turbo Tournament 96 (Europe) (v1.1) (J-Cart).zip</path>
    <name>Micro Machines : Turbo Tournament 96</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Micro Machines Turbo Tournament 96 (Europe) (v1.1) (J-Cart).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Micro Machines 2: Turbo Tournament was released in 1994[5] and featured vehicles which required different handling techniques for each course, including hovercraft and helicopters. There are different playing modes including "head-to-head", in which each player earns points by driving a full screen ahead of the opponent. TV presenter Violet Berlin features as a playable driver. The MS-DOS version featured a track editor which allowed players to create their own custom vehicles, backgrounds and obstacles and export and import tracks.

A selling point for the Sega Genesis/Mega Drive version was the J-Cart, a cartridge including two control ports, thus eliminating the need for a 4-player adaptor.[6] It also included a 'pad-sharing' feature which allowed 2 players to share a single joypad; thus it enabled 8 players to compete simultaneously, on certain tracks.

An updated version of Micro Machines 2: Turbo Tournament was only released in PAL regions for the Mega Drive entitled Micro Machines Turbo Tournament '96. The updated version featured new tracks combined with some updated tracks from Micro Machines 2. It also featured a track construction kit previously included in the MS-DOS version.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950701T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Supersonic Software</developer>
    <publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>8</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mortal Kombat II (World).zip</path>
    <name>Mortal Kombat II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mortal Kombat II (World).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Following his failure to defeat Liu Kang in the first Mortal Kombat game, the evil sorcerer Shang Tsung begs his master, Shao Kahn, to spare his life. He tells Shao Kahn that the invitation for Mortal Kombat cannot be turned down, and if they hold it in Outworld, the Earthrealm warriors must attend. Kahn agrees to this plan, and even restores Tsung's youth. He then extends the invitation to Raiden, who gathers his warriors and takes them into Outworld. The new tournament is much more dangerous, as Shao Kahn has the home field advantage, and an Outworld victory will allow him to subdue Earthrealm.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Midway</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mortal Kombat III</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Fed up with continuous losses in tournament battle, Shao Kahn, who had lost to Liu Kang in the Outworld tournament, enacts a 10,000 year-old plan. He would have his Shadow Priests, led by Shang Tsung, revive his former Queen Sindel, who unexpectedly died at a young age. However, she wouldn't be revived in the Outworld. She would be resurrected in the Earthrealm. This would allow Shao Kahn to cross the boundary lines and reclaim his queen.
When Sindel is reincarnated in Earthrealm, Shao Kahn reaches across the dimensions to reclaim her. As a consequence of his action, the Earthrealm becomes a part of the Outworld, instantly stripping billions of their souls. Only a few are spared, as Raiden protects their souls. He tells them that Shao Kahn must be stopped, but he cannot interfere; due to his status, he has no power in Outworld, and Earthrealm is partially merged with Outworld.
Shao Kahn has unleashed extermination squads to roam throughout the Earthrealm and kill any survivors. Also, Raiden's protection only extends to the soul, not to the body, so his chosen warriors have to fight the extermination squads and repel Shao Kahn. Eventually with his final defeat, every human on Earthrealm comes back.
Mortal Kombat 3 follows Mortal Kombat II and shares continuity with both Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 and Mortal Kombat Trilogy which were both updates of this game. The next new game in the series was Mortal Kombat 4.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Midway</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor (USA).zip</path>
    <name>MUSHA : Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>A spin-off from the successful Aleste series by Compile, Musha Aleste takes the same top-down shooter mechanics of it's predecessors but stages the action in a bizarre universe that merges traditional Japanese lore with sci-fi mecha action.

Instead of commanding a ship, you will actually step into the cockpit of a ninja-styled mecha as you fight through the many levels in the game, with several option satellites that can be configured to use different formations.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Compile</developer>
    <publisher>Seismic Software</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./NHL '94 (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>NHL '94</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/NHL '94 (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Over 25 NEW features in HOCKEY '94! 4-Way Play Support - Use the EA Sports 4-Way Play and NHL '94 becomes a 1, 2, 3 or 4 player game! Goalie Control - You control the double pad stacks and kick saves of all the greats. Penalty Shots and Shootout Mode - Take the hottest shooters and go head to head with the greatest goalies in the league. One Timers - New blistering slap shots make offense faster and more challenging. New Expansion Teams - Play with the Mighty Ducks or with the Florida Panthers. Music and Animations - Over 70 new pieces of organ music from arenas around the league. Plus new crowd and player animations!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930302T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>High Score Productions</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Hockey</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Phantasy Star II (USA, Europe) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Phantasy Star II (USA, Europe) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The time: Space Century 3240. The place: The Algol Star System. It began when King Lassic turned evil and let hordes of hideous, magical creatures run amok on the three planets. When her brother was killed, Alis vowed to avenge his death and put an end to Lassic forever.

Join her in a journey across time and space to worlds where creatures speak...where magic and science combine to take you on the ultimate video quest.

The battle system is turn-based, allowing the player to choose commands for up to four characters. Each of the eight characters has a different set of preferred weapons and armor, as well as techniques, suited to the character's job. The player must defeat enemies in the overworld and in dungeons to advance in the game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Phantasy Star III - Generations of Doom (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star III : Generations of Doom</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Phantasy Star III - Generations of Doom (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Vanquish the Dark Forces

It's been a millennium since Laya's hordes battled Orakio's cyborg armies. And civilized man was almost destroyed. But the Dark Forces still remain. Conquer these monstrous mutations. Fight them with swords, knives, bows - even your wits. You live and die by them.

Explore the Planet and Beyond

Trek through 7 distant lands - some friendly, some not. Transform into an aerojet and fly over snow-capped mountains. Or become a submersible or aquaskimmer and cross vast oceans and raging rivers. Then find and fight your way through danger-laden dungeons.

Come Forth Now

Embark on a journey so vast, it spans the lives of three generations. Begin with Maia, spirited away by a winged dragon on your wedding day. Experience one of our four endings that will surprise new and former Phantasy Star players alike.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Phantasy Star IV (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star IV</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Phantasy Star IV (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Launch into the biggest RPG ever on Genesis! This is the explosive magic-and-monster packed FINALE to the incredible Phantasy Star saga. An ancient, hideous Dark Force stalks the Algol star system. You, a young hunter, are destined to become Motavia's greatest warrior and strike the death-blow that destroys evil FOREVER!</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Adventure, Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Pirates! Gold (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Pirates! Gold</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Pirates! Gold (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Pirates! is a single-player game. The player receives a letter of marque authorizing service as a privateer for Spain, the Dutch Republic, England, or France in the Caribbean. The player's loyalties may change over the course of the game; he may also hold rank with multiple countries and may turn to piracy at any time. Gameplay is open-ended; the player may choose to attack enemy ships or towns, hunt pirates, seek buried treasure, rescue long-lost family members, or even avoid violence altogether and seek to increase his wealth through trade. The game also has no predetermined end, although as time goes on, it becomes more difficult to recruit crew members. Also, as the player character ages, fighting becomes more difficult, and deteriorating health will eventually force the character into retirement. The game ends when the player retires, at which point he is given a position in his future life, from beggar to King's adviser, based on accumulated wealth, land, rank, marital status, and other accomplishments.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>MicroProse</developer>
    <publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ranger X (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ranger X</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ranger X (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Engage in airborne combat with jump-jets and weapons of incredible power or link up with your cyber cycle for high speed ground attacks. Each step inches you closer to your goal and the fight of your life. You are Ranger X... A mysterious lone warrior who has risen from the ashes to return peace and justice to a failed society. Eight post-apocalyptic levels of high-intensity action! Monstrous mechanical bosses await your every move. Use jump-jets to attack by air or transform into the Super Cyber Cycle and roll to victory!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930527T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>GAU Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>GAU Entertainment- Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Revenge of Shinobi, The (USA, Europe) (Rev B).zip</path>
    <name>Revenge of Shinobi, The</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Revenge of Shinobi, The (USA, Europe) (Rev B).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>You are Musashi, master ninja. You are one of the mystic warriors, who see and know all things. You are deadly! Now you must destroy the vicious army of Neo Zeed. If you fail, then Naoko, their beautiful prisoner, dies! Attack with a ninja sword and crossed daggers! Somersault over fences while hurling deadly knives! Ward off bullets, Death Stars, and junked cars by leaping, twisting, and kicking! The Neo Zeed are masters of disguise. But you are a master of Shinobi, the art of stealth. You'll stalk the Neo Zeed through 24 treacherous scenes, while they stalk you! Battle ninja, musclemen, deadly lasers, and the diabolical Boss! Outfight Kung Fu gangs and armies of machine gunners. The Neo Zeed is almost unstoppable, but you have a secret weapon - ninja magic!</desc>
    <releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ristar (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Ristar</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ristar (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Ristar, the son of a legendary hero who's been captured, is the solar system's last hope against the evil space pirate Greedy. Ristar must travel to the 7 planets of his home system to restore peace to their once happy worlds and ultimately free his father. Ristar stretches his long elastic arms to grab enemies and head-butt them! His long limbs help him climb up walls or swing out of danger. Discover totally different worlds and new creatures on each planet! Battle strange beings who aren't always what they seem! Shoot through a variety of gameplay! Action, puzzle and strategy combine to challenge Ristar at every turn.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950216T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Road Rash (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Road Rash</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Road Rash (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>No Speed Limit? No Rules? No Problem! Blow 14 opponents off the backroads of California in the most illegal, unofficial and dangerous race there is. Kick and punch your opponents outta the way at 150 mph. Snatch a club - if you wanna do some real damage. Avoid cows, road blocks, oil spills and oncoming traffic! Finish the race to take home cash or look for a police escort to your favorite jail. The roads get tougher and your opponents get meaner with each new level - so get used to the abuse. Eight bikes are up for grabs - if you have the cash!</desc>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Road Rash 3 (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Road Rash 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Road Rash 3 (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The Rash is back in the latest, nastiest, baddest race game for your Genesis. This time there's five NEW weapons, including the cattle-prod and crow bar. NEW race tracks take you across the globe, from the Aussie Outback to nighttime urban Japan. NEW modes raise the ante with the other Rashers while the NEW digitized graphics and interactive obstacles charge NEW life into the gameplay!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950301T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Rocket Knight Adventures (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Rocket Knight Adventures</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Rocket Knight Adventures (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>He's courageous! He's clever! He's one good lookin' opossum. It's Sparkster the Rocket Knight, the heroic jet pack jockey with warp speed, quick wits and pumped up personality. After all, who else do you know can get a grip with his tail? Rocket through 7 epic stages of animalistic adventure, home of the hugest, strangest enemy pig creatures imaginable. (In fact, your mission is crammed with more ham than a Hollywood premier.) Destroy the Emperor who's on a porcine power trip that will take him to the Key to the Pig Star. In every stage you'll be moving, flying and riding in a new direction to escape opossum punishment. You're the thrust-meister controlling Sparkster's jet pack and his assault sword. Confront mechanized menaces like the Giant Pigbot, the Drill Of A Lifetime, and the snappy Crab Rangoon. Things take a turn for the worst in the room of rotating gravity where Axle Gear, the Black Knights awaits you. And you've never seen anything like the unreal mirrored lava pools where things will reflect badly on you. The tricks, the traps and challenges never end. But the world as you know it will if you don't grind those pigs for sausage.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Rolo to the Rescue (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Rolo to the Rescue</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Rolo to the Rescue (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>Rolo to the Rescue is a side-scrolling platform action game. The player controls Rolo, an elephant who escaped from the circus. Rolo's main task is to find and rescue four other animals - a squirrel, a rabbit, a beaver, and a mole. Once rescued, each of those friends become player-controlled characters with special abilities that can help the player along the way -- the squirrel can climb, the rabbit jumps, the beaver swims, and the mole digs.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Vectordean</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Samurai Shodown (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Samurai Shodown</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Samurai Shodown (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>The game is set in the late 18th century and all the characters wield weapons. The game uses comparatively authentic music from the time period, rife with sounds of traditional Japanese instruments, such as the shakuhachi and shamisen, and a refined version of the camera zoom first found in Art of Fighting. True to its use of bladed weapons, the game also included copious amounts of blood.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SNK</developer>
    <publisher>Saurus - SNK - Takara</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Shadow Dancer - The Secret of Shinobi (World).zip</path>
    <name>Shadow Dancer : The Secret of Shinobi</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Shadow Dancer - The Secret of Shinobi (World).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>The Shinobi explosion is back! The master of stealth and the death-dealing art of Shuriken returns to avenge the murder of his friend Kato. It's war with all the lightning-fast combat, evil menace, and magic of the arcade powerhouse. The ultimate evil is Sauros, a crazed reptilian monster with the power to invoke cataclysmic catastrophes. His army of vicious ninja controls the city as he summons sudden firestorms, earthquakes and avalanches! Lizard henchmen guard terrified hostages that you must rescue. Dodge through the inferno! Hurl yourself across crumbling buildings. Conjure up total devastation with powerful ninja magic. Heave an onslaught of Death Stars - the last things the evil ones see! Shinobi's fearless attack dog Yamato joins your race through danger. He combines the strength of three men, razor jaws, and the speed of a Shinobi Sabre. You're Shadow Dancer. They've dishonored you. They die!</desc>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Shining Force (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Shining Force</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Shining Force (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Shining Force is a turn-based tactical RPG. Battles take place in square grids, and each unit occupies 1 square. Each unit can move up to a fixed amount of squares along the battlefield, determined by its Move statistic. Depending on its location relative to enemies and to allies, a unit can also perform one action: attack, cast a spell, use an item, or search the area. Some commands, such as equipping or dropping items, don't count as actions. The order of turns is determined by the unit's agility score and a random seed.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Climax Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Climax - Sega - Sonic! Software Planning</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games, Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Shining Force II (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Shining Force II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Shining Force II (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Shining Force II is a tactical role-playing game. The player assumes the role of the Shining Force leader, Bowie. When not in combat, the player can explore towns and other locales, talk with people, and set the members and equipment of the army. Some towns have a headquarters where the player can inspect and talk with his allies. While roaming through town or moving throughout the world, one can find both visible and hidden treasures and interact with certain objects.
Each ally unit is represented by a character with a background and personality. Some of these characters are hidden, requiring specific events to occur before they will join the force. Each ally unit also has a class, which defines the abilities for that unit. These abilities range from what type of weapons they can use to what kind of spells they can learn. Units can become stronger by fighting enemies and performing various actions which gives them experience points (EXP), which allow them to gain levels. Once a unit reaches level 20, that character has the ability to advance to more powerful class through promotion. Some characters have two different classes they may be promoted to, one of which is only accessible using a special hidden item.
Battles take place on a square grid, and each unit occupies a single square. Battle is turn-based. Each turn, a character can move and perform one action: either attack, cast a spell, or use an item. Some commands, such as equipping or dropping an item during the turn, do not count as actions.
The battle is won if all enemies are defeated, or if the enemy commander is defeated. If Bowie is defeated in combat or withdraws, the battle is lost and the player is returned to the nearest town, where he can recover his allies and fight the same battle again.</desc>
    <releasedate>19941002T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Camelot Software</developer>
    <publisher>Sega - Sonic! Software Planning</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Shinobi III - Return of the Ninja Master (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Shinobi III : Return of the Ninja Master</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Shinobi III - Return of the Ninja Master (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>The Shinobi master of stealth and the lethal ninja arts is back, bigger and deadlier than ever! Joe Musashi's sworn enemy, the Neo Zeed, grips the city in a vicious crime ring. Shadow Master, a super ninja cloned from Joe's own bloodline, controls the Zeed's savage army of bio-ninja. Musashi has no choice but to annihilate them all!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930822T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Megasoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Sonic &amp; Knuckles (World).zip</path>
    <name>Sonic &amp; Knuckles</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Sonic &amp; Knuckles (World).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Sonic and Knuckles join forces to defeat rotten Dr. Robotnik's Death Egg invasion! Play Sonic &amp; Knuckles by itself or Lock-on with other Sonic games. This game's revolutionary Lock-on technology adds all new features to your other Sonic games for ultimate replays! Play as Sonic and let loose on Robotnik with amazing new powers. Play as Knuckles and tackle Robotnik and Metal Sonic with bare-fisted attacks, high-speed glides and wall-climbing power! Lock-on with Sonic 3 and transform Floating Island into a huge 34 meg Sonic-epic loaded with new secrets! Play as Sonic, Knuckles, and even Tails - with Game Save! Lock-on with Sonic 2 and play as Knuckles with all his signature moves!</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action, Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Sonic Spinball (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Sonic Spinball</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Sonic Spinball (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Dr. Robotnik has assumed control of Mt. Mobius and turned it into a mechanical base. Utilizing energy produced by the magma flowing under the volcano, this new monstrosity (the Veg-O-Fortress) has the power to transform helpless animals into robot slaves at an astounding rate. Sonic the Hedgehog and Tails fly onto the scene to mount an aerial assault, but Sonic is knocked off the wings of Tails' airplane by a blast from the fortress. He falls into the water, but is rescued and taken to the subterranean levels of the Veg-O-Fortress. The fortress must be destroyed from the inside-out, and the only way to make that happen is to trigger an eruption in the volcano it's built on. Sonic knows this can be done by removing the Chaos Emeralds that keep the volcano stable. Robotnik, however, is also aware of the fragile relationship that exists between the Emeralds and the mountain, and he's set up an elaborate Pinball Defense System to make sure the precious jewels don't go anywhere.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931114T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Pinball</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Sparkster (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Sparkster</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Sparkster (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>He's back, and he's one oppumped-up opposum! SPARKSTER is jet-packin' into action as the toughest Rocket Knight to ever swing a sword. Grab the controls and blast through 8 wild stages in your quest to rid the world of the evil King Gedol and his allies - a pack of lizards that are tougher than a suitcase! Oh yeah, and before you get too comfortable - Axel Gear is here. This Rocket-Knight-gone-bad has a score to settle with Sparkster. Our hero will need his revved-up new rocket pack and powerful new attack moves to kick Axel's tail back to the dark side of the planet.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Splatterhouse 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Splatterhouse 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Splatterhouse 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Three months have gone by since the events of the first game. The Terror Mask, which has reformed after breaking at the climax of the first game, appears to Rick and repeatedly tempts him to "go back to the house", telling him that Jennifer "doesn't have to die". It closes by telling Rick "You need me.". Rick succeeds in rescuing Jennifer, and the House sinks into the bottom of the river.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Splatterhouse 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Splatterhouse 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Splatterhouse 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Splatterhouse 3 is a video game released by Namco for the Mega Drive/Genesis in 1993. It is the sequel to Splatterhouse 2 and was one of the first games to be given a rating by Sega's own Videogame Rating Council.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Now Production</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Sports</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Street Fighter II' - Special Champion Edition (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Street Fighter II' : Special Champion Edition</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Street Fighter II' - Special Champion Edition (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>From the corners of the globe come twelve of the toughest fighters to ever prowl the streets. Choose your champion and step into the arena as one of the eight original challengers or as one of the four Grand Masters! Pound your opponent as Balrog and knock them out for the count. Tower over your prey as Sagat and daze them with your awesome Tiger Shot. Slash your opponent with Vega's claw and send them running for cover. Or strike fear into your enemies as M. Bison, the greatest Grand Master of them all!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Streets of Rage 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Streets of Rage 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Streets of Rage 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Original rumblers Axel and Blaze slam the asphalt with bigger, better, totally devastating attacks! Skull-crushing ex-wrestler Max Thunder joins up with earth-shattering body slams and spinning fist attacks. New thrasher Skate slices punks with high speed in-line skate attacks and spinning jump kicks. Go maniac with jaw-shattering, bone-busting punches, head-cracking jump kicks and secret weapons. Gangs of dirt bikers dive into you from every side. Smash 'em with a pipe as they speed by. 16 gigantic megs of compound fractures! All new moves, and more of 'em! Bust knuckles with a friend in an all-new 2-player head-to-head mode!</desc>
    <releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Streets of Rage 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Streets of Rage 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Streets of Rage 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Snatch the Police Chief and replace him with a robot? Bomb city streets to splinters? Mr. X and the Syndicate surface once again to hatch the ultimate evil plot! Blaze Fielding launches a furious counterattack with Axel, Skate and cyborg newcomer Dr. Zan! Totally new moves including jump kicks, power slams and spin punches and secret attacks! Out-RAGE-ous 2-player combo attacks and head-to-head battles! Four bone-busting endings - the better you get, the more you see! Thrashing digitized sound FX and incredible street tunes!</desc>
    <releasedate>19970317T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Strider (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Strider</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Strider (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Set in the future, the game centers around a secret organization of ninja-like operatives known as "Striders", who specializes in various kinds of wetworks such as smuggling, kidnapping, demolitions, and disruption. The player takes control Strider Hiryu, the youngest elite-class Strider in the organization. Hiryu is summoned by the organization's second-in-command, Vice Director Matic, to assassinate his friend Kain, who has been captured by hostile forces and has become a liability to the Striders. Instead of killing him, Hiryu decides to rescue Kain from his captors. With the help of his fellow Strider Sheena, Hiryu uncovers a conspiracy between a certain faction of the Strider organization led by Matic himself and an unknown organization known simply as the "Enterprise" (headed by a man named Faceas Clay) which involves the development of a mind-control weapon codenamed "Zain". In the course of finding and destroying these Zain units, Hiryu learns that the faction of conspirators is headed by Vice Director Matic himself. Hiryu eventually tracks Matic to an orbiting space station where the two Striders face off; after a brief battle Hiryu bests Matic and kills him. Afterwards Hiryu locates and destroys the last of the Zain units.

In the epilogue, it is revealed that though Hiryu was asked to return to the Strider organization he instead opted to retire. The final credits show him sheathing his weapon and walking away.

" Sega produced their home version of Strider for the Mega Drive/Genesis, which was released in Japan on September 29, 1990, with subsequent releases in North America and the PAL region. It was advertised as one of the first 8-Megabit cartridges for the system, and went on to be a bestseller. This version was also re-released for the Wii Virtual Console in Japan on November 15, 2011 and later in North America on February 16, 2012. The Genesis/Mega Drive version contains a different ending from the arcade game. This ending shows the destruction of the final stage as the game's protagonist makes good his escape. This is then followed by the main credit sequence that sees Hiryu flying his glider in space and reminiscing about the various encounters he had during his mission as he heads back to earth. The ending theme was an edited combination of two separate pieces of music planned for the arcade game, but replaced with a repeat of the first level music. Computer magazine ACE considered the previous Amiga conversion to be "as good as this o</desc>
    <releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom - Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Strider Returns - Journey from Darkness (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Strider Returns : Journey from Darkness</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Strider Returns - Journey from Darkness (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>The warrior returns with a vengeance in his ultimate fight for freedom! A flash of steel, a blast from his devastating laser Gyro gun - Strider's back in action, pulverizing the enemy and striving for justice. This time, there will be NO LIMITS... NO MERCY... NO SURRENDER!

" Two years after the release of the computer versions, U.S. Gold and Tiertex ported Strider II to the Mega Drive. In addition to its European release, Strider II was also released for the American Sega Genesis under the title of Journey from Darkness: Strider Returns. The Mega Drive version of Strider Returns differs from the previous computer version in several ways. " -Wikipedia</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tiertex Design Studios</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom - Tiertex Design Studio - U.S. Gold</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Fantasy Zone (Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Super Fantasy Zone</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Fantasy Zone (Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <desc>The next-gen sequel to Fantasy Zone, Super Fantasy Zone starts as a strange gravitational force appears in the Menon planet, home of the evil Menon empire and thus a new threat looms over the Fantasy Zone.

In a sudden strike by the Menon forces O-Papa, Opa-Opa's father, is fatally wounded. Thus Opa-Opa once again sets forth to destroy the Menon empire and avenge his father.

EU release</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sega - Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Hyperstone Heist (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles : The Hyperstone Heist</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Hyperstone Heist (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Shredder steals the powerful Hyperstone to shrink New York City and it's up to you to teach that treacherous troublemaker not to mess with the fearless foursome! Pick your favorite Cowabunga commando to slash through 5 lawless levels of lambasting. Four levels each have 3 intense stages and the other is packed with brand new challenges that will make you hurl your pizza lunch. Pulverize shrink-happy Shredder before he pockets our whole planet!</desc>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Thunder Force II (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Thunder Force II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Thunder Force II (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Taking place soon after Thunder Force, the ORN Empire creates a powerful new battleship, the Plealos (a.k.a Preareos). Using this battleship, ORN once again attacks the Galaxy Federation. The outcome of the attacks result in the destruction of the Galaxy Federation affiliated planet of Reda, and heavy destruction on the planet Nepura (a.k.a. Nebula), which ORN eventually captures from the Galaxy Federation.
Eventually, the Galaxy Federation learns that ORN houses Plealos deep below Nebula's surface when not in use and takes the opportunity to plan an operation to take it down. They send the next iteration of their Fire Leo series of fighter craft, the FIRE LEO-02 Exceliza, to destroy ORN bases on Nepura and eventually find and destroy Plealos. The player controls the Exceliza and travels through a variety of stages to accomplish this goal.</desc>
    <releasedate>19890814T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technosoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Thunder Force III (Japan, USA).zip</path>
    <name>Thunder Force III</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Thunder Force III (Japan, USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>This masterpiece of shooting games takes you to a world of extraordinary proportions. It's the sequel to the explosive conflict that erupted in Thunder Force II. The unique backdrops scroll in three dimensions and offer you numerous surprises beyond imagination. Battle the enemy with a wide array of highly sophisticated weaponry. The menacing boss vehicles at the end of every stage have abilities unlike anything you've ever experienced.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900608T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technosoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Puzzle-Game, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Acme All-Stars (USA, Korea).zip</path>
    <name>Tiny Toon Adventures : Acme All-Stars</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Tiny Toon Adventures - Acme All-Stars (USA, Korea).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>Now those crazy Tiny Toon Adventures characters are creating sporting havoc! Create teams from amongst your favorite toons - each with their own individual techniques - for the wackiest games of soccer and basketball you've ever seen!</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Buster's Hidden Treasure (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Tiny Toon Adventures : Buster's Hidden Treasure</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Tiny Toon Adventures - Buster's Hidden Treasure (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Hit it big when you join Buster Bunny on a 33 stage hunt for treasure. So loaded with hare-raising animation, it's like playing in a whacked-out Tiny Toon cartoon! Do you dare to set paw on this mysterious island? Trip through 7 tangly territories that include an overly-enchanted forest, caverns of bubbling lava-lava, secret underground seas, plains that are just plain crazy, a freaky factory, a mega mountain and a spooky shipwreck rumored to be dripping in 14 carrot gold! Save Babs Bunny and the rest of your pals along the way and you'll really see some kooky island hopping. With Gogo Dodo as your guide, you can be sure this adventure is packed with tricks, traps, and hidden bonus areas!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./ToeJam &amp; Earl (World) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>ToeJam &amp; Earl</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/ToeJam &amp; Earl (World) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>ToeJam &amp; Earl has been called a surreal, comic satire, and a "daringly misanthropic commentary on Earthly life". The game's protagonists, ToeJam and Earl, have been described as a "three-legged red alien" and "fat orange alien", respectively. ToeJam wears a large gold medallion and a backwards baseball cap, while Earl is marked by high-tops and oversized sunglasses; both outfits are "over-the-top appropriations" of 1990s urban culture. Their speech features California slang. The game is set to a soundtrack which has been described both as jazz-funk, and as hip hop. For the game's unique sound, composer John Baker was inspired by Herbie Hancock and The Headhunters.

In the game's opening sequence, ToeJam explains that Earl's erratic piloting abilities have resulted in a crash-landing on Earth. He says that they must find the pieces of their spacecraft's wreckage to return to their home planet, Funkotron. The player guides the characters as they avoid Earth's antagonistic inhabitants and search for the debris. Should the player succeed, the final sequence depicts ToeJam and Earl escaping the planet in their reconstructed spacecraft. Under the player's control, the characters proceed across a purple landscape that represents Funkotron, and are greeted by their friends and family.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./ToeJam &amp; Earl in Panic on Funkotron (USA).zip</path>
    <name>ToeJam &amp; Earl in Panic on Funkotron</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/ToeJam &amp; Earl in Panic on Funkotron (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The plot of the game follows on from that of its predecessor, which followed the adventures of alien protagonists ToeJam and Earl after they crash landed on Earth. After escaping to their home planet of Funkotron, the characters discover that antagonistic Earthlings have stowed-away on the duo's spacecraft.

A sub-plot involves ToeJam and Earl's attempt to lure Lamont the Funkapotamus back from the Funk Dimension, where he is hiding from the invading Earthlings.

ToeJam and Earl must hunt down Earthling antagonists, which include a "pneumatic-drill-crazed construction worker, a camera-wielding tourist, our old friends the bogymen [sic], pea-shooter armed kids and a rather rotund woman with ankle-snapping poodles.

Capturing Earthlings involves rummaging for them in bushes and trees, before pelting the antagonist with "jars" which imprison them. The player completes a level by catching all the at large Earthlings and sending them back to Earth via spacecraft.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Tyrants - Fight through Time (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Tyrants : Fight through Time</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Tyrants - Fight through Time (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>First you choose one out of four different characters to represent you, Scarlet (red army), Oberon (yellow army), Caesar (green army), or Madcap (blue army). The game is split into 10 levels - the first 9 are groups of 3 territories which can be completed in any other, while the final 'Mother of All Battles' has its own surprises. 

Land is mostly of sand, grass or ice. You start with 100 men and you can use whatever quantity you find necessary on each island. The rest men left will go to another level with another new 100. In the second half of the game you can freeze men to save them for the Mother of All Battles. Once you select your island and place for your HQ, you must do some research for better weapons and defences. On the roof of your buildings you can put protectors like archers, gunmen, boiling oil men, and later on even laser turrets. If you send a team of unarmed men into an unoccupied square, they will build an additional base there, with larger armies completing this more quickly.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sensible Software</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Vectorman (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Vectorman</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Vectorman (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>In 2049, the human population of Earth embarks on a migratory voyage to try to colonize other planets. They leave mechanical "orbots" to clean up the mess they made on Earth through littering and pollution. Raster, a high-level orbot who watches Earth through a planetwide computer network, is accidentally attached to a working nuclear missile by a lesser orbot and goes insane, becoming an evil dictator named Warhead. He declares himself ruler of Earth, and begins preparing to execute any humans who dare return to their planet.

Enter VectorMan, a humble robot in charge of cleaning up toxic sludge by simply discharging it into the sun. As he lands on Earth after his last trip, he finds chaos and confusion. Because all the other Orbots are controlled by Warhead (VectorMan having not been affected because he was away), VectorMan takes it upon himself to destroy the errant orbot and restore peace to Earth.</desc>
    <releasedate>19951024T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>BlueSky Software, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Blue Sky Software - Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Vectorman 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Vectorman 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Vectorman 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>After saving Earth from Warhead in the previous game, VectorMan's sludge barge is targeted and destroyed by a missile. VectorMan escapes, parachuting down to the planet to battle with the Earth's multitudinous enemy; mutant insects. Now it is up to VectorMan to fight through the mutant bugs and find the most fearsome source infestation; the evil Black Widow Queen.</desc>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>BlueSky Software, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Blue Sky Software - Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Virtua Racing (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Virtua Racing</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Virtua Racing (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Virtua Racing is a home port of Sega's first ever 3D, polygon-based racing game for the arcade. The game consists of racing Formula-1-looking cars around a beginner, intermediate, or expert track, competing against a second player or computer drivers. Despite having Formula-1 cars, the game controls are very "arcadey" and players can see the leap they made from here to Daytona.

The Megadrive/Genesis version of Virtua Racing is of note as it is the only game for the system which features the SVP chip (Sega Virtua Processor). The chip is a 3D processor built into each cartridge (the console itself had no 3D capability) and is very similar to the SNES's SuperFX chips, used in games such as Starfox and Stunt Race FX.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940314T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Warsong (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Warsong</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Warsong (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>The Dalsis Empire has laid seige upon the Castle of Baltia to seize the legendary sword WARSONG. In a desperate attempt, King Alfador sends his only son, Prince Garett, into the countryside, away from impending death. Now Garett must rally his allies from across the kingdom, and lead their valiant armies in a battle against the Empire to retrieve the sacred sword! But, time is running short! Command troops and choose your mission commanders. Unite with loyal allies and charge into campaigns that forge the destiny of a realm. Between you and the path to victory lie dangerous rogues, the steel of Dalsis, and a confrontation in the ultimate showdown against evil!</desc>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Masaya</developer>
    <publisher>Treco</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games, Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Wiz'n'Liz (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Wiz'n'Liz</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Wiz'n'Liz (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Wiz 'n' Liz: The Frantic Wabbit Wescue is a platform game developed by Raising Hell Software for the Amiga and Sega Mega Drive and published by Psygnosis in 1993. It is a humorous, cutesy platform game. With the exception of some end-of-level bosses, the game contains no enemies.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Wizard Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Wonder Boy III : Monster Lair</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>Released in Japan and Europe for the Mega Drive. 

Wonder Boy III: Monster Lair is a quite different game to most of the games in the Wonder Boy series. You play a green-haired dude who must attack the invaders that attempt to collect weapons and use them to destroy the land. The game starts out like a simple platform game, but it's just when Wonder Boy enters the skull further on that the game is transformed into a shoot 'em up, so basically the gameplay consists of action and shooter scenes.</desc>
    <releasedate>19901222T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Westone</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Wonder Boy in Monster World (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Wonder Boy in Monster World</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Wonder Boy in Monster World (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Townsfolk cower in fear as legions of deadly monsters invade the planet. Only Wonder Boy can fight smart enough - and tough enough - to wipe out the terrible beasts. Sleuth out secret clues to thwart the undead. Match wits against an evil force of otherwordly dimensions. And prove the awesome strength and courage of the amazing Wonder Boy!</desc>
    <releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Westone</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games, Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <desc>Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel is a spin-off of the Aero the Acrobat games, its main protagonist being one of Aero's antagonists. The gameplay is similar to that of Aero the Acrobat games, involving fast-paced side-scrolling and platforming action. Zero can eliminate his enemies by executing his trademark Kamikaze Slam: spinning in the air and crushing the unlucky adversary. He can also collect shurikens (shooting stars) scattered across the levels, and use them for projectile attacks. The squirrel is able to perform double jumps to reach high platforms and jump over larger chasms.</desc>
    <releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Iguana Entertainment - Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Zero Wing (Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Zero Wing</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Zero Wing (Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>Zero Wing is an horizontal shooter game where the player is in control of a ZIG, an escape pod released after its main ship was attacked and destroyed by the evil cyborg CATS, bent on taking over the world.

Like most games in the genre, there are three color-coded weapons: red (scatter), green (homing) and blue (lasers). Each weapon has three levels of power, and to obtain those, similar upgrades must be collected sequentially. However, what makes the game unique is the ability to use a traction beam to trap an enemy and then throw him against his peers, destroying them.

The game (more precisely, the European PAL version of it) is known for being the origin of the grammatically incorrect phrase in the English translation, All your base are belong to us, which has since become an internet phenomenon.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920701T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Toaplan</developer>
    <publisher>Toaplan</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Zombies Ate My Neighbors (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Zombies Ate My Neighbors</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Zombies Ate My Neighbors (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Zombies have invaded your neighborhood and are trying to eat your neighbors. Try to save the neighbors, cheerleaders, and babies in 55 levels of action and adventure. Battle zombies, mummies, evil dolls, lizard men, vampires, and giant ants with a wide range of weapons including Uzi squirt guns, exploding soda, bazookas, weed whackers, and ancient artifacts. 

If you have a hard time getting through one of the levels, have a friend come over and help you out in the Two-Player mode. Save your neighborhood from a terrible fate in Zombies Ate My Neighbors.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>LucasArts</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
</gameList>