<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>./ActRaiser (USA).zip</path>
    <name>ActRaiser</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/ActRaiser (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>ACTION &amp; SIMULATION GAME
This sensational game combines pulse-stopping action sequences with an intelligent Simulation Mode, allowing the player to forge a new civilization. Finally......experience a game that fully utilizes the advanced capabilities of the Super NES.

Restore peace and order to your people's world! Long ago, you and your people built a peaceful land. Since then, your world has been taken over and inhabited by the evil Tanzra and his Guardians. Your once-tranquil land has become a breeding ground for monsters. Injured, you have retreated to your Sky Palace and have fallen into a deep sleep.

Now, many years have passed and you have recovered from your injuries and slumber. You must punish Tanzra and restore the world to your people or lose their faith forever.

Action Mode
Breathe life into the statue modeled after your likeness to cleanse the land and defeat the monsters who have conquered.

Simulation Mode
Help your people develop a new land from that which has been purified and build towns with your powers.</desc>
    <releasedate>19911102T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Quintet</developer>
    <publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./ActRaiser 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>ActRaiser 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/ActRaiser 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Gameplay for ActRaiser 2 consists primarily with side-scrolling platform action, similar to the "Professional!"/"Action" mode from the original game. The player, assuming the role of "the Master" (still referred to as "God" in the Japanese version), controls a floating palace to inspect the people of the world below. After hearing their plight the Master descends to the world below to fight the monsters and rid the land of evil. Like the original, each area contains two "acts"; the first act of an area consists of monsters spawned from a lesser demon named after an unfavorable condition, while the second act consists of monsters spawned from the primary evil, named after one of the seven deadly sins, with heightened challenge and peril.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Quintet</developer>
    <publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Aladdin (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Aladdin</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Aladdin (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Disney's Aladdin is based on the 1992 Disney animated film. For the GBA and the SNES editions development was handled by Capcom. Like other versions, the game is a side-scrolling platformer where the player controls Aladdin through locations from the movie like the city of Agrabah, the Cave of Wonders, and Jafar's palace. Some locations not appearing in the film include a trippy, candy-colored world inside the Genie's lamp and an ancient pyramid. Enemies standing in Aladdin's way include the Sultan's guards, animals and various magical creatures. They can be dispatched by jumping on top of them or by throwing apples at them. Besides jumping and throwing, another one of Aladdin's abilities consists of him pulling out a blanket and using it to slow his fall.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931102T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Alien 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Alien 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Alien 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>Alien&#179; is video game based on the movie sequel of the same name. The plot of the movie picks up directly after the end of Aliens. Ellen Ripley, the main character of the Alien series, is in cryo-sleep aboard the space ship Sulaco.

Unfortunately, an alien or two has stowed away on the Sulaco, and wreaked havoc within the ship. Thus, it crash lands on the prison colony planet Fiorina 161. Ripley and the unarmed prisoners have to figure out a way to survive the alien who terrorize the colony until help arrives.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930501T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Probe Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>LJN</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Axelay (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Axelay</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Axelay (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>An unknown alien race came to this planet and promptly laid waste to it. The remaining defense force has been sent out to try and defeat them. One lucky person gets to fly the latest line of defense ships made: the AX-77 Axelay. However, these ships are still in the prototype stage, and as such, only one exists.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Blackthorne (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Blackthorne</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Blackthorne (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>After years of awaiting his destiny on Earth, Kyle Blackthorne has finally come home to face the galaxy's most terrifying mutant monsters and goblin hordes. With brute strength, animal cunning and a lead-spewing shotgun he's on a quest to reclaim his once peaceful Planet Tuul.

Surrounded by enemies and confronting danger at every turn, Blackthorne's commando training and survival skills are put to the ultimate death-defying test in this brutally savage land. So prepare to enter Blackthorne's world and blast your way through one of the most intense, challenging games ever.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940923T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Interplay Entertainment Corp.</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Breath of Fire (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Breath of Fire</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Breath of Fire (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>NOW YOU'RE PLAYING WITH FIRE!
In a distant land, peace was maintained for thousands of years by a fearful dragon clan who could transform into powerful monsters. One day they discovered a goddess who could fulfill their every wish. Greed split the clan into Dark and Light Dragons, each battling the other to win her magic.

One member of the Light Dragons, along with seven of his companions, emerged to keep the opposing forces from destroying their world. Using six magical keys, they sealed the goddess into another realm.

Centuries have passed. The Dark Dragons are destroying the land in search of the keys. When they find the keys, they will once again release the magic goddess. Light Dragon... the time has come to draw your sword and fight for the future of your people.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Breath of Fire II (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Breath of Fire II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Breath of Fire II (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The incredible sequel to the best-selling RPG hit Breath of Fire is here! You are the last member of the Dragon clan, fighting to rid the world of a growing evil. A cast of unusual and exciting companions joins you in your adventures across a wondrous land full of magic and mystery. You'll find strange mystic items, memorable monsters and exotic locations in your quest to conquer evil. There's strategy and spellcasting galore in the hours of compelling action and adventure that awaits you. Breath of Fire II is the ultimate in RPG excitement!</desc>
    <releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Bust-A-Move (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Bust-A-Move</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Bust-A-Move (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Which will burst first: your concentration or the level you're working on? It takes more than just swinging the bubble-turret and taking aim on the falling ceiling; tactical planning and mental dexterity are the only way to string together three or more bubbles and 100 wins to make it through all the bubble and ego-bursting rounds of Bust-a-Move!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950301T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
    <publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Chrono Trigger (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Chrono Trigger</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Chrono Trigger (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>The 32-Meg quest begins.
The millennium. A portal is opened. The chain of time is broken. A young man is transported into the past, altering the course of history and the outcome of the future. He has to find his way home, but first he must travel to the outer edges of time to repair the world's chronology. On the way he encounters strange friends and foes, utilizes incredible devices and vehicles, and penetrates and neutralizes the fortresses of the past, present, and future. A paradox has been created. If he does not restore the order of time, nothing will ever be the same. He is the one who will become a hero. He is Crono.
*FROM THE CREATORS OF THE ACCLAIMED FINAL FANTASY SERIES
*CHARACTER DESIGNS BY AKIRA TORIYAMA</desc>
    <releasedate>19950822T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
    <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Contra III - The Alien Wars (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Contra III : The Alien Wars</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Contra III - The Alien Wars (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Welcome to 2636, the year the Notorious One gets even, with an unprecedented alien onslaught orchestrated to push 16-bit technology and its commandos to their ultimate reaches.

Plunge through a molten hot massacre on a high speed voyage to the guts of the archenemy alien. Scope out the side and top perspectives and backgrounds that do a 360 to engulf you in 3-D sensation.

Pick off solar slimedogs like the Mutant Megasquitos and the Psycho Cyclers while you scale over walls, swing from girders and ropes, hitch rides on a missile, whatever it takes. Sweat through six gut splitting stages, including the Battle of the Blazing Sky and the Mucho Grande Badlands.
The graphics are so real the explosions will nearly knock you off your feet. And the Boss Enemies are so gigantic, your screen can hardly hold them. You'll need to wrap both hands around artillery powerful enough to make today's weapons look like squirt guns. The Contra legacy is alive and dangerous!</desc>
    <releasedate>19920406T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter / Run and Gun, Shooter, Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Demon's Crest (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Demon's Crest</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Demon's Crest (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>The demon realm is peaceful until six wondrous stones fall from the sky. Each stone represents a portion of the Demon's Crest. When united, the stones of the Demon's Crest bring the user ultimate power over demons and humans.
These stones were so highly sought that clvil war broke out in the realm. The fight led to much bloodshed until one gargoyle emerged victorious: the red demon known as Firebrand.
After Firebrand&#8216;s final battle, his evil nemesis Phalanx ambushed Firebrand and stole the stones. Now Firebrand must recover the stones and unlte the power of the Demon's Crest before both realms fall into the hands of the sinister Phalanx!

*Morph into 6 different forms to explore new areas when you find parts of the Demon&#8216;s Crest
*Incredible Mode 7 effects as Firebrand flies high above
the demon realm, overlooking 7 intense levels
*25 items hidden in the realm. with different endings based on how many items you find
*For one player</desc>
    <releasedate>19941021T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./EarthBound (USA).zip</path>
    <name>EarthBound</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/EarthBound (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Intergalactic terror stikes the small town of Onett as a blazing extraterrestrial object crashes in the night! The earth now faces imminent destruction by the universal evil threat known as Giygas! Armed with a cracked baseball bat, a cookie and an ATM card, a courageous boy named Ness vows to save the planet from hideous destruction. He must first find his heroic companions, Paula, Jeff and Poo. Will Ness succeed in his attempts to ambush countless frightening monsters as he travels? The ultimate test lies in the impending encounter with the all powerful Giygas!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ape Studios</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Earthworm Jim (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Earthworm Jim</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Earthworm Jim (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>A crow is chasing a worm named Jim while in outer space Psy-Crow is chasing a renegade ship. The ship's captain has stolen an ultra-high-tech-indestructible-super-space-cyber-suit and Queen Slug-for-a-Butt has ordered Psy-Crow to get it, since it can make her more beautiful than Princess-What's-Her-Name. Psy-Crow blasts the captain and the suit falls to Planet Earth.

Back on earth Jim wonders if he is finally safe when an ultra-high-tech-indestructible-super-space-cyber-suit lands on him. Luckily Jim rests in the neck ring of the suit. Then the space particles begin interacting with Jim, causing a light-speed evolution. Jim soon realizes he is in control of the suit.

Jim overhears the Queen's plans for the suit and decides to meet this Princess...</desc>
    <releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Shiny Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Playmates Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Plateform / Run Jump, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Earthworm Jim 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Two times two is four! Too much to list, but keep reading:

From Evil the Cat's Circus of the Scars' to the planet of Meat, join Jim on a madcap chase across the galaxy. Saving cows, thwarting lawyers and outsmarting Psy-Crow are all in a day's work for Jim. Are you up to the challenge? Can you handle the awesome new weapon? Excellent! Then stop reading this. Take it up to the front counter and try it at home! Trust no one play it yourself... or EAT DIRT!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Shiny Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Playmates Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./F-Zero (USA).zip</path>
    <name>F-Zero</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/F-Zero (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>F-Zero is set in the year 2560, when humanity's multiple encounters with alien life forms had resulted in the expansion of Earth's social framework. This led to commercial, technological and cultural interchanges between planets. The multi-billionaires who earned their wealth through intergalactic trade were mainly satisfied with their lifestyles, although most coveted more entertainment in their lives. This resulted in a new entertainment based on the Formula One races to be founded with vehicles that could hover one foot above the track. These Grand Prix races were soon named "F-Zero" after a rise in popularity of the races. The game introduced the first set of F-Zero racers: Captain Falcon, Dr. Stewart, Pico, and Samurai Goroh.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920604T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving, Race 3rd Pers. view</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Fatal Fury (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Fatal Fury</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Fatal Fury (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <desc>The plot of Fatal Fury centers around a martial arts tournament known as the "King of Fighters" tournament, held in the fictional American city of South Town and sponsored by local crime boss Geese Howard. Ten years prior to the events of the game, Geese murdered a rival martial artist named Jeff Bogard who was on his trail. Now, Jeff's sons, Terry and Andy, along with their friend Joe Higashi, enter the tournament to get their revenge on Geese.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SNK</developer>
    <publisher>SNK</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Fatal Fury 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Fatal Fury 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Fatal Fury 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>ARE YOU READY FOR THE TOUGHEST CHALLENGE OF YOUR LIFE?
It&#8217;s time for 20 megs of non-stop action, with another super-hot arcade game for your Super Nintendo. Rejoin the brothers Andy and Terry Bogard, with their friend Joe Higashi as they discover that FATAL FURY was just a warm up! Now they must face the meanest, most dangerous fighters ever assembled!
Choose from among 8 fierce opponents; from Big Bear - the savage unmasked wrestler to Mai Shiranui-the female beauty with mystical arts of the Ninja. Battle through Thailand, Spain, Australia and many other locations. Feature packed, and filled with all the hard-hitting action you&#8217;d expect from Takara&#8217;s Fighting Series. Unique 30 movements enable you to move and tight both in foreground and background - in ways No other street fighting game can. This game rocks with huge, blazing arcade style graphics and faster animation than ever before! The question is - are you up to a new challenge?

*HUGE GRAPHICS AND INCREDIBLY FAST ANIMATION
*POWERFUL NEW MOVES TO LEARN AND MASTER
*UNlQUE 3-D ACTION - FIGHT IN BOTH FOREGROUND AND BACKGROUND
*1P VS COMPUTER (SELECTABLE), 1P VS 2P, AND NEW TEAM ELIMINATION FIGHTING
*PLAY AGAINST THE COMPUTER OR TAKE ON ANOTHER PLAYER IN HEAD-TO-HEAD
COMBAT
*FOR 1 OR 2 PLAYERS</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SNK</developer>
    <publisher>TAKARA Co., Ltd.</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Final Fantasy - Mystic Quest (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
    <name>Final Fantasy : Mystic Quest</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Final Fantasy - Mystic Quest (USA) (Rev 1).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>THINK YOU CAN SAVE THE WORLD?
Here's your chance to play the world's first role-playing game for the entry-level player.

The planet is dying. Cold winds blow. Fires rage. Trees are withering. In other words, it's brutal out there.
Only you can stop the Dark King from consuming the light from the Crystals of Earth. But don&#8217;t think it'll be a walk in the park. You're up against the sleaziest of slimebags, the evilest of ecto-scum - we're talking serious monsters here.
This isn't your basic shoot-em-to-smithereens kiddy game, either. You'll have to think your way out of some tough spots. Think you can handle that?

Free strategy guide available for a limited time with mail-in coupon. See inside for details.

*Entry-Level Role-Playing Adventure
*World's Best-Selling RPG Series
*Free Strategy Guide Offer
*Battery Back-Up Saves Up To 3 Games</desc>
    <releasedate>19921005T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
    <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Final Fantasy II (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
    <name>Final Fantasy II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Final Fantasy II (USA) (Rev 1).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>THE CRUSADE FOR THE CRYSTALS.
In the Kingdom of Baron, powerful airships rule the skies. At the head of this elite fighting force is Cecil, Captain of the Red Wings.
As our adventure begins, Cecil and his squadron are ordered to steal a powerful crystal from a rival kingdom. Upon their return, Cecil questions the King&#8217;s orders and is stripped of his command To prove his loyalty, he must slay a dreadful monster and deliver a mysterious package to a neighboring town. But when the package explodes, destroying everyone, Cecil and his friend Kain vow to fight the King &#8217;s dark forces. Will you be able to save the world from their evil plan to control the crystals?
Get ready for the most challenging role-playing adventure ever.

*16 BIT ROLE-PLAYING GAME
*8 MEG MEMORY
*BATTERY BACKUP SAVES UP TO FOUR GAMES
*76 PAGE PLAYER'S STRATEGY MANUAL
*STEREO SOUND</desc>
    <releasedate>19911102T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
    <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Final Fantasy III (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
    <name>Final Fantasy III</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Final Fantasy III (USA) (Rev 1).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>MagiTek has been reborn. And the end of the world is near.
Ages ago, evil beings created powerful creatures called Espers, and unleashed them against each other. The resulting battles left their world a smoldering rubble. Legend has it, the Espers destroyed themselves and most of humanity. Magic disappeared forever.

Centuries have passed and a rational world now exists with Espers living only in myths, until one frozen solid since the ancient wars is unearthed. Suddenly, there are reports of magical attacks on civilians. Imperial Commandos launch raids using magic-powered MagiTek weapons. Magic is obviously alive and the world is in danger again.

Who or what is behind the rediscovery and redeployment of this legendary power? What chaotic plans exists that will wreak havoc on this orderly world?</desc>
    <releasedate>19941011T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
    <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Final Fight (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Final Fight</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Final Fight (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Mayor Mike Haggar vows to snatch the streets of Metro City back from the crooks with his bare knuckles! But the Mad Gear Gang snatches his daughter Jessica. Now there's gonna be some bone-crunching dues to pay!

Jessica's boyfriend Cody hits the streets hard with Haggar, denting heads downtown and slugging it out in the slums. He's a one man army! His weapons are anything he can find -- swords, knives, or pipes.

Now you're Haggar or Cody, each with his own fighting style. Demolish gangland henchmen, samurai swordsmen and musclebound crime bosses in a fist-to-nose frenzy!</desc>
    <releasedate>19910901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Final Fight 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Final Fight 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Final Fight 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>It's Mad Gear Madness! They're back stronger than ever and they want revenge. With a new mysterious leader they plan to dominate the entire world. This time they've kidnapped Genryusai and his daughter Rena.

Now Haggar must travel around the world to search for Genryusai and Rena. But he's not going alone. Carlos and Rena's sister, Maki, are joining the slam-fest to put the gang away for good. Search for numerous weapons such as knives, nightsticks and 2x4's or find food to recover your strength.

Choose from Haggar, Carlos or Maki, each with their own style of fighting. Or have a friend join in for double the power and crush any punk that stands in your way.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Final Fight 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Final Fight 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Final Fight 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>YOU CAN TEACH A NEW SKULL OLD TRICKS

Metro City is under attack, and this time a new crime organization is claiming responsibility. Pulling pages from the Mad Gear Gang's guidebook, the feared group named SKULL CROSS are up to the same old tricks: arson, terrorism, assault, and armed robbery.

Mayor Mike Haggar returns with the potent Guy at his side. And with help from Cody's pal Lucia, and Dean, a revenge-seeking fighting machine, the Final Fight team will ambush the enemy at their next move. Choose to play one of the 4 characters, each with thier own fighting style and "SUPER" knock out techniques. Have a friend join in for a double assault on the city's scum and crush any punk that gets in your way!


-9 huge levels of action that really packs a punch!
-Pull off special attacks to power up your SUPER move meter and blam! The multiple-hit punch and kick barrage you unleash devastates your opponents!
-Make decisions on directions to travel-makes your fight different every time!
-Enjoy 2-player simultaneous fun, or try the new AUTO 2-PLAYER mode where the computer acts as your teammate!
-24-MEGS-The biggest Final Fight ever!</desc>
    <releasedate>19951221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Gradius III (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Gradius III</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Gradius III (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>SOMETHING NASTY IS GOING AROUND AND THE WHOLE UNIVERSE IS CATCHING IT!
The gentle Gradians thought they were cured of Bacterion&#8217;s contemptible curse after generations of germ-free living. Guess again. That wretched fiend is once again wreaking havoc on Gradius and the surrounding planets. It&#8217;s your destiny to put an end to it. Unless maybe you think life as an amoeba would be pleasant!
You play a key role in engineering your M.A.X. starship&#8217;s battle gear and arsenal. You&#8217;ll use masterful marksmanship and strategy to engage the right weapon at the right time, like spread bombs, ripple lasers, photon torpedoes, mega crush and much more. Do so and you&#8217;ll gallantly conquer the galactic gargoyles and obstacles in ten Terror Zones, such as the Dunes of Doom, Bacterion&#8217;s Garden, and The Greased Lightning Round. Just when you think you&#8217;ve made it through each of the Zones, you&#8217;ll be greeted by a hideous Mayor who will try to see that his Zone is your last. Choose from three difficulty levels to see just how keen your alien zapping skills are. Throughout your journey, you will be engulfed in magnificent stereo sound and stunning visual effects that will dazzle your senses.
In the final forum, you&#8217;ll have to be as tough as Orakian ore to confront Bacterion and disintegrate its hailstone of a heart. If you do, all that is good in the universe will breathe a sigh of relief. And if you don&#8217;t, you&#8217;ll hear the echo of a solitary clap and the final Dark Curtain will fall.

Featuring alternate play for two players, or play against the Super NES.</desc>
    <releasedate>19901221T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Harvest Moon (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Harvest Moon</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Harvest Moon (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Getting Back to the Basics
City kids of all ages will want to take in the natural beauty and breathe the fresh country air in this fascinating farming simulation game. Harvest Moon gives you a chance to experience first-hand the down-to-earth goodness of life on a farm. Instead of zapping zombies from Mars, your goal is to get by on old-fashioned hard work and dedication. Success in this game is measured by the fruits of your labor, so strap on the suspenders, roll up your shirt sleeves and dig in!</desc>
    <releasedate>19970601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Natsume</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Illusion of Gaia (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Illusion of Gaia</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Illusion of Gaia (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Journey into the Dark Side of an Ancient Civilization
Radiating an ominous light in its path, the Chaos Comet threatens the existence of the planet. Battles erupt and a tentative peace is returned to the lands. Danger lurks as the Chaos Comet orbits and dreadful beasts lie awaiting.
In the Age of Exploration a boy named Will is born. Tragedy strikes during an expedition to the Tower of Babel separating Will from his father. Telekinetic forces awaken as Will returns to South Cape. Armed with his transformation abilities of two great warriors, Will must save the planet.
Gaia, Will's guiding spirit bestows magical powers and advice along his journey. With the help of his friends Will must battle relentless enemies and solve the puzzles of the ancient ruins. Patience and knowledge are essential to reunite this father and son.

*Three players can save their journeys through entries into Will's travel diary.
*Battery back-up saves your progress.
*60 hours of game play
*Over 22 locations</desc>
    <releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Quintet</developer>
    <publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./International Superstar Soccer Deluxe (USA).zip</path>
    <name>International Superstar Soccer Deluxe</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/International Superstar Soccer Deluxe (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>It's a whole new ball game... Reallistic prites with 36 teams featuring recognisable celebrity players. Increased CPU intelligence to challenge beginners and experts alike. Choose from 15 formations, 8 strategies, 20 players and 9 adjustable player skills. Four way play possible with adaptor.</desc>
    <releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports, Sports / Soccer</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Joe &amp; Mac 2 - Lost in the Tropics (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Joe &amp; Mac 2 : Lost in the Tropics</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Joe &amp; Mac 2 - Lost in the Tropics (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>THE CROWN OF LEGEND IS GONE!
Our heroes, Ice and Mac, have volunteered to search for their leader's crown and bring it back so that peace can be restored. Of course, they're not risking their lives just out of the goodness of their hearts - they're out to impress the cave-babes, too!

Still, it&#8217;s loe and Mac. They may have a little problem with navigation. They'd better be careful not to get lost....

*8 megs of prehistoric action with password feature!
*l-player and 2-player modes - even a 2-player competitive mode!
*18 fast-paced, funny and fierce levels!
*Visit the Village Market for clues and power-ups!</desc>
    <releasedate>19940402T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
    <publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Jungle Strike (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Jungle Strike</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Jungle Strike (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Some time after Operation Desert Strike, Ibn Kilbaba, son of Kilbaba S.R, threatens to annihilate America. After his father was killed, the people who were under his control, sent his son running off, along with his father's money and nuclear weapons program. Kilbaba, more ruthless than his father, longs for revenge of his father's death and decides to shed the blood of those who killed him, the Americans. Already armed, Kilbaba hires Carlos Ortega to help him set up his Nuclear Weapons program, deep in South America. Carlos Ortega, the world's most notorious druglord, also yearns to seek revenge. With his own private army, armed with the most hi-tech weapons, he's ready to fight America at all costs.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Gremlin Interactive Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ken Griffey Jr.'s Winning Run (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ken Griffey Jr.'s Winning Run</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ken Griffey Jr.'s Winning Run (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>Ken Griffey Jr.'s Winning Run is a licensed arcade baseball game featuring MLB's own Ken Griffey Jr. Released in 1996, it contains all 28 MLB teams and logos from that time, with rosters containing fictitious names for the players (Ken Griffey Jr being the only real player in the game).

Next to exhibition games, there are different game modes to compete in. In the MLB Challenge, players start with a weak team and go against every major MLB club to go up the rankings. There is also a complete World Series, All-Star games and the MLB League. In the league modes up to eight players can choose a team and play a season of 26, 52 or 162 games. Between matches players can change the line-up and rotation, and trade away players.</desc>
    <releasedate>19960602T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Killer Instinct (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
    <name>Killer Instinct</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Killer Instinct (USA) (Rev 1).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The King of the Killer Arcades Comes to Super NES!
Don't wait in endless arcade lines to play&#8211;Killer Instinct comes to Super NES with action, graphics and sound that annihilates all other combat games!

Fulgore, Jago, B.Orchid, Spinal and all your favorite warriors contend in the Ultratech KI Tournament. Each combatant engages in the KI Combo Theory of connected moves and finishing tactics to destroy their opponents. With incredible displays of eyelasers, ice lances, wind kicks, and laser blades these fearless fighters prove their battle prowess. But remember, if you lose, it's hero to zero!

*The killer arcade classic comes to the Super NES with astounding graphics and incredible sound!
*The complete cast of famous fighters with all their special combos and finishing moves!
*Contains a colossal 32 mega-bits of incredible fighting action!
*Killer Cuts&#8482; Music CD included inside! This incredible CD is packed with the Killer Instinct soundtrack and remixed tracks for an added level of entertainment!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action, Fight / Versus</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Kirby Super Star (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Kirby Super Star</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Kirby Super Star (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <desc>Power up for EIGHT action-packed battles and adventures!
Dream Land is under siege again! Our hero, Kirby, returns to instigate a rescue. King Dedede is snatching up Dream Land's food supply, but he's not the only one! Dyna Blade, Meta Knight and a slew of other evil baddies are on the loose and wreaking havoc throughout the land.

Use any of Kirby's amazing powers to create a "helper" to assist you in battle. Or have a friend join you for some two-player action by taking control of Kirby's helper. Help Kirby work through EIGHT challenging games filled with action and adventure. Enter the fray in Spring Breeze, enter a foot race against King Dedede in Gourmet Race and tackle a winged warrior in Dyna Blade. Hone your reaction skills in Megaton Punch and Samurai Kirby, then battle your way through the Great Cave Offensive, Revenge of Meta Knight and Milky Way Wishes. Each game is different AND some extra-special surprises are in store for you!

*Includes EIGHT action-packed games and special surprises!
*Two-player action is possible when you activate Kirby's "helper" feature!
*Huge 32-meg game provides excellent entertainment value for Kirby fans of all ages!
*Battery back-up saves your progress and best scores!</desc>
    <releasedate>19960920T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Kirby's Avalanche (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Kirby's Avalanche</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Kirby's Avalanche (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>King Dedede has challenged Kirby and other members of Dream Land to an Avalanche Competition in the Dream Fountain. Kirby, taking on the challenge, has decided to battle his way through the forest and into the Dream Fountain to win the Avalanche Cup from King Dedede.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Compile</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Kirby's Dream Course (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Kirby's Dream Course</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Kirby's Dream Course (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Scan the course and check out the obstacles ahead. Get ready for the most surprising game play imaginable in Kirby's battle against King Dedede!

This checkboard challenge brings outrageous hazards and bizarre surfaces. Warp panels instantly transport you to new and exciting challenges. Conveyer belts provide higher levels of adventure. Turntables take the action in a whole new direction.

Gordo, Kracko, Whispy Woods and a cast of zany characters await you. Gain special powers including Fireball, Freeze, Spark and Parasol. Transform your enemies into stars revealing eight hidden cups of each wildly different course. Control the force and angle of your shot and sink Kirby for a hole-in-one!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Kirby's Dream Land 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Kirby's Dream Land 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Kirby's Dream Land 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Dream Land&#8217;s in trouble...AGAIN! Kirby&#8217;s back for more action in the latest chapter of the Dream Land saga. This time, though, Kirby has more help than he knows what to do with. In addition to his old pals Rick the hamster, Coo the owl and Kine the fish, there are three new friends to assist Kirby (not to mention Gooey, his blobby little sidekick). With all those friends, two-player simultaneous play and many other helpful surprises, Kirby should have no trouble saving Dream Land again, right? Not if King Dedede has anything to say about it!

*Two-player simultaneous play!
*Six different animal friends!
*48 different abilities!
*Mini-games galore!
*Battery-backed memory saves three different game files</desc>
    <releasedate>19971127T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>THE TRUE STRENGTH OF A MYSTICAL NINJA IS HIS WISDOM.
A curse has stricken the village of Horo-Horo. Their beloved princess has vanished. And without her powers, a plague of giant locusts will ravage the helpless. Talk about sick!
All hope rests on the village&#8217;s two ninja guardians. Kid Ying and Dr. Yang. Ying is a daring young mystical ninja who often rips apart opponents while riding a psychedelic tiger. Yang is his all-powerful mentor and master of the invincible spirit transformation. Together they must overcome ten Levels of the Dragonbeast, until they find the princess or die trying.
With double Warlock Stages in most levels and intense 3D and 20 zones blasting savage stereo sound effects, you'll be challenged to perform dozens of attack moves and solve magical problems betore advancing. And talk about enemies! There&#8217;s the Carp Meister, who stuns victims with poisonous fighting fish; Tanaka-U-Out, a knock out artist who wallops opponents with a bone crushing hammer; and the Sumo Tag Team, kings of the unbeatable belly buster crunch.
All-powerful sinjin items like the fire staff must also be captured. And if you fail to collect gotd coins from defeated foes you won&#8217;t receive important clues from the Fortune Palace and Char Cheddar Sushi Joint, or be allowed to go for broke at &#8220;hidden risk&#8221; areas such as the Quiz House and Horse Races.
But that&#8217;s only the tip of the volcano. Which is why your ultimate strength must come not from your might, but from your mind.
Featuring simultaneous play for two mystics, or play against your Super NES.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920202T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Lufia II - Rise of the Sinistrals (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Lufia II : Rise of the Sinistrals</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Lufia II - Rise of the Sinistrals (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>This exciting sequel to the Lufian legend pits monster hunter Maxim and six adventuring companions against the sinister Sinistrals. The story develops into a complex maze, challenging you with big battles, puzzles and loads of surprises. You can even grow your own monsters! You will enjoy countless hours on a fantastic journey in the world of Lufia!</desc>
    <releasedate>19960831T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Neverland</developer>
    <publisher>Natsume</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Madden NFL '94 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Madden NFL '94</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Madden NFL '94 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>Madden NFL '94 is the third in the Madden series of football games for the SNES. It features 80 teams -- 28 teams from the 1993 season, 38 Super Bowl teams from 1966-1991, 12 All Star franchise teams since 1950, and two "All-Madden" teams: one for the 1993 season and one from a 20-year time span. You can play these teams in a regular exhibition game or sudden death overtime game, or take the 1993 teams through an entire season. You can also enter the playoffs with the 1993 teams, the Super Bowl champions, or the All Star franchise teams. Unlike many other sports games, saving a season is done by password rather than by storing the data into a saved game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>5</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Madden NFL 95 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Madden NFL 95</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Madden NFL 95 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>John Madden's back in the 1995 version of Madden NFL. Play exhibition, Super Bowl, playoffs or full season with any of the 1994 teams or all Madden teams.

This time around, you can select whether or not to include weather conditions, new player animations (high steppin', QB slides), a bigger field and over 100 injuries.

Also includes windowless passing, all new Madden-designed strategies and team match-up that shows how your players stack up to the other team in their position.</desc>
    <releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Madden NFL 96 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Madden NFL 96</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Madden NFL 96 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <desc>Madden NFL '96 is a football video game designed for the 1995 NFL season, licensed by the NFL. It features John Madden on the cover. The AI has been boosted and can now hurry in two-minute drill situations, spike the ball, and cover the receivers with better efficiency. Among the innovations in Madden 96, the Create-a-Player feature was added, which included many position specific mini-games that would determine the ability of the player. The game also was the first in the Madden series to include secret "classic" teams, which were unlocked by playing any of the 28 pre-expansion NFL franchises in the playoffs and by winning Super Bowl XXX with that team (a rather easy feat as the playoff tournament system allows a player to abort the game while in the lead and still win). The 28 pre-expansion teams were each represented by a classic era equivalent, which ranged from 1960 (Philadelphia Eagles) to 1986 (New York Giants), although all players identified as number-only. Jacksonville Jaguars and Carolina Panthers, having debuted in 1995, did not have a secret classic team revealed in this manner, nor did the All-Madden team. However, Carolina was attached to the blank slate NFLPA team used for Create-a-Player, and Jacksonville and All-Madden hid the "superteams" with players named after the developers; these teams were accessed using unstated cheat codes.</desc>
    <releasedate>19951110T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tiburon Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>EA Sports</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Madden NFL 97 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Madden NFL 97</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Madden NFL 97 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Welcome to Madden NFL 97, the game that captures the excitement of a 30 yard touchdown pass, the strategy of a well executed scoring drive, and the atmosphere of a crisp autumn afternoon in the stadium. Madden NFL 97 delivers state of the art graphics and sound -- and with modem and network support, it's ready to put your competitive skills to the test.</desc>
    <releasedate>19961002T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>5</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Madden NFL 98 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Madden NFL 98</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Madden NFL 98 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Playcalling expert John Madden again licenses Electronic Arts' flagship football simulation. New features for 1998 include more advanced Quarterback functions such as the ability to play lob passes and adjust timing patterns, and more instinctive AI features to adjust as the match goes on. Squad features have also been advanced, with the opportunity to create plays and trade them.

Gameplay is much the same as the other editions, with the full season on offer as well as playoffs and the Superbowl. Everything is presented TV-style, with play-by-play analysis and reports. The contemporary NFL teams are joined by great squads of the past.</desc>
    <releasedate>19971102T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>EA Sports</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>5</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse, The (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse, The</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse, The (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Pluto has disappeared and his pal Mickey is hot on his trail! But evil Emperor Pete won't make it easy. He's snatched poor Pluto and hidden him deep within his dungeon. Now, Mickey must summon his courage and begin a treacherous trek through Emperor Pete's magical world to rescure his chum before it's too late!

Jump and touch the clouds as you and Mickey leap past buzzing bees and sinister snakes in the Treetops. Journey through the Dark Forest and dazzle Pete's guards with the power of Mickey's magical turban! Sink into the blazing inferno of the Fire Grotto and help Firefighter Mickey extinguish the flames! Scale the rocky heights of Pete's Peak and head straight for Emperor Pete's castle. Sneak inside, and Mickey must face the awesome might of Emperor Pete's sinister magic! Hurry! Pluto needs your help!</desc>
    <releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mario Paint (Japan, USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mario Paint</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mario Paint (Japan, USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Mario Paint lets you draw, paint, animate and compose music! Creation! Imagination is your only limit with an amazing variety of drawing tools. Animation! Add exciting dimension by creating moving animation with up to 9 frame sequences. Orchestration! Compose your own songs by selecting from over 15 different musical sounds and the entire scale of notes. Coordination! Increase your Super NES Mouse dexterity by playing Gnat Attack, the clever fly swatter game included inside.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920714T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Educational</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Man 7 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Man 7</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Man 7 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Dr. Wily's crusade to rule the world ends abruptly at the hands of Mega Man, so what's a villain to do? Create a diversion and break out of prison! Mega Man has his hands full as 4 gigantic machines exit Dr. Wily's lab to ravage the city, but... who is behind this new plot as Wily sits behind bars?

Dr. Wily knew his diabolical deeds would end an failure one day. So as hiss robots attack by remote control, the sinister doctor breaks out of prison and flies off in his spaceship. The Titanium Titan is tricked!

With the help of Rush, Roll and Dr. Light, can Mega Man put the slippery Dr. Wily back in prison where he belongs? The future of the world hangs on Mega Man's every move.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950902T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Man X2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Man X2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Man X2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Just when Mega Man X thought he had brought down all the X-Hunters, several months later an uprising moves from within an abandoned factory. While 8 all-new X-Hunters occupy Mega Man X, a triple threat plots to resurrect a secret weapon that is all too familiar!

The good Dr. Light supplies Mega man X with incredible new abilities hidden in capsules buried deep below the surface. And with new vehicles like the mobile attack cycle plus powers he gains from the X-Hunters, Mega Man X will be ready to face his destiny as a Maverick Hunter. Now it's all or Zero for Mega Man X!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950303T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Man X3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Man X3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Man X3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Mega Man X and his trusty partner Zero have a new force to reckon with. Who or what has caused a riot of Mavericks to break out in the experimental utopia known as Doppler Town?

Named after the scientist reploid, Doppler Town was supposed to be a place where humans and reploids could live in harmony. After discovering a virus that was turning reploids to Mavericks, Doppler's anti-virus was a big success. But Doppler itself became infected with the virus and assembled a team to take out the Maverick Hunter Units. The Doppler Effect is about to unfold, with Mega Man X and Zero the only cure for the deadly virus!</desc>
    <releasedate>19960214T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Metal Warriors (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Metal Warriors</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Metal Warriors (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>It's the year 2102 and the Dark Axis Forces - an intergalactic army threatening to enslave the Earth - are knocking at your door with a plasma-blast greeting. You've got a three ton laser-sword wielding, energy-cannon firing, jet-propelled suit of robotic armor at your disposal.

What are you gonna do?</desc>
    <releasedate>19950402T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mortal Kombat (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mortal Kombat</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mortal Kombat (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>PREPARE YOURSELF...

The #1 arcade hit is here: from Sub-Zero, Rayden and the rest of the Kombat Warriors to the grueling endurance and intense mirror matches! Execute bone-shattering combos and ferocious finishing moves! Defeat the half human dragon Goro, and destroy the shape-changing Shang Tsung to become the Supreme Mortal Kombat Warrior!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930913T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mortal Kombat II (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
    <name>Mortal Kombat II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mortal Kombat II (USA) (Rev 1).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Following his failure to defeat Liu Kang in the first Mortal Kombat game, the evil sorcerer Shang Tsung begs his master, Shao Kahn, to spare his life. He tells Shao Kahn that the invitation for Mortal Kombat cannot be turned down, and if they hold it in Outworld, the Earthrealm warriors must attend. Kahn agrees to this plan, and even restores Tsung's youth. He then extends the invitation to Raiden, who gathers his warriors and takes them into Outworld. The new tournament is much more dangerous, as Shao Kahn has the home field advantage, and an Outworld victory will allow him to subdue Earthrealm.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940909T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mortal Kombat III</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Fed up with continuous losses in tournament battle, Shao Kahn, who had lost to Liu Kang in the Outworld tournament, enacts a 10,000 year-old plan. He would have his Shadow Priests, led by Shang Tsung, revive his former Queen Sindel, who unexpectedly died at a young age. However, she wouldn't be revived in the Outworld. She would be resurrected in the Earthrealm. This would allow Shao Kahn to cross the boundary lines and reclaim his queen.
When Sindel is reincarnated in Earthrealm, Shao Kahn reaches across the dimensions to reclaim her. As a consequence of his action, the Earthrealm becomes a part of the Outworld, instantly stripping billions of their souls. Only a few are spared, as Raiden protects their souls. He tells them that Shao Kahn must be stopped, but he cannot interfere; due to his status, he has no power in Outworld, and Earthrealm is partially merged with Outworld.
Shao Kahn has unleashed extermination squads to roam throughout the Earthrealm and kill any survivors. Also, Raiden's protection only extends to the soul, not to the body, so his chosen warriors have to fight the extermination squads and repel Shao Kahn. Eventually with his final defeat, every human on Earthrealm comes back.
Mortal Kombat 3 follows Mortal Kombat II and shares continuity with both Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 and Mortal Kombat Trilogy which were both updates of this game. The next new game in the series was Mortal Kombat 4.</desc>
    <releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
    <publisher>Williams Electronic Games, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./NHL '94 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>NHL '94</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/NHL '94 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Aside from the licenses, the gameplay for this edition sees for the first time the inclusion of the devastating one-timer shot, but to keep forwards (literally) in check, defenders also feature harder body checks, with new animations. For an additional challenge, players can also choose to control the goalkeeper manually. A popular feature in previous editions, fighting is completely removed from the game. Game modes include exhibition games (or "regular season" in-game), playoffs (best of one or best of seven) and an all new shoot-out mode. The main options remain basically the same couple since the establishment of the series - period length (5, 10 or 20 minutes), line changes (off, manual or the new automatic mode) and penalties. (off, on, on but no offsides).</desc>
    <releasedate>19931002T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>4</players>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ogre Battle - The March of the Black Queen (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ogre Battle : The March of the Black Queen</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ogre Battle - The March of the Black Queen (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>It's up to you to defeat the Empire!
It's been nearly a quarter of a century since the Zetegenian Empire first conqured the Kingdoms of Zenobia with a wrath of fear and bloodshed. You are the leader of a band of rebels who have fought to preserve the last shred of honor in this desperate time of treachery. This sets the somber scene for Ogre Battle, the first in the superb line of fantasy, roleplaying and simulation sagas from Enix. Manage the ranks of a full-blown rebel army complete with hundreds of characters, magic items, weapons, and mystical Tarot cards. You must succeed in ousting the evil usurpers, as your fate, and that of the entire population, depends on it!</desc>
    <releasedate>19950501T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Quest</developer>
    <publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games, Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Pilotwings (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Pilotwings</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Pilotwings (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The Sky's the Limit!
Are you ready to earn your wings at the most exclusive flight school in the world? Then report immediately to the secret Pilotwings Flight Club, where your training begins!
You'll see the ground twist beneath you as you jump from your plane and attempt a precision skydive (don't forget to pull your rip cord!). You'll relive the early days of flying as you bring your biplane in for a pin-point landing. After you master the basics, you'll be called on to test an experimental rocket pack, soar in a hang glider, and pilot an advanced attack helicopter in a hazardous rescure mission.
The realism is incredible as the Super NES takes you airborne with multi-dimensional graphics, endless skylines and the freedom to fly wherever you like. Do you have what it takes to earn your wings? Then get going! You're late for your first class!</desc>
    <releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Pocky &amp; Rocky (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Pocky &amp; Rocky</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Pocky &amp; Rocky (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Pocky was enjoying a quiet cup of tea in her shrine, when Rocky the Raccoon, a Nopino goblin came running to Pocky.

"Something terrible has happened. My fellow Nopino goblins have lost their minds. When I woke up, they were very agitated. When I tried to calm them, they came after me."

"Why"?

"I don't know, but I believe that they are under the spell of another force.... In any case, I can not handle this by myself. I need your help."

Who on earth has cast the spell and are controlling the Nopino goblins? And what for? Find out as Pocky and Rocky battle the Goblins in this epic adventure from Natsume.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Natsume</developer>
    <publisher>Natsume</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Pocky &amp; Rocky 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Princess Luna was visiting from the moon for the joyous harvest day celebration. All the villagers were gathered around the festival square, eating, dancing and having a wonderful time. Meanwhile, far away on the Demon Island, Dynagon was plotting his revenge. After the beautiful Proncess Luna refused to marry him, Dynagon went into a frenzy.

Dynagon then ordered Impy, his most faithful servant, to go kidnap the princess from the harvest festival, in order to force her to get married to him.

"Help! Help!" cried the Princess, but it was too late. In a flash, She disappeared. Pocky stood in amazement as she watched the Princess vanish.

As Pocky and her partner, you are about to embark on a fantastic and dangerous adventure to rescue the Princess. You will need to use your wits and bravery to reach the end of your journey. Are you up to the challenge?

- Seven different partners to choose from.
- Outstanding graphics and music.
- Plenty of unique and playful moves.
- Action/Adventure game for the entire family.</desc>
    <releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Natsume</developer>
    <publisher>Natsume</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Populous (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Populous</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Populous (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>You play a god, gaming against other gods in a celestial game of conquest. To win, you must help your chosen people take over the world and wipe out the vermin who worship that other god.

Each god starts out with a single human, dumped into the middle of the wilderness. Sometimes there is inhabitable land in sight, sometimes not. To get win, you must change the landscape, creating flat land for your followers to build on. The more followers you have you have, the more powerful you will be, so take care of them. Build as fast as you can, because the other god is doing the same.

When you have enough followers, you can make the leader of your people into a hero. He will then go around the land you have built, literally taking strength from the people into himself, and working his way toward the enemy. When he gets there, he will engage in holy warfare upon your enemy's people. He will burn; he will kill. And he won't stop until they're all dead... or he is.</desc>
    <releasedate>19901216T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Bullfrog Productions</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Rock n' Roll Racing (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Rock n' Roll Racing</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Rock n' Roll Racing (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>The game pits four racers against each other, with up to two of them being player-controlled and the rest being AI opponents. Each race consists of four laps around tracks viewed from an isometric perspective, which enables players to discern the presence of frequent sloping sections spread throughout the game's various tracks. In addition to navigating the turns, racers must also maneuver hills and dips without falling or jumping over the guard rail at the track's edge.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Silicon &amp; Synapse</developer>
    <publisher>Interplay Entertainment Corp.</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Secret of Mana (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Secret of Mana</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Secret of Mana (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>GOOD AND EVIL BATTLE FOR A YOUNG WARRIOR&#8217;S HEART.
There is one force in the universe that keeps good and evil in perfect balance. It is called the tree of Mana. But a magic sword has tricked a young warrior into upsetting this balance, spreading evil throughout the land.

Thus, the warrior must undertake a dangerous journey to find the seeds of the Mana tree which have been hidden for centuries. Only then can perfect harmony be restored.

In this incredible adventure, things are not as they seem. Magic swords release evil as well as fight it. Treasure chests hold booby traps. Monsters are friends and friends are enemies. Potions give power, black magic takes it away. Dragons fly, weapons change.

It&#8217;s a world turned upside down that you must help the warrior make right. And the only way to succeed is to solve the Secret of Mana.

Brought to you from the makers of the Final Fantasy series.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931003T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
    <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>3</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Shadowrun (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Shadowrun</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Shadowrun (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Disoriented and confused, you are forced into a race against time, technology and termination. Running in the shadows and cracks between the Megaplexes, survival depends on your wits, your weapons and your wayward companions. Plunge into the dark side of the future, where technology and magic become one, where devolution and destruction are a way of life. Plunge into Shadowrun.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Beam Software</developer>
    <publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./SimCity (USA).zip</path>
    <name>SimCity</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/SimCity (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>SimCity sets you as the mayor of a new municipality, with the responsibility of building and maintaining a place where citizens can move to and work and be happy. The first task is to place essentials such as housing, transport links, schools, factories and shops. There are 50 types of these, allowing for homes of all standards and different types of businesses. Make sure to consider which sites are effective for which tasks. Some power sources pollute, others don't but are more expensive. Taxes must be raised to ensure an income, and then portions allocated to public services such as policing and roads. Earthquakes, floods and fires are all emergency situations that must be dealt to contain any damage.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Soul Blazer (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Soul Blazer</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Soul Blazer (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Obsessed with the desire for wealth, King Magridd cut a dastardly deal with the ruler of evil: one gold piece for each soul in the kingdom. Now the Freil Empire is in shambles and you are sent by the Master to save it. Free the kingdom&#8217;s captive souls. Teach the King a thing or two about integrity. Rescue a beautiful maiden. Liberate an imprisoned inventor.

Your journey will lead you across six mythical lands in this action-RPG. Gather the six stones to enter the World of Evil and confront Deathtoll. Then make him pay&#8230;</desc>
    <releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Quintet</developer>
    <publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Sparkster (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Sparkster</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Sparkster (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>HE&#8217;S ONE OPUMPED-UP OPOSSUM!
SPARKSTER is jet-packin&#8217; into action as the toughest Rocket Knight to ever swing a sword. Grab the controls and blast through nine wild stages in your quest to rid the world of the nasty Colonel Wolfheim and his allies - a tough pack of wolves that aren&#8217;t here to dance!

Oh yeah, and before you get too comfortable - Axel Gear is here. This Rocket Knight-gone-bad has a score to settle with Sparkster. Our hero will need his REWED-UP new rocket pack and powerful new attack moves to kick Axel&#8217;s tail back to the dark side of the planet.

Come on. Don&#8217;t waste time on games that were designed for somebody&#8217;s little brother. Take Sparkster for a spin and feel what real adventure is! You&#8217;ll sizzle through the secret rooms in the ancient pyramid and stomp wolf hide in a midair battle. Search for the power-ups and avoid opossum-squelching traps, and see some of the most amazing boss characters ever put into a video game. Feel the opower of the opossum!</desc>
    <releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Street Fighter Alpha 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Street Fighter Alpha 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Street Fighter Alpha 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES?

The bad boys from the Street Fighter series are back for more fisticuffs of fury! Eighteen different combatants, some old and some new, are here to lay claim to the title "World's Best". Screamin' moves like Ken's Dragon Punch, Adon's Jaguar Tooth and M. Bison's Somersault Skull Driver will blow you away! Play alone or pummel a friend in two-player simultaneous action. This ain't no cakewalk. This ain't no cakewalk. This is Street Fighter Alpha 2 and it's blazing on your Super NES!</desc>
    <releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Street Fighter II (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Street Fighter II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Street Fighter II (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>GET READY TO RUMBLE!

From across the globe comes eight of the wildest fighters the world has ever known. Choose your champion, gather your courage and prepare to battle your opponents in a bare knuckle brawl. Face Ken and his devastating "Dragon Punch"! Watch the temperature rise as Dhalsim incinerates you with his mystical Yoga Flame! Hear your spine crack as Zangief smashes you to the pavement with his spinning pile driver! Cover your ears as Guile breaks the sound barrier with the awesome power of the Sonic Boom!

Annihilate your competition and claim the right to test your skills against the bone-crushing power of the Grand Masters! Can you survive? Can Anyone?</desc>
    <releasedate>19920610T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Street Fighter II Turbo (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Street Fighter II Turbo</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Street Fighter II Turbo (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <desc>Feel the Need for Speed!

They're back and they're badder than ever! Faster, stronger and with all new moves, twelve of the greatest fighters from across the globe are ready to do battle! Choose your champion and get ready for the big brawl as they try to earn the right to battle M. Bison for the title. And just when you think you've mastered it all, crank it up a notch and go TURBO!

Cover your head as Blanka dives at you from above and hear your neck crack as Zangief hits you with the Turbo Spinning Clothesline. Stare in disbelief as Dhalsim disappears before your eyes and Chun Li unleashes her blazing fireball! Watch in awe as Sagat fights Sagat and Ryu does a Hurricane Kick in mid-air! Survive all this and you may live long enough to become the greatest Street Fighter ever!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Sunset Riders (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Sunset Riders</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Sunset Riders (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The Wild West...full of the criminal element. Sir Richard Rose, the most despicable face in the criminal lot, has enough power to control the mining facilities, cattle ranches, and trading communities and turn everything to his favor. With that much power, he could literally buy himself the Wild West and control everything!

The people need help, desperately. And just as things were looking grim, who should ride into town but 4 men who have made a pact: to put down Sir Richard Rose and make the Wild West a free and peaceful place to live.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Bomberman (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Bomberman</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Bomberman (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Super Bomberman is the first video game in the Bomberman series to appear on the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. It is also the first four-player game to be released on the Super NES.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Bomberman 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Bomberman 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Bomberman 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Five evil cyborgs, called the "Five Dastardly Bombers" are bent on taking over the universe. At the planet Earth, they capture the original Bomberman, and he is placed in a prison cell in their base. He awakens in the dungeon of Magnet Bomber and must fight his way to a final showdown with the Magnet Bomber himself. In the following four levels, Bomberman will challenge Golem Bomber, Pretty Bomber, Brain Bomber, and their leader, Plasma Bomber in an effort to free the Earth of these alien invaders as well as save himself.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950223T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Produce</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy, Action</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Bomberman 3 (Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Super Bomberman 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Bomberman 3 (Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>This game scales back a lot of gameplay additions made in Super Bomberman 2 and returns to the classic formula. As for multiplayer, the game adds a lot over the previous game by adding more characters, each representing a country of Earth (including one of the villains, Pretty Bomber, as France, which marks her first appearance as a non-enemy character). There are also new cutscenes for the Story mode, which centers around the resurrection of the Five Dastardly Bombers who were previously defeated in Super Bomberman 2, as Shirobon and Kurobon adventure across various element themed stars in which the Five are causing havoc, under the rule of their creator, Bagular.</desc>
    <releasedate>19951015T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Castlevania IV (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Castlevania IV</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Castlevania IV (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>THE GRAVEST CASTLEVANIA ADVENTURE BREAKS NEW GROUND...AND BURIES YOU IN IT.
A century of Transylvanian tranquility is about to come to a shocking end. Once again the mortifying screams of helpless villagers shake the ground as they huddle against new nightmarish horrors unleashed by the Duke of Darkness, Count Dracula. And this time he has a tombstone with your name on it, Simon Belmont.
You must descend into Castle of the Undead and its gruesome ground, accompanied by the most chilling sound effects to ever tingle your spine. Inside, a freshly dug 11 levels maze features the treacherous Terrace of Terror, the dangerous Rotating Dungeon, the Sunken Ruins of Lost Spirits, torture chambers and creature filled caves. Use your whip like a grappling hook and swing past hundreds of traps and a host of ghost freaks, living corpses and hidden goblins. All while dodging or destroying the unpredictable spitting lizards, carnivorous coffins, and more.
Find the concealed weapons needed to defeat everything from eerie phantoms to haunted furniture. Then prepare to find yourself face-to-thing with hideous torments like the Tongue Lasher, the Darkest Knight, the Bone-Afide Horseman and the Granite Crusher. When your nerves get shot, use your password and take a breather. But forge on, Simon Belmont, because if you though Dracula was down for the count, he's only just begun to fright!</desc>
    <releasedate>19911031T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Double Dragon (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Double Dragon</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Double Dragon (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The two greatest martial arts heroes of all time are back -- in SUPER DOUBLE DRAGON, an all-new adventure with awesome new moves, impossible new missions, and a hair-raising new cast of enemies!
Marian, a beautiful policewoman, is a student of Kung Fu and part-time assistant instructor at the martial arts training school run by Billy and Jimmy Lee. A narcotics investigator, she has disappeared while attempting to infiltrate the rughtless criminal mob known as the Black Shadow Warriors.
It will take all your incomparable fighting skill and knowledge to find and rescure Marian. Alone, or with the help of your brother, you must face the fearsome onslaught of the Shadow Warriors with the fabled power and ferocity of the DOUBLE DRAGON!</desc>
    <releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technos</developer>
    <publisher>Tradewest, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Ghouls'n Ghosts (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Ghouls'n Ghosts</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Ghouls'n Ghosts (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>As dauntless knight Arthur you are caught up in the most dangerous of quests! A spell has been cast upon the kingdom. Your fair maiden, Princess Prin Prin has been snatched up by the evil emperor. Only as Arthur can you get her back from the creatures of the undead that haunt the land. Test your courage and skill to the limit. You must keep up the quest. On your journey, your mightiest weapon of all awaits you... MAGIC!</desc>
    <releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Mario All-Stars (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario All-Stars</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Mario All-Stars (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Revisit the magic and fun of the classic Super Mario Bros. series on your Super NES!  All the great Super Mario Bros. games for the NES have been powered up with 16-bit graphics and sound and collected on one super game pak.  As an added bonus, the previously unreleased &#8220;Lost Levels&#8221; are included.  These super challenging courses have never been available in this country until now!

* Four great games in one game pak!
* Battery backed memory saves up to 4 players&#8217; progress through every game!
* Play alone or 2 players can alternate play!
* New 16-bit graphics, sound, and other surprises!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Compilation, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Mario Kart (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario Kart</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Mario Kart (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The Super Mario GoKart Park is open for tons of racing fun!  Hit the track with Mario, Luigi, Yoshi and the Princess.  Get tough and lock fenders with Donkey Kong, Jr. and Bowser.  Even Toad and Koopa Troopa will mix it up in an all-out quest for the Gold Cup!  Race head-to-head with a friend or challenge the computer in great, split-screen, Mode 7 graphics.

Feel like a bit less speed and a lot more strategy?  Take a crack at the Battle Mode!  In four different maze-like courses you&#8217;ll use Koopa Shells, Banana Peels, Super Stars and other wacky weapons to burst your opponent's target balloons and triumph!

* 2 games in 1 - Mario Grand Prix and Battle Mode
* 8  Familiar Characters
* 20 Different Tracks
* 3 Different Skill Levels
* Battery-backed memory saves your best times!</desc>
    <releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving, Race 3rd Pers. view</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario RPG : Legend of the Seven Stars</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Mario returns in this incredible new role-playing adventure! His latest rival is Smithy, a menacing creature who causes fear and treachery in the Mushroom Kingdom. Mario must recover seven stars and repair the Star Road before he can make his way to Bowser's castle for a final confrontation with Smithy. Powerful weapons, sinister spells and other useful items help Mario to complete his harrowing journey. New friends and old allies support him along the way. Even Bowser lends a hand!</desc>
    <releasedate>19960513T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Mario World (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario World</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Mario World (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Mario&#8217;s off on his biggest adventure ever, and this time he&#8217;s brought along a friend.  Yoshi the dinosaur teams up with Mario to battle Bowser, who has kidnapped Princess Toadstool once again.  Guide Mario and Yoshi through nine peril-filled worlds to the final showdown in Bowser&#8217;s castle.

Use Mario&#8217;s new powers and Yoshi&#8217;s voracious monster-gobbling appetite as you explore 96 levels filled with dangerous new monsters and traps.  Climb mountains and cross rivers, and descend into subterranean depths.  Destroy the seven Koopa castles and find keys to gain entrance to hidden levels.  Discover more warps and thrilling bonus worlds than ever before!

Mario&#8217;s back, and this time he&#8217;s better than ever!</desc>
    <releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario World 2 : Yoshi's Island</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island (USA) (Rev 1).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <desc>Yoshi Returns to Save Baby Mario in this Sequel to Super Mario World!
The Evil Magikoopa, Kamek, is out to kidnap Baby Mario!  In this sequel to Super Mario World, you play as Yoshi.  Your goal is to successfully carry Baby Mario back to his parents in the Mushroom Kingdom while avoiding all of Kamek&#8217;s clever traps and evil minions.  Enjoy the various backgrounds of the rich and vibrant locales of Yoshi&#8217;s Island as you race to complete your quest.

Is Yoshi up to the momentous task at hand?  Help him toss his eggs, manipulate unique objects and solve puzzling situations!  When in doubt, don&#8217;t be afraid to try EVERYTHING!!

* 16 megs of memory provide 6 worlds - each with 8 stages!
* Morphmation delivers powerful special effects - scaling, rotating, and 360 degree scrolling.
* Huge characters and even bigger bosses require quick thinking!
* Battery back-up to save your progress.</desc>
    <releasedate>19951004T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Punch-Out!! (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Punch-Out!!</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Punch-Out!! (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Slug your way through the grueling and sweat-pounding matches of the Minor, Major and World Circuits. Dodge bone-bruising punches and dance to the top of the supreme Special Circuit. Face off against old favorites including Bear Hugger, Piston Hurricane, Bald Bull, Mr. Sandman and Super Macho Man plus a cast of new and weird challengers. With a right hook! Body blow! And precise quick jabs! The referee announces "Knock Out!" Your opponent lies face down as you win the title of Nintendo Video Boxing Association Champion!</desc>
    <releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Star Wars - Return of the Jedi (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
    <name>Super Star Wars : Return of the Jedi</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Star Wars - Return of the Jedi (USA) (Rev 1).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Join the Rebellion and crush the Death Star in a giant 16-meg universe filled with all the action and adventure of the Star Wars finale. The command of five different characters-- from Wicket the Ewok to Princess Leia--and go up against the Empire's worst, from Jabba the Hutt to the Emperor himself! This is it! You're going to need every ounce of Force you're got in you.</desc>
    <releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
    <publisher>JVC Musical Industries, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
    <name>Super Star Wars : The Empire Strikes Back</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back (USA) (Rev 1).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Pursued across the galaxy, and your Rebel Forces now marshall new strength on the remote ice world of Hoth. Although tracked by probe droids, attacked by ice monster, and confronted by an army of gigantic Imperial Walkers, you must not give in. You are the Alliance's only hope. Learn the ways of the Force, then test your skills in this fast-paced, action-packed sequel to the high game, Super Star Wars.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
    <publisher>JVC Musical Industries, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Tennis (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Tennis</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Tennis (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>The world circuit of tennis awaits you. Select from 20 male and female players, each with their own style of game play (strengths and weaknesses) and play singles, doubles either against or with a human opponent or a CPU controlled player(s) on all the major surfaces (clay, grass &amp; hardcourt).

The circuit mode is the meat of the game. Here, using a password save system, you play a selection of tournaments all around the world. The more games you play and win, the more points you receive. These points go towards your rank in the world tour rankings. There are 4 major tournaments (as in real life) and many minor tournaments to play.</desc>
    <releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Turrican (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Turrican</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Turrican (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Super Turrican is the next generation installment of the famous Turrican Series. Once again it is up to the U.S.S. Freedom Forces to get into their Turrican Assault Suits and drive back the forces of "The Machine".

Similar to it's predecessors, Super Turican features large levels that are crammed with secrets and can be explored freely and in any direction. To get rid of the numerous enemies, Turrican can use three upgradeable shots: A spreadshot, a powerful laser and a rebound that bounces off of walls. Additionally, there is a Freeze-Beam that can be used to temporarily freeze enemies. It is fully rotatable, and therefor also a great help in discovering secret capsules. These capsules contain powerups and can often be used to reach secret areas. Last but not least, Turrican has the ability to transform into an energy wheel (as long as he has enough special energy), which enables him to lay mines and even makes him invincible.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Factor 5 GmbH</developer>
    <publisher>Seika Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Turrican 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Super Turrican 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Turrican 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Twice the Firepower, Twice the burn.

If you haven&#8217;t played Super Turrican, chances are you won&#8217;t last past the intro sequence here... As an intergalactic hero-wannabe commissioned to crush a venomous mutant armada, you are thrust into a chaotic world even more violent than the original. This time there are more enemies to torch (and be torched by)-including the most heinous level bosses on 16-bit-and enough Mode7 graphic levels to make you wish mommy were there to hold your hand. But she&#8217;ll be busy cleaning up your charred carcass.

Super Turrican 2. Feel the burn.</desc>
    <releasedate>19951102T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Factor 5 GmbH</developer>
    <publisher>Ocean Software Ltd.</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV - Turtles in Time (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV : Turtles in Time</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV - Turtles in Time (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Sunday evening. You're sitting around the sewer watching your main reported, April O'Neil do a live remote from the Statue of Liberty. Then it happens. A humungoso flying android screams out of the sky and rips Lady Liberty from her foundation, sending hundreds of freaked out tourists into the harbor below. "No way!" cries Raphael. "Way," replies Donatello. And the crazy quantum chase is on!
Journey through ten levels of enormous arcade graphics, the largest and craziest talking Turtles ever with eons of bodacious battlegrounds, from prehistoric to futuristic galaxies. To prepare for the toughest Shred-heads you've ever seen, try the Versus mode, a Turtle-on-Turtle combat arena that finally proves who's the mightiest mutant of all. Also test your slice-em-up speed in the Time Trials mode to find out how fast you can clear three courses.
Get ready for the 3-D jab and toss that sends enemies flying right in your face. Mondo body slams and pizza power bonuses make you more Turtle than ever before. You better believe you're going to need it. Shredder's out for Turtle hide. And he's got all the time in the world to get it.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Tetris &amp; Dr. Mario (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Tetris &amp; Dr. Mario</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Tetris &amp; Dr. Mario (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The two greatest puzzle games are now together in one exciting game pak only on Super NES! TETRIS: The relentless building block video puzzle from Russia is back and enhanced for Super NES. Play solo, with a friend or challenge one of three computer opponents in this exciting and addicting game! DR. MARIO: Those nasty viruses have returned. Dr. Mario, vitamin pills in hand, is ready to eliminate them once more. In addition to the ever-popular 2-player game, now you can challenge the computer in the guise of the Blue, Yellow or Red Virus. MIXED MATCH: Combine Tetris and Dr. Mario and what do you get? One exciting contest for 2 players! Race against the clock to outscore your opponent while playing both Tetris and Dr. Mario!</desc>
    <releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game, Compilation</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Buster Busts Loose! (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Tiny Toon Adventures : Buster Busts Loose!</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Tiny Toon Adventures - Buster Busts Loose! (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>It's just like a real cartoon, except you're the main character!

But be warned. Accept the role of Buster Bunny, and your tail will be on the line against Calamity Coyote, Elmyra, Dizzy Devil, Dr. Gene Splicer, Montana Max and gazillions of other 16 bit bullies craving a pot of Hasenpfeffer stew. Gulp!

Only you can stop those pesky pranksters from getting the jump on your pal Buster Bunny. But it won't be cake, Jake! You'll have to use Buster's all new Spin Kick and Mad Dash to bust through ACME Looniversity's toughest classes. If you pass that test, you'll hop aboard a Wild West Train Ride. Then explore a spooky Monster Mansion. Play in a far-out Foot Game. Bounce through an aerial Sky Jinx in search of stratospheric treasures. And blast-off on a Babs Bunny (no relation!) rescure mission that's totally spaced-out.

Ready to fork over the bucks, Buster? Well hang on your ears - there's more! Between each level are five subgames, including Furrball's Championship Squash, Hungry Boy Hamton and Plucky Duck's Go-Go Bingo. SO ACTUALLY IT'S LIKE ELEVEN GAMES IN ONE! And we haven't even mentioned the Pinball Wizardry, Acme Anvils and Icky Tricky Sticky Traps that'll make you feel like you're in an actual cartoon.

Wow! To make it through all that Buster better have a lucky bunny's foot. Or else you'll be the one getting stewed!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Top Gear (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Top Gear</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Top Gear (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>In the first of three released games for Super NES, players can choose among 4 different cars, each one with different attributes (maximum speed, fuel consumption, boost power and tire grip) to face 32 challenging courses situated in several places around the world as Brazil, USA, France, Japan etc.

In more longer tracks, players will find a Pit Stop section, where they can enter to replenish the fuel meter (total or partially). The game has a split-screen display for 1 or 2 players. In 1-Player mode, you'll dispute the races against the computer, that has a slightly bigger speed than yours, helping to give a lot more of competitiveness. A password system was included, being possible to stop a current game and resume it later.

Through the game, players will find several obstacles scattered by the courses, like rows of iron plates or even lots of stones. In order to qualify for the next circuit, it's required to complete it at least in the 5th position, or else the game is over.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920401T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Kemco</developer>
    <publisher>Kemco</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Top Gear 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Top Gear 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Top Gear 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>This third-person racing game resembles Gremlin's earlier Lotus series, in terms of its general look and feel, right down to the text font used in the game. Your task is to race through 16 countries, each of which features four races, with many real-world circuits recreated in incongruous locations (such as the Monza layout in Ayers Rock, and the old Hockenheim in Vancouver). 

These four-race blocks each represent their own mini-championship, in which you race against 19 cars, needing to finish in the top 10 to continue, and with the top 6 scoring points 10-6-4-3-2-1, and the respective amount of money in thousands. This can be spent on various upgrades, ranging from engine to tires (wet and dry) and from shocks (front, side and rear) to gearboxes. The ideal approach is to buy the more expensive versions ASAP, as you get no saving when upgrading. If you win the four-race championship, you get the next password. 

You get a set amount of nitro boost to use during each race, although bonus nitros, money and instant speed-up token appear on many tracks. Hazards such as puddles, barriers and ramps are also frequent.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Gremlin Interactive Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Kemco</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./U.N. Squadron (USA).zip</path>
    <name>U.N. Squadron</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/U.N. Squadron (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Soar to glory in a high-tech aircraft! The Evil Project 4 has torn freedom from the people of Aslan. Mercenaries control the entire country, except for a tiny airfield. But this field is headquarters for the best fighter pilots in the world -- UN Squadron!
You must destroy all eight of Project 4's bases as you force back an overpowering enemy war machine. Dog-fight a wolfpack of stealth fighters in a battlefield of clouds! Strafe enemy tanks!
A giant missile launcher, laser cannon and desert aircraft carrier hammer at your plane. Counterstrike with missiles, thunder lasers, napalm and bombs. Lead an airstrike for freedom!</desc>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 combines the best of all the Mortal Kombats into a single cartridge. 23 playable characters are immediately available, such as Reptile, Cyrax, Scorpion, Sub-Zero, Jax, Katana, Sonya, and more. There are two bosses that are unlockable, as well as additional characters.

There is a variety of new levels, some of which are interactive. Characters can uppercut someone, causing them to hit the ground hard and crash through to the bottom floor, or they can knocked someone off a bridge, landing in a pit of spikes.

Players can go against the computer one-on-one, two-on-two, or take part in the 8-fighter tournament.

The DS version has a wireless one-one-one multiplayer mode and includes the Puzzle Kombat mini-game from Mortal Kombat: Deception.</desc>
    <releasedate>19961001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Avalanche Software LLC</developer>
    <publisher>Williams Electronic Games, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Fight, Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Uniracers (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Uniracers</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Uniracers (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>What do you get if you cross Sonic the Hedgehog with Tony Hawk's Pro Skater?

It might seem an odd combination, but it describes Uniracers perfectly. One of the more successful releases of the Super Nintendo's twilight era, Uniracers mixes platform-based high-speed racing, with crazy stunts and tricks.

The basic idea in most levels of the game is simple. Get your unicycle from A to B as quickly as possible, and finish ahead of your opponent. It's like Sonic, but with none of those pesky enemies, pointless power-ups and frustrating obstructions. In fact it doesn't sound like much of a game at all...

Here's the key, though. Tricks performed and landed during the race increase your speed. The better the trick, the greater your increase in speed will be.

Also, some levels are set in areas designed solely for stunts. Such levels require you to earn as many style points as possible, by doing tricks. These levels are against the clock, and a set points score, rather than an opponent.

Unicycles are stupid and difficult, and yet fun, once you get the hang of them. Much the same could be said about Uniracers...</desc>
    <releasedate>19941202T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>DMA Design Limited</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Wario's Woods (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Wario's Woods</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Wario's Woods (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>It's up to Toad to keep the woods safe in this new Super NES puzzle action!

Toad is back in his very own big adventure in this game with the challenge of Tetris. It's up to you and Toad to keep peace in the Mushroom Kingdom - and that means outfoxing the wicked Wario!

Monsters, goblins and bombs fall from the sky faster and faster as Wario fires them into the woods. Toad must scramble to catch and line up the falling puzzle pieces to eliminate Wario's evil hold. If you loved Tetris, this puzzle action game is for you!</desc>
    <releasedate>19941210T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./X-Men - Mutant Apocalypse (USA).zip</path>
    <name>X-Men : Mutant Apocalypse</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/X-Men - Mutant Apocalypse (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Because of a rise of anti-mutant activity in Genosha, Professor Xavier uses Cerebro to scan the island nation and discovers Apocalypse's presence there. Genosha's government is apparently using Apocalypse to bring their mutant population under control. However, Xavier suspects Apocalypse to follow his own plans and sends five X-Men, Cyclops, Wolverine, Psylocke, Beast and Gambit, to investigate.

X-Men: Mutant Apocalypse combines the gameplay of a side-scrolling brawler like Final Fight with elements of a platformer, that is, players have to fight various enemies and survive the occasional jumping-puzzle. Most levels also feature mid- and end-bosses in form of robots, monsters or known Super-Villains.

Each character has unique abilities and special moves: Cyclops uses his Optic Blast to attack enemies from a distance, Wolverine can climb walls, Psylocke is very agile and the best jumper of the team, Beast can cling to the ceiling while Gambit throws explosive cards at his enemies. Special moves are quite similar to those found in Street Fighter II (Wolverine has a Dragon-Punch-style attack and Gambit's Double Kick is virtually identical to M. Bison's Scissors Kick), and require similar button combinations.

While most stages are unique for each character, some can be played with any of the X-Men. Progress is saved via password.</desc>
    <releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Avalon Hill</publisher>
    <genre>Platform, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Yoshi's Cookie (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Yoshi's Cookie</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Yoshi's Cookie (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Yoshi's Cookie is a fast-paced puzzle game that can be enjoyed by everyone as it is easy to play, but challenging to complete. To play, you move the randomly placed cookies into rows and columns of cookies with similar patterns. When you successfully assemble a row or column of the same cookies, the line will disappear, and you can begin on a new row or column. The "Yoshi" cookie is very special in both the 1-player and the 2-player game. Since the Yoshi Cookie is the key to both games, you must use it wisely.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Zombies Ate My Neighbors (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Zombies Ate My Neighbors</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Zombies Ate My Neighbors (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>In the game you are a male or female protagonist (Zeke or Julia), fighting the vampires, mummies, zombies, etc. on over 50 levels (not including secrets) and saving all of the people you find. There are defined number of neighbors you save on every level. When they are free then "Exit" door opens and you jump on next level.The levels differ from mall and grocery store to beaches and football fields. Using different weapons such as bazooka or water gun you have to kill the bosses such as huge babies, dragons or ants at the end of levels. You can play the game with two players cooperatively.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
</gameList>