<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>./Hudson's Adventure Island (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Adventure Island</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Hudson's Adventure Island (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>In the South Pacific, Master Higgins lives peacefully wearing only a grass skirt and a cap. That is until the Evil Witch Doctor decides to capture the Princess Leilani and hold her as his own. It's up to Master Higgins to gather throwing axes, fireballs and skateboards in order to aid his noble quest.

The game is a side scroller, Master Higgins moves across the screen from left to right and finds his power-ups in giant eggs. This includes a skateboard which results in a great speed enhancement - until Master Higgins gets hit and loses his power. If he is not on a skateboard a hit means instant death. Another game mechanic is starvation which gets indicated through a meter which steadily decreases. If it hits zero the hero dies and the only way to fill it up is by collecting food on the way. Bosses await him at the end of levels, all the way to the Evil Witch Doctor himself.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880902T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hudson</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Adventure Island 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Adventure Island 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Adventure Island 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Jeannie Jungle Kidnapped by Space Aliens!
What&#8217;s a hero to do? A mysterious flying saucer just made off with Master Higgins&#8217; girlfriend and it&#8217;s up to him to save her! But first he must defeat scores of mutated monsters across eight uncharted islands! Fly a dive-bombing pterodactyl or ride under the waves on a sea serpent in search of the missing Jeannie Jungle!

Battle your way through all new dangers and challenges on the biggest Adventure Island yet! Find secret treasure chambers, surf through killer waves and grab all the bonus items you can handle as you master each realm! Action, adventure and more await you in this thrilling addition to the Adventure Island saga!

-A new dinosaur friend joins Master Higgins&#8217; team of wild reptiles!
-Collect Power Crystals to gain temporary in vulnerability!
-Hours of entertainment for the whole family to enjoy!</desc>
    <releasedate>19920902T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Horizontal, Jumper, Platform, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Adventure Island II (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Adventure Island II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Adventure Island II (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Soar into action with Adventure Island II. That Evil Witch Doctor's just snatched your favorite lady. And you've got to battle your way past EIGHT treacherous islands to get her back.
Combat prehistoric monsters -- some of the creepiest, fire-spitting critters ever to slither across a video screen! Survive molten volcanoes. Dodge giant scorpions and king cobras. And the action gets even crazier with a new vertical/horizontal scroll, while stage select lets you control play.
So sharpen your axe, slip on a leopard skin, and take off for ADVENTURE ISLAND II. It's gonna be a wild ride!!!</desc>
    <releasedate>19910202T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Horizontal, Jumper, Platform, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
  <game>
    <path>./Adventures of Lolo (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Adventures of Lolo</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Adventures of Lolo (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Prince Lolo of Gentryland visited Eden, a country of love and peace, and enjoyed many pleasant days with Princess Lala of Eden. But one day, Egger, the King of Darkness, who had an evil plot to conquer Eden, spirited the Princess away before Lolo's eyes.
After a long and difficult journey, Lolo has come to the evil Castle of the Labyrinth. The castle is guarded by an army of evil monsters led by Egger, the King of Darkness.

Can Lolo solve the seemingly endless series of mazes and save Lala? Lolo is not gifted with strength or agility, but has great courage and patience. Now the battle of wits begins. Good luck, Lolo!</desc>
    <releasedate>19890401T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>HAL America Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Avoid, Collect, Puzzle, Singlescreen, Topdown</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Adventures of Lolo 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Adventures of Lolo 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Adventures of Lolo 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Our hero Lolo has charmed and enchanted puzzle-loving game players around the world with his unfailing courage and plucky persistence - and now he's off for his second quest!

Join forces with Lolo and his faithful sidekick Lala for another journey full of puzzles and pitfalls. The whole crew is back - Snakey, Leeper, Medusa, Gol, Don Medusa, Rocky, and of course our favorite, Alma.
Improved graphics, increased difficulty, and a few new tricks and techniques will keep you guessing through every fun-filled moment. A game for mental giants of all ages!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900301T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>HAL America Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Avoid, Collect, Puzzle, Singlescreen, Topdown</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Adventures of Lolo 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Adventures of Lolo 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Adventures of Lolo 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>The journey continues! The game preferred by the best and the brightest is back with a brand new installment. See if you qualify!

Seventeen levels, one hundred rooms. Play as either Lolo or Lala. Underwater levels with new challenges. Lolo's Grandpa teaches you the tricks of the game. New tactics, techniques and characters.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910902T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>HAL Laboratory, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Avoid, Collect, Puzzle, Singlescreen, Topdown</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Airwolf (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Airwolf</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Airwolf (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.2</rating>
    <desc>Deep within enemy territory, your fellow countrymen are imprisoned. Only one man in the free world would dare attempt to save them. You, Stringfellow Hawke, commander of Airwolf. And yet, as you strap yourself into the cockpit of your supersonic jet copter, you know this is the most dangerous assignment you have ever flown.

Your mission is mapped out. Airwolf's heat-seeking missiles and superpowered machine guns are fired up, ready to blow the terrorists away. But can you evade enemy radar time after time? Can you sneak behind the enemy lines, find the captives and bring them to safety before you crash land or worse?

Headquarters knows that you have the skill and firepower it takes. You say you've got the guts... now prove it!</desc>
    <releasedate>19890601T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Acclaim</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Horizontal, Shootemup, Shooter, Sideways, Tv</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Alien Syndrome (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Alien Syndrome</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Alien Syndrome (USA) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>The extra-terrestrials in this game are anything but friendly. They're slimy monsters that are holding space colonists captive aboard seven alien starships.

For one or two players, this super action game challenges you to free the helpless hostages. Search each ship's deadly levels, using flamethrowers and laser cannons to vaporize alien scum. Look for maps to help you find your way.

After you've saved all the captives from one ship, you must destroy its powerful leader before you can move on to the next ship. Remember, to the aliens, you're slime. And they want you good... and dead!</desc>
    <releasedate>19890101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sanritsu</developer>
    <publisher>Tengen</publisher>
    <genre>Alien, Arcade, Cooperative, Multidirectional, Scifi, Scrolling, Shooter, Topdown</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Back to the Future (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Back to the Future</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Back to the Future (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.35</rating>
    <desc>You are Marty McFly, just a typical senior at Hill Valley High. But after getting behind the wheel of a nuclear-powered sports car turned time machine, you find yourself in the year 1955 where you've accidentally tampered with history. Now it must be corrected. You must somehow make sure that teenagers Lorraine Baines and George McFly (the two kids that will eventually grow up to become your parents) fall in love before the photo of your family fades away and you're left with nothing to come home to. It won't be easy. You'll have to protect George from Biff and his gang of bullies while doing your best to keep them from beating you up instead. To complicate things, Lorraine has a crush on you, so you'll have to dodge her advances while trying to figure out a way to get George and her to kiss at the school dance. Time is wasting and even if you manage to put all of the pieces in place, there is still no guarantee that you'll get back. It will all come down to one brief moment in time when the past, present and future all meet.</desc>
    <releasedate>19890901T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Software Images</developer>
    <publisher>LJN</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Angle, Collect, Movie, Multidirectional, Wanderer</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Back to the Future Part II &amp; III (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Back to the Future Part II &amp; III</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Back to the Future Part II &amp; III (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <desc>Get ready for a wild romp through time, Marty McFly, 'cause you're about to take off on a double mission to save the past, present and future! Better load up on pizza and soda as you rocket to the year 2015 in Doc's supercharged time machine. Hang on to your hi-speed hoverboard as you teach Biff Tannen a thing or two about stealing your Sports Almanac, and locate the special objects he's hidden throughout time. Then, if your flux capacitor isn't on the fritz, it's off to the Wild West, where sharp shootin' gunslingers want you out of town by sundown. The fate of the world -- not to mention generations of McFly's -- is in your hands... and you're out of time!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900930T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Beam Software</developer>
    <publisher>LJN</publisher>
    <genre>Movie, Multiangle, Multitype</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Bad Dudes (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Bad Dudes</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Bad Dudes (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>The game starts in New York City, where President Ronnie (based on former U.S. President Ronald Reagan) has been kidnapped by the nefarious DragonNinja. The intro says: "Rampant ninja related crimes these days... Whitehouse is not the exception...". As soon as that occurs, a Secret Service agent (who resembles Arnold Schwarzenegger as he appears in The Terminator) asks two street-smart brawlers, named Blade and Striker: "President Ronnie has been kidnapped by the ninjas. Are you a bad enough dude to rescue Ronnie?", which this quote became an infamous meme and is often lampooned on the Internet. In the Japanese version, however, the words are completely different. After they heard that, the Bad Dudes confirmed it by pursuing the DragonNinja through the city streets, highway, sewers, transport train, forest, cave and into the secret ninja base, in order to save President Ronnie.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900701T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Batman - The Video Game (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Batman</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Batman - The Video Game (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>He's totally new. Totally tough. And he'll stop at nothing to make sure justice prevails! From the dark streets of GOTHAM CITY to the deepest corners of the criminal underworld comes the CAPED CRUSADER as you've never seen him before. Incredibly strong. Armed to the teeth. And ready to put his life on the line for the sake of all, on a search-and-destroy mission to end the Joker's reign of terror. He leaps, he flies, he dodges enemy fire and delivers it right back... with a vengeance. This is no kid stuff. This is as real as video gaming gets. If you liked what you saw in the movie, you're gonna love what you see here. Because this time around, BATMAN is all business, and he won't let anything stand in his way!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>SUNSOFT</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
  <game>
    <path>./Batman Returns (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Batman Returns</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Batman Returns (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Frigid winter winds swept over an already chilled Gotham City. Random street crimes were running at an all-time high, despite the holidays. Down below, in the city's frozen sewers, Oswald Cobblepot, known as The Penguin, planned more mayhem and schemed the take over of the fightened metropolis. His loyal army of missle-packing Penguin Commandos and the bizarre Red Triangle Circus Gang are energized by the evil genius of the web-footed orphan. A desperate call to Batman goes up. Partner with Batman to salvage Gotham City from The Penguin's cold-hearted plot. Guide him in swift, life-like moves from dark alleys to rooftops in vivid scenes based on the hit movie, "Batman Returns." Control his combat style, and help conduct relentless interrogations of The Penguins many allies. Use the Batcave computer to input clues, analyze evidence, and review enemy bios. You're in charge of weapons, too. Stock Batman's Utility belt with enough heat to match the diverse fighting styles of The Penguin and cold-blooded, sewer-dwelling minions. Gotham City is in trouble.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930102T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Comic, Horizontal, Movie, Platform, Scrolling, Sideways, Superhero</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Batman - Return of the Joker (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Batman: Return of the Joker</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Batman - Return of the Joker (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The seedy underworld is crawling with criminals. Even worse - the JOKER is back on top of 'em all! Law and order means nothing... until now! Because BATMAN is here - and the action is hotter than ever! Ear-crunching sound effects. Pulse-quickening music. Graphics that are as hot as 16-bit. And this time, BATMAN hits fast and hard. Flying, leaping, and sliding to attack! And striking at the heart of the JOKER. The CAPED CRUSADER has a totally new arsenal at his command: Batarang, Crossbow, Sonic Neutralizer. He's even got a superfueled jetpack. And even more powerful weapons at the touch of a button. BATMAN has got to use all of his power. Because this world is a very dark place, and you never know where the JOKER is hiding!</desc>
    <releasedate>19911202T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>SUNSOFT</publisher>
    <genre>Comic, Horizontal, Jumper, Platform, Shooter, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Battletoads (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Battletoads</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Battletoads (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>After her defeat by the Galactic Corporation at the battle of Canis Major, the evil Dark Queen and her renegade space troops retreat to the outer reaches of the universe, hiding out in dark spaces between the stars. Meanwhile, on board the spaceship Vulture, Professor T. Bird and the trio of Battletoads - Rash, Zitz and Pimple - are escorting the Princess Angelica back to her home planet, where her father, the Terran Emperor, awaits her safe arrival. Along the way, Pimple, the biggest Battletoad, takes Angelica out for a cruise in the Toadster to a nearby Leisure Station, but the Dark Queen ambushes them before they can get there, and they are kidnapped and carried away to Ragnarok's World, the Dark Queen's planet. Professor Bird sends remaining Battletoads down on Ragnarok to save Pimple and Angelica, but it will be a hard battle against planet's dangerous environments, traps and Dark Queen's troops. They have to go a long way from the planet's rough surface to deep caves and landed Gargantua and ultimately to the Tower of Shadows, where the Dark Queen awaits.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910602T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Tradewest, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Beatemup, Fighter, Horizontal, Progressive, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Battletoads-Double Dragon (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Battletoads &amp; Double Dragon</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Battletoads-Double Dragon (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Earth is under fire by Colossus, a battleship the size of a city. Using powerful laser cannons, it has destroyed most of Earth's defence forces, while its many troops clean up the rest of the planet. All expect for 5 warriors.

The Battletoads, who are well aware of evil forces in the galaxy, join forces with Billy and Jimmy Lee from Double Dragon to defend Earth from the deadly ship and its troops. Using a range of special moves you must fight your way through the streets into the heart of the ship and destroy it.
</desc>
    <releasedate>19930701T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rareware</developer>
    <publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Animalprotagonist, Beatemup, Cooperative, Fantasy, Horizontal, Scifi, Scrolling, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Best of the Best - Championship Karate (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Best of the Best - Championship Karate</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Best of the Best - Championship Karate (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Best of the Best: Championship Karate is a Kick Boxing game that features black belt kick Boxing masters. The object is to win the kick Boxing championship by defeating an array of Kick Boxing masters in a series of fighting matches.
Originally titled "Panza Kick Boxing" on home microcomputers in Europe, the game was retitled to "Best of the Best: Championship Karate" when it transitioned to home video game consoles.</desc>
    <releasedate>19921201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Movie Software</developer>
    <publisher>Electro-Brain</publisher>
    <genre>Fighting, Kickboxing, Martialarts, Sideways, Singlescreen, Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Blades of Steel (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Blades of Steel</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Blades of Steel (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>At the beginning of the game, players can select either "Exhibition" or "Tournament" matches. An exhibition match is just one game played against either the computer or another player. Tournament matches are similar to the NHL playoffs. It starts out as one team of the player's choice going against other teams in a playoff style tournament. The team that is successful in beating all of the opposing teams is awarded the Konami Cup.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881202T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Horizontal, Icehockey, Sideways, Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Blaster Master (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Blaster Master</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Blaster Master (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>You've fallen down a hidden manhole into a world of creatures so terrifying they'd scare the rats away. You can panic and perish, or blast your way through an endless maze of tunnels, searching for the secret passages to your escape. And that's the easy part. Because the Masters of the Caverns lay waiting - prehistoric creatures so powerful, so gigantic, they literally fill your screen! So load your arsenal and get ready for Blaster Master.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>SUNSOFT</publisher>
    <genre>Horizontal, Jumper, Platform, Shooter, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Bomberman (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Bomberman</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Bomberman (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Bomberman is an action game that has become synonymous with the Hudson brand. This is the very first version of Bomberman, which was released in 1985, and it went on to sell over one million copies. Bomberman boasts a simple and addictive game system where the players set bombs to knock out enemies.</desc>
    <releasedate>19890102T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Bomberman, Cute, Horizontal, Scrolling, Topdown</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Bomberman II (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Bomberman II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Bomberman II (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>A Bomberman named White Bomberman is framed for terrible crimes by Black Bomberman. After being accused of robbing a bank, White Bomberman is thrown in jail. Bomberman's mission is to escape his prison cell and bring Black Bomberman to justice.

The game follows the classic Bomberman formula: you are in a room full of blocks and enemies and Bomberman must plant bombs to destroy the blocks and enemies. Several blocks contain power-ups (such as blast radius increasers or fuse shorteners), and one in each level contains a door, which takes Bomberman to the next level.
Passwords are given after game over, recording the level, number of bombs, and strength of bombs. These passwords can be entered when the game starts allowing the player to continue where he left off.
New to the series are the multi-player modes. Vs Mode is a 2-player mode, while Battle Mode is a 3-player mode. The objective is to kill the opposing Bomberman by planting bombs. An NES Four Score is required to play the 3-player mode.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Bomberman, Competitive, Cute, Horizontal, Levelcodes, Scrolling, Topdown</genre>
    <players>3</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Bubble Bobble (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Bubble Bobble</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Bubble Bobble (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>THESE ARE TWO HUNGRY DINO-MIGHTS AND THEY'VE GOT BUBBLE FIGHT'N FUN DOWN TIGHT. You and your two brontosaurus buddies, Bub and Bob, are up to your brows in bubble troubles. You've got to battle battalions of bullies by blowing and bursting billions of bubbles. It's a fast-paced bubble banquet through over 100 screens of slap happy suds. Got an appetite for fun... then get blowin'.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
    <publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Cartoonish, Cooperative, Cute, Jumponthings, Platform, Powerup, Single</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Bubble Bobble Part 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Bubble Bobble Part 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Bubble Bobble Part 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>A new breed of heroes! Cubby and Rubby, descendants of the famous Bubby, must battle the Skull Brothers and their army of fiends to rescue a friend in danger. Fortunately, our dinosaur heroes can blow bubbles that will destroy their foes. They will rain fire, floods and tornado!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930801T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>ITL</developer>
    <publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Cartoonish, Cooperative, Cute, Jumponthings, Platform, Powerup, Single</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Castlevania (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Castlevania</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Castlevania (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>If you think it's scary on the outside, wait'll you see the basement! You're in for the longest night of your life. Ghosts, goblins, demons, wolves, bats - creatures lurking around every corner. As you descend deeper and deeper, they get thicker and thicker. Better stick close to the cavern floor - it's your only chance of finding a weapon or two. You're gonna need 'em. Because when you finally meet the Count, you know he'll be going for the jugular. So keep your courage up and your stake sharp. And say your prayers!</desc>
    <releasedate>19870501T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Castlevania II - Simon's Quest</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Castlevania was a cakewalk compared to this bloody curse. You thought you had the Prince of Darkness defanged - eh, Simon Belmont? Well think again, 'cause according to a damsel in distress, evil Count Dracula has left a horrifying curse in his wake. And the only hope you have of ending the terror is to destroy his missing body parts! Talk about your frightening quest, searching a maze of mansions, graveyards and dark, eerie forests - each guarded by man-eating werewolves, fire-throwing zombies and other devilish demons. Your grim chances are kept alive in Transylvania, where cowardly villagers offer clues to the whereabouts of Dracula's remains. And where you'll purchase magic weapons, including silver knives and flame whips. But beware the night. For when the sun disappears, Dracula's curse grows deadlier. And your chances grow dimmer and dimmer.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Fighter, Horizontal, Horror, Platform, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <desc>Led by the immortal Count Dracula, the greatest army of evil ever assembled is poised to bury mankind in a Tomb of Terror. Destroying this legion of Swamp Dragons, Slasher Skeletons and Forces of the Undead will be the supreme challenge for the mightiest of warriors. Your place in history is 100 years before Simon Belmont's birth. Dracula is young at heart, and it will take more than a stake to penetrate his evil. Luckily, you command the role of Trevor - Simon's forefather and the origin of the Belmont Warlord Chromosomes. Trevor has a power never before seen by human eyes - the power to transform into three different spirits: Grant DaNasty, the ferocious Ghost Pirate. Sypha, the Mystic Warlord. And Alucard, Dracula's forgotten son. You must perfectly time Trevor's body transformations to match up his different fighting spirits against Ultimate Evils. Trevor also has the strength and wisdom to command the Battle Axe, Invisibility Potion and Mystic Whip. But the most important weapon Trevor has is your cunning to choose the correct Paths of Fate and your bravery to lead him past 17 possible levels of never-ending doom, including the Haunted Ship of Fools, the Sunken City of Poltergeists, the Clock Tower of Untimely Death and Curse Castle. Never before have so many dangers confronted you at one time. And if by some miracle you triumph, you'll no longer be a mere mortal. You'll be a legend who'll live forever!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900901T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Fighter, Horizontal, Horror, Platform, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  <favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
  <game>
    <path>./Commando (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Commando</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Commando (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>The player takes control of a soldier named Super Joe, who starts by being dropped off in a jungle by a helicopter, and has to fight his way out singlehandedly, fending off a massive assault of enemy soldiers.

In the NES version, there is a more powerful machine gun upgrade, as well as "glasses" to let the player view all the hidden bunkers and an unlimited grenade upgrade (the player will lose these upgrades after losing a life).</desc>
    <releasedate>19860101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Overhead, Powerup, Scrolling, Shooter, Vertical, War</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Contra (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Contra</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Contra (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The universe teeters on the brink of total annihilation at the hands of the vile alien warmonger, Red Falcon. Earth's only hope rests with you, a courageous member of the Special Forces elite commando squad. Your mission: Battle deep into the deadly Amazon jungle, where the Red Falcon and his galactic henchmen have transformed ancient Mayan temples into awesome monuments dedicated to mass destruction. A multitude of weapons, from rapid-fire machine guns to high-tech lasers are at your disposal as you sweat blood, fighting past 3-D mazes, underground security systems, and tropical forests surrounded by giant waterfalls and alien cannons. This is the ultimate test for the ultimate guerilla warrior. And if you survive, Earth survives!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880202T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Horizontal, Platform, Shooter, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Cool World (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Cool World</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Cool World (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.25</rating>
    <desc>Cartoonist Jack Deebs (the player's character) has discovered Cool World; eliminating the fine line between fantasy and reality. Holli Would has a major crush on Jack and is using him romantically to get a human body and move to the "Real World." Jack's only goal is to escape this alternative reality and return to the real world. By doing so, he returns to his beloved hometown of Las Vegas. If Holly grabs the Golden Spike of Power, then both worlds will be destroyed.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930601T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ocean Software Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Ocean Software Ltd.</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Horizontal, Movie, Platform, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Crystalis (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Crystalis</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Crystalis (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>You must save the world from evil magic by finding the four powerful swords that form Crystalis.

After the apocalypse, magic returns to Earth.

A blessed group of good-intentioned sorcerers have used their new magical powers to rebuild the Earth, but an evil sorcerer named Dragonia has combined his supernatural forces with man-made technology to devastate the rebuilt Earth. It is your mission to recover four mystical swords, and combine them to form the ultimate blade: the Sword of Crystalis. This legendary weapon is the only tool which can put an end to Dragonia's black reign.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900701T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SNK</developer>
    <publisher>SNK</publisher>
    <genre>Rpg, Scifi, Topdown, Wanderer</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Donkey Kong (World) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Donkey Kong</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Donkey Kong (World) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Can you save Mario's girl from the clutches of Donkey Kong? Donkey Kong has kidnapped Mario's girlfriend Pauline and taken her to the top of a construction site. It's up to you to help Mario save Pauline before time runs out. But it won't be easy. Donkey Kong will do everything in his power to stop you. He'll throw barrel bombs, flaming fireballs and anything else he can get his hands on. So if you're looking for action, don't monkey around. Get the original Donkey Kong from the Nintendo Arcade Classics Series!</desc>
    <releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Donkey Kong 3 (World).zip</path>
    <name>Donkey Kong 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Donkey Kong 3 (World).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Donkey Kong is at it again! This time he's loose in the greenhouse. And he's got company: a swarm of very pesky bees! It's up to you to get Donkey Kong out of the greenhouse and exterminate the bees... without hurting the flowers. But that's easier said than done! Because Donkey Kong has plenty of coconuts to hurl at you, and those bees know just where to sting you so it hurts. But, if you keep your wits about you, you'll score lots of points and have lots of laughs in the best Donkey Kong of them all... DONKEY KONG 3!</desc>
    <releasedate>19840704T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Donkey Kong Classics (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Donkey Kong Classics</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Donkey Kong Classics (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>What's more fun than a barrel of monkeys? A Donkey Kong double feature! In DONKEY KONG you'll duck barrel bombs and flaming fireballs as you help Mario save his girlfriend Pauline from the clutches of Donkey Kong. In DONKEY KONG JR., you'll join forces with these madcap monkeys to help Donkey Kong Jr. rescue his father from Mario's prison. Are you ready for laughter? You'd better be. Because this double dose of monkey business will have you rolling in the aisles!</desc>
    <releasedate>19881001T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Avoid, Platform, Singlescreen</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Donkey Kong Jr. (World) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Donkey Kong Jr.</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Donkey Kong Jr. (World) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Mario has gone mad! He's turned the tables on Donkey Kong and locked him in a cage. It's up to you, as Donkey Kong Jr., to rescue your father by stealing Mario's set of keys. But it won't be easy. You'll have to fight off ape-eating Snapjaws, jump onto moving islands and break through a jungle of vines to get to the keys that will free Donkey Kong. Can you handle the action? Because this off-the-wall monkey business will have you going bananas!</desc>
    <releasedate>19870715T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Double Dragon (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Double Dragon</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Double Dragon (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Double Dragon is the story of Billy and Jimmy Lee, twin brothers who learned to fight on the cold, tough streets of the city. Their expert knowledge of the martial arts combined with their street smarts, has made them both formidable fighting machines. But now Billy is faced with his greatest challenge. Marian has been kidnapped by the Black Warriors, the savage street gang of the mysterious Shadow Boss! Using whatever weapons come to hand - knives, whips, bats, rocks, oil drums, even dynamite - Billy must pursue the gang through the slums, factories, and wooded outskirts of the city to reach the hideout for his final confrontation with the Shadow Boss... his brother Jimmy!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880602T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
    <publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Beatemup, Cooperative, Horizontal, Scrolling, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Double Dragon II - The Revenge (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Double Dragon II: The Revenge</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Double Dragon II - The Revenge (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>The Double Dragons - Billy and Jimmy Lee - are back to avenge the loss of Marion! In their quest to defeat the evil Shadow Warriors, the martial arts duo are challenged in 9 incredible missions, facing ruthless street gangs, nunchaku-toting ninja and giant mutant warriors! The non-stop action winds its way through construction sites, alleyways and underwater hideouts complete with secret elevator shafts, spiked ceilings and razor-sharp mechanical claws! And in a bonus mission, never before seen, the duo's worst fear becomes reality as they fight the ultimate battle between good and evil. A battle where not only their lives are at stake, but the fate of the entire world!</desc>
    <releasedate>19881201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
    <publisher>Technos Japan Corp.</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Double Dragon III: The Sacred Stones</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Only one man knows the real story behind Marion's disappearance... and he's dead! Now the Double Dragons must rely on a mysterious fortune teller to locate Marion and her ransom - the Sacred Stones of Power! You'll fend off vicious street thugs, evil ninja warriors, deadly gladiators, Manchurian barbarians and more! Defeat your most dreaded enemies and out of pure respect they'll join your side - adding their Iron Claws and Shangai Stars to your all-new martial arts maneuvers - like the awesome mid-air somersault. Double Dragon III. If you survive the action, you'll rescue Marion, retain your honor and discover the truth behind the Sacred Stones. If you fail...</desc>
    <releasedate>19910202T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>East Technology Corp.</developer>
    <publisher>Technos Japan Corp.</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Beatemup, Cooperative, Horizontal, Magic, Scrolling, Shop</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Double Dribble (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Double Dribble</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Double Dribble (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Finally, it's here! The basketball game you've dreamed of. The first home game with 5 on 5, full court, board-banging action. A contest with graphics so real, they'll knock your high-tops off. Ready to captain your team to the title, you bolt into the arena with electricity in your fingers and ice in your veins. Intensity builds. The crowd roars. The game is yours to win or lose. But to win you'll need speed in the lane, touch for three-pointers, muscle to power past picks, and the skill to crash the glass. And, if you break free underneath - watch out! Because now you can power home a rim-rockin' slam! So pull up your shorts and take a deep breath. It's crunch time. Time to show your stuff!</desc>
    <releasedate>19870901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Dr. Mario (Japan, USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Dr. Mario</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Dr. Mario (Japan, USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>A puzzle game similar to Tetris, Dr. Mario features Nintendo mascot Mario as a doctor. Gameplay consists of dropping two-sided vitamin capsules into a playing field 8 blocks wide by 16 blocks high resembling a medicine bottle, populated by viruses of three colors</desc>
    <releasedate>19901014T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo R&amp;D1</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Dragon Warrior (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Dragon Warrior</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Dragon Warrior (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Dragon Warrior uses console role-playing game mechanics which were described by Kurt Kalata of Gamasutra as archaic in 2008. The player takes the role of a namable Hero. The Hero's name has an effect on his statistical growth over the course of the game. Battles are fought in a turn-based format and experience points and gold are awarded after every battle, allowing the Hero to level-up in ability and allows them to buy better weapons, armor, and items. Progression consists of traveling over an overworld map and through dungeons, fighting monsters encountered via random battles along the journey.

" As a whole, Dragon Warrior has been credited with establishing the basic template for the Japanese console RPGs that followed. " -Wikipedia</desc>
    <releasedate>19890801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Chunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Dragon Warrior II (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Dragon Warrior II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Dragon Warrior II (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>This game allows the player to control more than one character, and it is the first one in the Dragon Quest series to do so. The player controls his or her characters as they move in the game world. They can search treasure chests, talk and trade with villagers, equip weapons and armor, and cast spells.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900901T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Chunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Fantasy, Rpg, Topdown, Wanderer</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Dragon Warrior III (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Dragon Warrior III</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Dragon Warrior III (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>Dragon Warrior III is noted for greatly expanding upon the original Dragon Warrior and Dragon Warrior II. The game uses basic console role-playing game conventions, such as leveling up by gaining experience points and equipping items. Battle is turn-based like the other games in the series.
Dragon Warrior III features a class system, in which each character has a certain class. While the Hero always keeps the Hero class, the other characters can choose among the following: Soldier (Warrior in the GBC version), Fighter, Pilgrim (Cleric), Wizard (Mage), Merchant (Dealer), Goof-Off (Jester), Sage, and Thief which was available only in the later versions. The choice of class greatly affects the character's stats and spells he or she can learn. Furthermore, upon reaching experience Level 20, a character has the option of changing classes at the temple of Dhama, found halfway through the game. The game starts with just the Hero in the party, who then is able to recruit a party of three at the local tavern. Unlike most Dragon Quest parties, aside from the Hero, the party is not made up of characters involved in the story. Although only four characters can be in the party at a time, extra members of the party can be kept at the tavern, allowing room for new recruits. Another innovation is an arena where the player can place bets on the outcome of monster battles.
The remakes incorporated some interface changes from later games in the series, such as simplified door opening; the bag, which replaced bank item storage; the item sorting "Tidy Item" and "Tidy Bag" commands; and the "Full HP" command, which can be used outside of combat to automate the process of casting healing and status restoring spells.
While the earlier Dragon Quest games were also non-linear, Dragon Quest III was the most substantial example of open-world gameplay among the early Dragon Quest games. It also allowed the player to swap characters in and out of the party at will, and another "major innovation was the introduction of day/night cycles; certain items, characters, and quests are only accessible at certain times of day."</desc>
    <releasedate>19920301T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Chunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Fantasy, Rpg, Topdown, Wanderer</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Dragon Warrior IV (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Dragon Warrior IV</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Dragon Warrior IV (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Dragon Quest IV differs from the rest of the series by breaking up the game into five distinct chapters, each of which focuses on a different protagonist or protagonists. The first four are told from the perspective of the Hero's future companions and the fifth one, from the hero's perspective, brings all the characters together as they begin their journey to save the world.</desc>
    <releasedate>19921002T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Chunsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Fantasy, Rpg, Topdown, Wanderer</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./DuckTales (USA).zip</path>
    <name>DuckTales</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/DuckTales (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Bless me bagpipes! When will that thrillseeker, Scrooge McDuck, ever quit? Never one to turn away from adventure, Uncle Scrooge has taken on his greatest challenge - to discover the legendary Five Lost Treasures and become the "Richest Duck in the World!" Join Scrooge and the DUCKTALES gang: gung-ho flying ace, Launchpad; the nephews, Huey, Dewey and Louie; and little Webby, on their search. Together they must trek through the treacherous Amazon Jungle, down into the diamond mines of Africa, and even to the moon! Are you "Duck" enough to join them on their adventure? Come along to Duckburg Headquarters and see for yourself!</desc>
    <releasedate>19890914T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Disney, Horizontal, Platform, Sideways, Tv</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./DuckTales 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>DuckTales 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/DuckTales 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Scrooge McDuck is hot on the trail of the richest adventure ever. Pieces to the map of the Lost Treasure of McDuck have been scattered across the globe, and Scrooge must find them before the greedy Flintheart Glomgold grabs them. It's going to be a race to the finish as both of them try to find the treasure and become the richest duck in the world! Join Scrooge and his nephews as they explore the ancient pyramids of Egypt and do battle with swash-buckling pirates in the Bermuda Triangle. Help them search the haunted halls of an ancient Scottish castle and scale the watery heights of Niagara Falls. Aid Scrooge in his quest for the secret of the island of Mu and you'll gain the final clue to unravel the hidden location of the Lost Treasure of McDuck!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930602T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Disney, Horizontal, Platform, Sideways, Tv</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Excitebike (Japan, USA).zip</path>
    <name>Excitebike</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Excitebike (Japan, USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Whether the player chooses to race solo or against computer-assisted riders, he/she races against a certain time limit. The goal is to qualify for the Excitebike (the championship) race by coming in at third place or above in the challenge race (preliminary race). The times to beat are located on the stadium walls (for first place) and in the lower left corner (for third place). In any race, the best time is 8 seconds ahead of third place. When the player places first, then they get a message: "It's a new record!" Additional points are earned by beating the previously-set record time.</desc>
    <releasedate>19841130T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo Research &amp; Development 1</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Horizontal, Motocross, Motorcycle, Racing, Sideways, Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Faxanadu (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Faxanadu</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Faxanadu (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Unlock doors of legend on your journey through Faxanadu!

You are the elves&#8217; last hope. Outside the town walls lurk monsters with the power to destroy anything in their path. Inside the walls, water and time are running out. Soon the ancient elf town of Eolis will vanish into eternity. Only you can save Eolis. No one else dares to venture beyond the walls, onto the World Tree, where towns and fortresses precariously await the whims of fate at the hands of the Evil.

You are searching for the water source and for an antidote to the poison that makes the water undrinkable. To find them you&#8217;ll need gold and food and magic, speed with a sword &#8230; and luck.

Every town holds a new mystery, every fortress a new danger. Merchants will sell you magic and valuable tools, but it&#8217;s up to you to figure out what you need. Long, secret mantras help you slip through the mists, but will you survive the next challenge?

This is Faxanadu, the legend, the adventure &#8211; the incredible journey on the World Tree.</desc>
    <releasedate>19871117T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Falcom</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Final Fantasy (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Final Fantasy</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Final Fantasy (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>An evil shroud covers the world in darkness. You must restore the powers of earth, wind, fire and water to the Four Orbs. Create your own band of 4 Light Warriors from fighters, thieves, martial artists, and magicians. You'll need all their skills to triumph in this massive role-playing adventure. Your treacherous journey takes you to all parts of a strange new world. Explore dangerous castles and dark caverns where deadly perils and great rewards, await at every turn. Hundreds of ferocious monsters block your path. With patience, skill, and cunning, you can defeat them.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900712T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
    <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
    <genre>Rpg, Topdown, Wanderer</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Galaga - Demons of Death (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Galaga - Demons of Death</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Galaga - Demons of Death (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The objective of Galaga is to score as many points as possible by destroying insect-like enemies. The player controls a starfighter that can move left and right along the bottom of the playfield. Enemies swarm in groups in a formation near the top of the screen, and then begin flying down toward the player, firing bombs at the fighter. The game ends when the player's last fighter is lost, either by colliding with an enemy or one of its bullets, or by being captured.
Galaga introduces a number of new features over its predecessor, Galaxian. Among these is the ability to fire more than one bullet at a time, a count of the player's "hit/miss ratio" at the end of the game, and a bonus "Challenging Stage" that occurs every few levels, in which a series of enemies fly onto and out of the screen in set patterns without firing at the player's ship or trying to crash into it. These stages award a large point bonus if the player manages to destroy every enemy.
Another gameplay feature new to Galaga is the ability for enemies to capture the player's fighter. While the player is in control of just one fighter, a "boss Galaga" (which takes two shots to kill) periodically attempts to capture the fighter using a tractor beam. If successful, the fighter joins the enemy formation. If the player has more lives remaining, play resumes with a new fighter. The captured fighter flies down with the enemy that captured it, firing upon the player just like normal enemies, and can be shot and destroyed. The player can free the fighter by destroying the boss Galaga while in flight, causing the captured fighter to link up with the player's current fighter, doubling his or her firepower but also making a target twice as large.
Galaga has an exploitable bug that can cause the attackers to stop firing bullets at the player, due to a coding error. In addition, similar to the famous "Split-Screen bug" in Pac-Man, a bug exists in Galaga in which the game "rolls over" from Level 255 to Level 0. Depending on the difficulty setting of the machine, this can cause the game to stall, requiring that the machine be reset or power-cycled in order to start a new game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880901T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Gauntlet (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Gauntlet</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Gauntlet (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>In a land known as Rendar, Morak, a hooded devil-like creature, has stolen the Sacred Orb that protected the lands. He hid this along with other treasures he stole in the Gauntlet which is protected by his evil creatures. Of the four heroes from the original Gauntlet only two were able to enter the portal and go after the Sacred Orb.</desc>
    <releasedate>19890101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tengen</developer>
    <publisher>Tengen</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Fantasy, Maze, Multidirectional, Shooter, Topdown</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Gauntlet II (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Gauntlet II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Gauntlet II (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>The gameplay is very similar to the original Gauntlet, a topdown dungeon crawl supporting up to four players. The biggest difference from the original game is that players can choose identical classes, instead of being limited to a particular one for each joystick; the players being differentiated by colors. Thus, instead of having a "warrior", "wizard", and "valkyrie" (for instance), in Gauntlet II there could be a "red wizard", a "blue elf" and a "green warrior".</desc>
    <releasedate>19900901T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Atari</developer>
    <publisher>Mindscape, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Cooperative, Fantasy, Gauntlet, Magic, Multidirectional, Scrolling, Shooter, Topdown</genre>
    <players>4</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ghosts'n Goblins (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ghosts'n Goblins</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ghosts'n Goblins (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The beautiful princess is kidnapped. Her lover, the Knight in shining armor, armed with five different weapons to fight the enemy, sets out to rescue the beautiful princess. The Knight, aided by your skill, must pass through seven different guarded gates, fighting and destroying demons, dragons, giants and zombies. There are hidden characters, too! Some friends, some foes. Ghosts 'N Goblins is exciting... challenging you and the Knight to rescue the princess, amid great danger, escaping Hades, land of the enemies!</desc>
    <releasedate>19861102T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Gradius (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Gradius</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Gradius (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>One of the defining characteristics of the Gradius series is the use of a "power meter." The power meter is powered by a power-up item, whose purpose, when collected, is to move a highlight to the next power-up on the power meter. When a power-up that the player wants becomes highlighted, he or she may activate it, also causing the highlight to reset.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Horizontal, Powerup, Shootemup, Shooter, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Guardian Legend, The (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Guardian Legend, The</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Guardian Legend, The (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>In The Guardian Legend, the player controls the female guardian of Earth, a "highly sophisticated aerobot transformer". The player's mission is to infiltrate Naju, a large planet-like object which aliens sent hurtling towards the Earth. While inside, the player must activate ten safety devices in order to initialize Naju's self-destruct mechanism and destroy the alien world before it reaches Earth. Five hostile tribes of alien lifeforms are vie for control of territories within Naju,and the player needs to fight through them to successfully activate the switches and escape.</desc>
    <releasedate>19890101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Compile</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Actionadventure, Angle, Maze, Multidirectional</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ikari III - The Rescue (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ikari III</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ikari III - The Rescue (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The presidential candidate's daughter has been kidnapped! It is your job to get past enemy lines and rescue her. This is the third game in the Ikari Warriors series, and features similar arcade/action gameplay. The screen is a top down view which scrolls vertically, with numerous bad guys to defeat. You start the game with just your fists, and as the levels progress you can find weapons and other objects to help you out.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SNK</developer>
    <publisher>SNK</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ikari Warriors (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Ikari Warriors</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ikari Warriors (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>The player takes the role of commando-like warriors named Ralf and Clark, who must try to reach the village of Ikari. Enemy units attempting to kill the player include tanks, enemy soldiers and helicopters. A number of power-ups along the way help the player to achieve victory.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Micronics</developer>
    <publisher>Tradewest, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ikari Warriors II - Victory Road (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ikari Warriors II - Victory Road</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ikari Warriors II - Victory Road (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <desc>When we last saw Paul and Vince, they had saved the Colonel and were about to head for home in a special plane given to them by the General. But then, while in flight over the ocean, the sky suddenly blackens - the ocean begins to churn - and the plane goes spinning! A booming voice fills the cockpit: "Hear me, Warriors! Zang Zip, the War Dog, has enslaved the people of Earth. Only you can save us from his grip of evil!" Caught in a time warp, hurled thousands of years into the future, Paul and Vince know they have no choice but to meet this impossible challenge head-on. After all, they are professionals... they are the Ikari Warriors!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880402T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SNK</developer>
    <publisher>SNK</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Cooperative, Scrolling, Shooter, Vertical, War</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Jackal (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Jackal</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Jackal (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The Jackal squad, a four-man team composed of Colonel Decker, Lieutenant Bob, Sergeant Quint and Corporal Grey, is sent to rescue soldiers kept as hostages by the enemy. One or two players control the teams in an armed jeep, which must venture through several enemy strongholds to rescue comrades imprisoned by the enemy. In each of the six levels, the goal is to rescue POWs from various buildings and then transfer them to helicopter dust-off locations. Once the soldiers are secure, the player(s) must then proceed to defeat the boss at the end of each level. In the last level, there are two bosses that must be defeated.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880901T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Shooter, Topdown, Vertical</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Joust (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Joust</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Joust (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>Joust is a platforming game where the player controls a yellow knight riding a flying ostrich from a third-person perspective. The player navigates the protagonist around the game world, which consists of rock platforms floating above a flat island surrounded by lava.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881002T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Williams</developer>
    <publisher>HAL America Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Arenacombat, Duel, Sideways, Singlescreen</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Kid Icarus (USA, Europe).zip</path>
    <name>Kid Icarus</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Kid Icarus (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Far away in a kingdom called "Angel Land," the evil goddess Medusa has stolen the Three Sacred Treasures and imprisoned the goddess of light, Palutena. As Kid Icarus, your mission is to find the treasures, destroy Medusa and rescue Palutena from the depths of the Palace in the Sky. To find the treasures you'll travel through ruins collecting weapons and storing power for use in combat against creatures of Medusa's army. Use your bow and arrow to ward off gatekeepers of the Underworld, Overworld and Skyworld as you strive towards your battle against Medusa. Will you survive to restore Palutena's light and return it to "Angel Land?" Only you know!</desc>
    <releasedate>19870701T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Jumper, Platform, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Kirby's Adventure (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Kirby's Adventure</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Kirby's Adventure (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>What would Dream Land be without dreams? A nightmare! The Dream Spring, source of all dreams, has dried up, taking with it all the blissful dreams of Dream Land. It's up to Kirby, the bombastic blimp, To return happy naps to the inhabitants of Dream Land! Kirby's appetite for adventure is as big as ever as he eats his way through a feast of all-new enemies! In this adventure, he can also steal the abilities of the bad guys he scarfs down! With this new power, Kirby can perform 20 new tricks that will help him make his way through the nightmare infested Dream Land! Kirby's Adventure features brand new worlds to explore with the same fun action-packed feel that made Kirby's Dream Land for Gameboy a hit!</desc>
    <releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Kung Fu (Japan, USA).zip</path>
    <name>Kung Fu</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Kung Fu (Japan, USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>You'll need lightning fast reactions to knock out the Knife Thrower, stop the Stick Fighter, and trip up the evil Tom Tom Brothers in this action-packed martial arts contest! Are you sure you're tough enough? Because it'll take all your strength and skill to master the moves in KUNG FU, beat your opponents, and rescue the fair Sylvia who's held captive on the top floor! The action is non-stop, and just when you think you've got your enemies licked there's always a Giant, a Snake, or a fire-breathing Dragon to contend with in KUNG FU!</desc>
    <releasedate>19850621T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Fighter, Horizontal, Martialarts, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Legend of Zelda, The (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Legend of Zelda - Gold Cart, The</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Legend of Zelda, The (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Welcome to the Legend of Zelda. Where the only sound you&#8217;ll hear is your own heart pounding as you race through forests, lakes, mountains and dungeonous mazes in an attempt to restore peace to the land of Hyrule. Along the way you&#8217;ll be challenged by Tektites, Wizzrobes and an endless array of ruthless creatures who&#8217;ll stop at nothing to prevent you from finding the lost fragments of the Triforce of Wisdom. But don&#8217;t despair. With a little luck and a lot of courage, you&#8217;ll conquer your adversaries, unite the Triforce fragments and unravel the mystery of the Legend of Zelda! &#8226; Explore the vast Overworld terrain of the land of Hyrule and discover hidden treasures. &#8226; Explore the mystical labyrinths of the Underworld and ward-off ruthless enemies.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870701T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo R&amp;D4</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Legendary Wings (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Legendary Wings</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Legendary Wings (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>20,000 years in the future, mankind has built a giant supercomputer named DARK to rule the planet. For hundreds of years, DARK has governed with wisdom and justice. But now the unthinkable has happened: DARK is malfunctioning, and humanity is writhing in the grasp of a ruthless tyrant. DARK has built a fleet of robot warships to patrol the skies, and has created an army of mutant monsters to guard the underground bases from which he now terrorizes mankind. Lulled by hundreds of years of peace, the people of earth are defensless against the minions of DARK. But two brave young men, following an ancient legend of Greek mythology, have devised mechanical wings to bear them aloft in search of DARK's hidden fortress. Armed with the last remaining guns and missiles from a crumbling arsenal, you must fly them across the continents and oceans to seek out and destroy the cruel colossus! If you fail, mankind is lost. Take wing, Legendary Soldiers!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880702T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Powerup, Shootemup, Shooter, Topdown, Vertical</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Life Force (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Life Force</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Life Force (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>You've saved the innocent people of Gradius from the vile Bacterions. But now an even deadlier plague has slimed into the neighborhood. It's Zelos, an all-engulfing, planet-eating alien who's hungering to take a bite out of you! Only this time you don't have to rescue the millions of Gradians alone. You can call on a starfighter friend from the planet Latis, who'll fight beside you in his RoadBritish space destroyer. You'll both be gunning for max power-ups, with ripple lasers, plutonic missiles and impregnable force fields. But you better be on target. For this isn't your ordinary space scum. And to crush him you've gotta soar through his guts, blast past his death traps and ultimately blow out his heart. Good luck, Commander. The galaxy's counting on you!

This game is also known in the japanese Famicom and Arcades as "Salamander".</desc>
    <releasedate>19880801T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Horizontal, Powerup, Shootemup, Shooter, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Little Nemo - The Dream Master (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Little Nemo - The Dream Master</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Little Nemo - The Dream Master (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Little Nemo receives a royal invitation to visit the castle in Slumberland. Is he dreaming? It seems the princess is looking for a new playmate. When he arrives he is told that King Morpheus has been kidnapped. Nemo sets off on a wild adventure to rescue the good king and restore peace to the land. Anything can happen in this realm of imagination. Little Nemo even learns how to get a ride from the local creatures so he can pass through the roughest parts of Slumberland. Rescue the King of good dreams and thwart the Master of Nightmares!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900901T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Comic, Horizontal, Jumper, Platform, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Lode Runner (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Lode Runner</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Lode Runner (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <desc>The player controls a stick figure who must collect all the gold in a level while avoiding guards who try to catch the player. After collecting all the gold, the player must travel to the top of the screen to reach the next level. There are 150 levels in the game which progressively challenge players' problem-solving abilities or reaction times.</desc>
    <releasedate>19870902T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Douglas E. Smith</developer>
    <publisher>Broderbund Software, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Avoid, Collect, Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Maniac Mansion (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Maniac Mansion</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Maniac Mansion (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The game takes place in the mansion of the Edison family: Dr. Fred, Nurse Edna, and their son Weird Ed. Living with the Edisons are two large, disembodied tentacles &#8211; one purple and the other green. The player starts out by selecting two of six characters to accompany protagonist Dave Miller. The intro sequence shows that a meteor crashed near the mansion 20 years earlier. The sentient meteor took control of the family and caused Dr. Fred to begin conducting human experiments while plotting to take over the world. After the introduction, Dave and his two companions prepare to enter the mansion to rescue his cheerleader girlfriend, Sandy Pantz, whom Dr. Fred has kidnapped.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900901T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</developer>
    <publisher>Jaleco Ltd.</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Alien, Humour, Mouseonly, Multidirectional, Pointandclick, Scifi, Scrolling</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mario Bros. (World).zip</path>
    <name>Mario Bros.</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mario Bros. (World).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Mario and Luigi are doing some underground plumbing when all sorts of weird creatures come flying out of the pipes. Turtles, crabs - even fighterflies - attack the helpless Mario Bros. It's up to you to kick, punch, and knock out these sewer pests before time runs out! But beware. Just when you think you got rid of them, they come back for more! Play against the computer, or with a friend - either way, this is one underground classic you'll want to play time and time again!</desc>
    <releasedate>19860601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Man (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Man</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Man (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>It's MEGA MAN versus the powerful leaders and fighting forces of Monsteropolis - that strange multi-layered land of robot-like humanoids created by the wrongly-performed experiments with human beings by Dr. Wily. Mega Man - the chosen defender of the human race. For he dares to single-handedly penetrate Monsteropolis' seven separate societies to stop the rapid expansion of strange misrepresentations of humans.

Mega Man's goal is monumental. He must infiltrate seven separate heavily-guarded empires. By himself, he must break down and destroy the following empire leaders: Cutman, Gutsman, Iceman, Bombman, Fireman, Elecman, and Dr. Wily. The action involves Mega Man armed only with laser beam weapons, encountering strangely-configured humanoids. They're atop, in and out of fortified prison-like structures strengthened with thick walls. Hidden amid gun turrets embedded in concrete uprights, even in subterranean passages below icefields. WOW!</desc>
    <releasedate>19871201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Platform, Scifi, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Man 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Man 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Man 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>He's Back! And this time the evil Dr. Wily (once the supreme power in the universe) has created even more sinister robots to mount his attack. But as MegaMan, you've also grown in power and ability. Can you save mankind from the evil desires of Dr. Wily? Each of the eight empires is ruled by a different super-robot. You must defeat each enemy on his own turf, building up weapons as you go. Only after all are destroyed will you go head-on with the mastermind himself, the evil Dr. Wily.</desc>
    <releasedate>19890702T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Platform, Scifi, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Man 3 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Man 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Man 3 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>It's robot rebellion, and nobody's safe! Least of all, Mega Man! This time the superpowerful cyborg takes on a horde of metal maniacs who've had it with being obedient! And they use every android-annihilator ever invented to make you believe it! Mega Man goes berserk, blasting through a galaxy of mining stations in search of energy crystals. But it takes more than guts to battle the phenomenal robot masters who control these worlds. It's a wrenching job, the worst - and the best - that Mega Man's faced so far!</desc>
    <releasedate>19901102T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Platform, Scifi, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Man 4 (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Man 4</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Man 4 (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>For a year the city has been quiet, but a new robotic terror has gripped the city! That scheming scientist, Dr. Cossack has arrived in town with eight new metal maniacs who are bigger and badder than anything Dr. Wily dreamed of. It's going to be a cybernetic showdown as the streets of the city erupt with the sizzling sounds of molten metal! Armed with the new Mega Buster, Mega Man runs, jumps and dodges his way through mazes of metallic munchkins on his way to the Siberian citadel of Dr. Cossack for the final cataclysmic clash!</desc>
    <releasedate>19911206T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Man 5 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Man 5</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Man 5 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Protoman has gone berserk! Destroying half the city was not enough. Now, he has snatched Dr. Light and is holding him and the entire city hostage. Speeding to the rescue is Mega Man and his modified Mega Buster, but eight of Protoman's cybernetic soldiers plan to send Mega Man to the scrap heap for good! Feel the weight of the world on your shoulders as you battle Gravity Man! Chip away at the rock-like defenses of Stone Man and bring him crumbling down! Hit the surf and sail up against the tidal power of Wave Man! Help Mega Man defeat all eight of Protoman's robots and then get ready for the fight that pits brother against brother in the battle of the century!</desc>
    <releasedate>19921202T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Platform, Scifi, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mega Man 6 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Mega Man 6</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mega Man 6 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>From the United States, Canada and Japan they came. The world's premier designers and their finest robotic warriors traveled to do battle in the First Annual Robot Tournament. But what began as a game suddenly took a terrifying twist! On the eve of the Grand Championship, the sponsor of the event announced that the entire tournament was just an elaborate scheme to get his hands on the world's most powerful robots! Now faced with an army of metallic mercenaries, Mega Man must fight a ferocious new foe - The Mysterious Mr. X!</desc>
    <releasedate>19940302T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Platform, Scifi, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Metal Gear (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Metal Gear</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Metal Gear (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Outer Heaven leader CaTaffy has activated the ultimate super weapon: Metal Gear! Responding to the crisis, covert unit "Fox Hound" is called into action, and that's where you come into play. Trained in hand-to-hand combat and skilled in every weapon known to man, you're Fox Hound's lethal fighting machine, code named "Solid Snake". But on this mission you better be sly as well, to surprise heavily-armed enemies, busting 'em up quietly and rescuing their hostages before alarms are triggered. Plus you gotta maintain radio contact with Commander South, who'll feed you crucial info on Metal Gear's whereabouts. To survive, capture sub-machine guns, Barettas, grenade launchers, and plastic explosives, until you find and destroy Metal Gear, ending CaTaffy's reign of terror!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880602T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Ultra Games</publisher>
    <genre>Actionadventure, Angle, Flipscreen, Singlescreen</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Metroid (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Metroid</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Metroid (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>It's you against the evil Mother Brain in the thrilling battle of Metroid!

You&#8217;re inside the fortress planet Zebes.  The planet of endless secret passageways where the Metroid are multiplying.  Left alone the Metroid are harmless.  But in the wrong hands they could destroy the galaxy.  It&#8217;s up to you to prevent the Mother Brain that controls Zebes from using the Metroid for evil purposes.  But that won&#8217;t be easy.  You&#8217;ll have to use your spacesuit to absorb valuable energy for your search to gain the use of power items like the Ice Beam, Wave Beam, High Jump Boots and Varia.  If you survive, it will be you and your acquired powers against the Mother Brain.

Worth Noting:
Metroid introduced nonlinear, side-scroller, maze-like, gameplay, in a platform, shooter. Metroid required players to discover permanent power-ups to progress further along; while backtracking through previously visited areas. The style is affectionately known as Metroid-vania' (Castlevania: Symphony of the Night being the second half to the term, mirrored the concept).

Metroid also used a password system to resume progression of the game (Before the addition of battery backups and save files in console cartridges). Additionally the password system could be used for cheat codes: 'JUSTIN BAILEY ------ ------' (Just in Ballet) being famous, would remove Samus' power suit and start the player with many of the power-ups and fairly progressed through the game.

Completing the game in time and with enough power-ups revealed different endings. At the end Samus removes the helmet or power suit (depending) to a reveal a shocking suprise that endeared the character and broke new ground in gaming.</desc>
    <releasedate>19860801T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo R&amp;D1</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Platfrom, Scifi, Shooter, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!! (Japan, USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!!</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!! (Japan, USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>It's a right jab, a left hook, an uppercut - it's Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!! where you'll get the chance to compete against boxers from around the globe. Punch your way through 13 bouts in the minor, major and world circuits against tough contestants like Piston Honda, Glass Joe, Super Macho Man and many, many more! Defeat all your opponents and meet the ultimate challenge against the World Heavyweight Champion Mike Tyson in the greatest fight of all - The Dream Bout! Knockout Tyson and you can become WVBA (World Video Boxing Association) Champ!</desc>
    <releasedate>19871018T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo R&amp;D3</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Fighting, Sports</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ms. Pac-Man (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ms. Pac-Man</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ms. Pac-Man (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Gobble, gobble, gulp. Ms. Pac-Man chows a power pellet and it's dinner time. Fly around the mazes at top speed while you dine on ghosts and score big points. Watch out! Don't let those little haunters get their hands on you or you're history.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Midway</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Maze, Pacman, Singlescreen, Topdown</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ninja Gaiden (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ninja Gaiden</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ninja Gaiden (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Ryu Hayabusa of the Dragon Ninja Clan receives a letter from his father, saying that he was leaving for a duel with an unknown warrior. Should he not return, Ryu was to go to America and seek a man named Walter Smith. Ryu honors his father's last request, and travels to America. While there, he is kidnapped by a CIA agent and given a statue of a hideous beast.</desc>
    <releasedate>19890302T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tecmo</developer>
    <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Fighter, Horizontal, Platorm, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ninja Gaiden II - The Dark Sword of Chaos (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ninja Gaiden - Episode II - The Dark Sword of Chaos</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ninja Gaiden II - The Dark Sword of Chaos (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <desc>Dynamic action scenes! Split your body into three, destroy all enemies with the Invincible Fire Wheel and other new Ninja fighting techniques! Ninja Gaiden II gives you the feel of real Ninjutsu! Exciting cinema display format! Ninja Gaiden II uses the same Cinema Display Format as the original. The fiendish plot unfolds in a movie-like sequence. Action, drama, revenge. Just wait till you get to the end!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900501T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tecmo</developer>
    <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up, Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  <favorite>true</favorite></game>
  <game>
    <path>./Ninja Gaiden III - The Ancient Ship of Doom (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Ninja Gaiden III - The Ancient Ship of Doom</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Ninja Gaiden III - The Ancient Ship of Doom (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Thrilling new cinema screen! Follow the story of Ryu's epic adventure through Tecmo's movie-like Cinema Screen Animation. As you complete each level, a new part of the story unfolds. Exciting new powers and weapons! Over the years Ninja Ryu's fighting skills have improved to include fantastic new powers and weapons. Action-packed Ninja adventure! Can you get Ryu through his most challenging adventure as he battles the hideous ancient forces of darkness to save mankind? The Ultimate Ninja Challenge!</desc>
    <releasedate>19910801T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tecmo</developer>
    <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Fighter, Horizontal, Platorm, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Pac-Man (USA) (Namco).zip</path>
    <name>Pac-Man</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Pac-Man (USA) (Namco).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Gobble, gobble, gulp! Who's munching Power Pellets? Who's zipping around the maze at top speed, chomping up ghosts and scoring big points? It's Pac-Man, the world's hungriest character! Devour a fruit treat and get a big bonus score. But if you're caught by the little haunters, you're ghostflakes! Use the warp tunnel for a quick escape. Now play this classic arcade mega-hit alone or with a friend for double the fun! Hours of ghost-chomping action!</desc>
    <releasedate>19931102T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Maze, Pacman, Singlescreen, Topdown</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Pac-Man (USA) (Tengen).zip</path>
    <name>Pac-Man</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Pac-Man (USA) (Tengen).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Gobble, gobble, gulp! Who's munching Power Pellets? Who's zipping around the maze at top speed, chomping up ghosts and scoring big points? It's Pac-Man, the world's hungriest character! Devour a fruit treat and get a big bonus score. But if you're caught by the little haunters, you're ghostflakes! Use the warp tunnel for a quick escape. Now play this classic arcade mega-hit alone or with a friend for double the fun! Hours of ghost-chomping action!</desc>
    <releasedate>19870612T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Maze, Pacman, Singlescreen, Topdown</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Paperboy (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Paperboy</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Paperboy (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>Hop on your bike for a free-wheeling ride up the avenues of not-so-typical suburbia. There are papers to be delivered, robbers to be foiled, and fame and fortune to be won as you brave the mean streets. Avoid motorcycles, tricycles, traffic, tires, gratings, curbs, dogs, skateboarders, breakdancers, bad guys, and other hazards as you deliver to your customers. Earn bonus points by hitting targets along the obstacle course at the end of your route. With superb animation and sound effects, Paperboy brings home all the thrills, spills, challenge, and excitement you loved in the arcades.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tengen</developer>
    <publisher>Mindscape, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Bicycle, Isometic, Reaction, Scrolling, Vertical</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Paperboy 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Paperboy 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Paperboy 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Rise and shine, bud! A great day's ahead, just waiting for you to become the neighborhood's terror of a paperboy. but it's a whole new job with double the fun and twice the excitement! That's right, you've now got houses on both sides of the street - which means even more customers' homes to deliver papers to and non subscribers' homes to damage. It also means you've got to watch out for lots more obstacles and meanies that are out to knock you off your bike! Wreak mischief across the town or do good deeds like saving the baby and stopping the burglar. At the end of the day, hone your skills on the all-new BMX-style test course. Add the new awesome graphics, and you're in for a rip roaring time on your bike!</desc>
    <releasedate>19920401T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tengen</developer>
    <publisher>Mindscape, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Bicyles, Hotseat, Isometic, Reaction, Scrolling, Vertical</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Punch-Out!! (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Punch-Out!!</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Punch-Out!! (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <desc>Punch-Out!! It's 13 tough matches in the minor, major and world circuits that lead to the final challenge - the World Video Boxing Association title fight. The ultimate bout against the newest WVBA Champ - Mr. Dream! Practice your hook and take a quick jab. Try to stay light on your feet as you dance left, then right, dodging punches while you throw your own. Boxers from around the world like Piston Honda, Glass Joe and Super Macho Man are all trying to knock you out of the ring. You've trained for months for this moment. There's the bell. Shake hands and come out boxing!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900801T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Behind, Boxing, Sports</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./R.B.I. Baseball (USA).zip</path>
    <name>R.B.I. Baseball</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/R.B.I. Baseball (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <desc>No other baseball game gets you closer to playing in the big time than R.B.I. Baseball. Because every one of the ten teams in R.B.I. Baseball contains the rosters and player stats officially licensed from the MLB Players Association. Like real baseball, these skills and stats affect the outcome of every play. Like a real manager, you'll need to make good use of this vital information - and wise strategy decisions - if you want a winning record. R.B.I. Baseball is so intensely realistic, we've added amusing animation and a touch of humor to keep the action light-hearted and fun. You can play against the computer in a nine game season or compete against a friend in your own best-of-seven series. Stop playing with no-names and step up to the plate with real superstars in R.B.I. Baseball!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Tengen</publisher>
    <genre>Angle, Baseball, Behind, Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./R.B.I. Baseball 2 (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>R.B.I. Baseball 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/R.B.I. Baseball 2 (USA) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <desc>R.B.I. Baseball first set the standard as the only baseball game for play on the NES to use real players and their stats. R.B.I. Baseball 2 raises the standard to a new level: You get all 26 pro teams, each with a roster of 24 real players. Every player comes with his actual 1989 stats. There's instant replay, as well as new and improved animation, graphics, music and sound effects to make the game come alive. As the manager, you get the designated-hitter rule, switch-hitting, and your own lineup of starters and subs. It's so great, it's approved by the Major League Baseball Players Association!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tengen</developer>
    <publisher>Tengen</publisher>
    <genre>Angle, Baseball, Behind, Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./R.B.I. Baseball 3 (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>R.B.I. Baseball 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/R.B.I. Baseball 3 (USA) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <desc>R.B.I. Baseball 3 is a Baseball Sim game, developed and published by Tengen, which was released in 1991.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tengen</developer>
    <publisher>Tengen</publisher>
    <genre>Angle, Baseball, Behind, Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./R.C. Pro-Am (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>R.C. Pro-AM</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/R.C. Pro-Am (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Nintendo puts you in control.
  Grab your controller and pull up to the starting line. It's you against three other all-star racers. You'll face hair-pin turns, outragerous curves, oil slicks and rainclouds as you make your way through 32 trecherous courses.
  Along the way you'll pick up performance boosters like Turbo Accelerations, Sticky Tires and Top Speed that will help you get to the finish line first. But if the going gets rough, use your bombs and missles to knock out the competition to make sure you're the winner.</desc>
    <releasedate>19881231T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Racing</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./R.C. Pro-Am II (USA).zip</path>
    <name>R.C. Pro-Am II</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/R.C. Pro-Am II (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>If you're into racing, but you're tired of racing big, unwieldy cars, then you should check out R.C. PRO-AM II for the Nintendo Entertainment System. You'll be in control of the remote-controlled cars that you remember from your childhood, complete with antennae to pick up your signal. There are 24 tracks covering a wide variety of terrain. If you're good enough to win a race, you can go to the R.C. Model Shop and upgrade your car's components to turn it into an unbeatable racing machine. You'll also have access to power-ups and weapons, adding a new element of strategy to the racing formula. Whether by yourself or with up to three friends, R.C. PRO-AM II delivers intense racing action miniature style!</desc>
    <releasedate>19921201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Tradewest, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Angle, Car, Multidirectional, Racing</genre>
    <players>4</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Rampage (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Rampage</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Rampage (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>The game where the nice guys don't get a look in. Grab your way through Chicago, punch up New York, and jump on San Francisco. Three indescribably nasty characters which bear a remarkable likeness to King Kong, Godzilla and Wolf-Man, need you to send them on a RAMPAGE in an enduring 150 days of destruction through 50 different cities!</desc>
    <releasedate>19881201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Data East Corporation</developer>
    <publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Beatemup, Horizontal, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./River City Ransom (USA).zip</path>
    <name>River City Ransom</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/River City Ransom (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>Hear the message from Sick, the meanest ganglord in town: "I hold your high school captive, and some of the students will have a trying moment, if they're ever fool enough to cross my path!" But you aren't afraid of anybody! Face the terrible gangs and neutralize their bosses, in order to deliver the city from terror!</desc>
    <releasedate>19900102T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
    <publisher>Technos Japan Corp.</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Beatemup, Fighter, Horizontal, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Rush'n Attack (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Rush'n Attack</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Rush'n Attack (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <desc>Up for a little guerilla warfare? You asked for it. You're behind enemy lines, armed with only a knife and a mission: to free dozens of POWs hidden in an isolated, well-armored camp. If you're good, you'll pick off the heavily-armed enemy guerillas, one by one, and grab their bazookas and hand grenades. If you're great, you'll turn their weapons against them, to blow away a pack of attack dogs, a fleet of choppers, and a whole battalion of guards. But make one mistake, and it's all over. For you, our POWs... the future of the Free World!</desc>
    <releasedate>19870402T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Arcade, Fighter, Horizontal, Platform, Shooter, Sideways</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Rygar (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Rygar</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Rygar (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>An evil being known as Ligar is about to conquer the land of Argool. Such is his power that no living creature dares to cross paths with him. But the legendary warrior Rygar rises from his grave to restore peace and justice. Armed with his famed weapon Diskarmor, Rygar begins to traverse the vast lands that lead to the lair of the demon, as his minions are trying in vain to stop him...</desc>
    <releasedate>19870701T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tecmo</developer>
    <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Smash T.V. (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Smash T.V.</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Smash T.V. (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>Moving from one room to the next within the studio/arena, players have to shoot down hordes of enemies as they advance from all sides, while at the same time collecting weapons, power-up items, and assorted bonus prizes until a final show down with the show's host where you are finally granted your prizes, your life and freedom. One of the enemies is fat and is named Mr. Shrapnel who roams aside of the walls of some rooms and after a short period of time he explodes. In the NES version, he is replaced by a giant rolling bomb.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910901T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Williams</developer>
    <publisher>Williams Electronic Games, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Arcade, Cooperative, Flipscreen, Powerup, Shooter, Topdown</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./StarTropics (USA).zip</path>
    <name>StarTropics</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/StarTropics (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Find out just how resourceful you can be in this classic game, with its mixture of adventure and RPG elements. Step into the shoes of Mike Jones, a teenage star pitcher from Seattle who has come to the tropics to visit his famous archaeologist uncle, Dr. Jones. After being told that his uncle has been abducted, Mike begins a perilous quest in order to rescue him and figure out the mysterious plot behind his disappearance.</desc>
    <releasedate>19901201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo R&amp;D3</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Actionadventure, Horizontal, Platform, Sideways</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Mario Bros. (World).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario Bros. / Duck Hunt</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Mario Bros. (World).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Double the fun on one Game Pak - use the light gun for Duck Hunt and the controllers for Super Mario Bros.

Take aim, fire and score! It's DUCK HUNT! Your trusty hunting dog wades into the marshes to flush out your prey. Your fingers tighten around your Zapper light gun. Suddenly, there's a duck in the air! You've only got three shots to bag this duck, and if you miss, even your dog laughs at you! But become a sharp-shooter, and you'll progress to the next round where two ducks fly up at the same time. And then you're on to the ultimate challenge: Clay Shooting. Where you'll compete in a wild clay-pigeon shooting contest! Play DUCK HUNT and discover you can have lots of laughs and be challenged at the same time.

Do you have what it takes to save the Mushroom Princess? You'll have to think fast and move even faster to complete this quest! The Mushroom Princess is being held captive by the evil Koopa tribe of turtles. It's up to you to rescue her from the clutches of the Koopa King before time runs out. But it won't be easy. To get to the princess you'll have to climb mountains, cross seas, avoid bottomless pits, fight of turtle soldiers and a host of black magic traps that only a Koopa King can devise. It's another non-stop adventure from the SUPER MARIO BROS.!</desc>
    <releasedate>19880726T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Shooter</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Mario Bros. 2 (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario Bros. 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Mario Bros. 2 (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Mario&#8217;s back!  Bigger and badder than ever before!  This time it&#8217;s a fierce action-packed battle to free the land of Subcon from the curse of the evil Wart.  It&#8217;s up to you, along with Mario, Luigi, Toad and the Princess, to fight your way through bizarre multi-level worlds and find him!  This time you&#8217;ve got a brand new kind of power - plucking power - and now anything you find can be a weapon.  But beware!  You&#8217;ve never seen creatures like these!  Shyguys and Tweeters!  Ninji and Beezos!  And you&#8217;ve never had an adventure like this!  Only cunning and speed can save you now&#8230;</desc>
    <releasedate>19881009T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo R&amp;D4</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Mario Bros. 3 (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Mario Bros. 3 (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Fight monsters and mini-bosses, avoid ghosts and the burning sun.  Make your way through water and quicksand.  Dodge cannonballs and bullets and rescue the King&#8217;s wand!

In Super Mario Bros. 3 there are more warps, more chances at extra lives, and new special suits!  The raccoon suit lets you fly and knock out blocks.  The frog suit helps you out-swim the deadly fish.  There are suits for every occasion!

Store up flowers and mushrooms to use later on.  Play game-show type bonus rounds!  Go back to that last screen and get a mushroom!  Pause to take a break, then continue where you left off!

Super Mario Bros. 3 is fun to play alone, or team up with a buddy to prolong the adventure!

Note: Turn based Co-op as players work in turn to clear individual levels in a world. There is also a vs. mini-game where players try to steal items from each other.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900212T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo R&amp;D4</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Super Mario Bros. + Tetris + Nintendo World Cup (Europe) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario Bros./Tetris/Nintendo World Cup</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Super Mario Bros. + Tetris + Nintendo World Cup (Europe) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>Super Mario Bros. / Tetris / Nintendo World Cup is a Miscellaneous game, developed and published by Nintendo, which was released in Europe in 1988. It is highly uncommon outside the PAL-region, although it is not valuable amongst collectors. This cartridge is exotic to North American gamers and not more worth than a few bucks for Europeans.</desc>
    <releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Puzzle, Sports, Platform</genre>
    <players>4</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Tecmo Bowl (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Tecmo Bowl</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Tecmo Bowl (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating/>
    <desc>TECMO BOWL! You've trained for it in the arcade. Now, strap on your helmet and go for it! Choose your team and select plays for your own game plan. From the snap, total control of every pass, block, run, and tackle is in your hands. Tecmo Bowl! The game of guts and glory!</desc>
    <releasedate>19890201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tecmo</developer>
    <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Tecmo Super Bowl (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Tecmo Super Bowl</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Tecmo Super Bowl (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>The teams, the players, and the halftime shows are ready for the ultimate football season, and you're in control. From the first pre-season game to the playoffs, it's your call, your skill, and your team. Can you get to and win the Super Bowl? Tecmo Super Bowl is the only football game to feature onside kicks, blocked passes and kicks, fumbles, pitchout to the running back, player injuries, time-outs, and much, much more! For 1 or 2 players. All 28 NFL teams! Four running plays, four passing plays. Team stats and data. Create your own Pro Bowl. Coach Mode, where you call the plays!</desc>
    <releasedate>19911202T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tecmo</developer>
    <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
    <genre>Americanfootball, Horizontal, Sideways, Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Tetris (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Tetris</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Tetris (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>A random sequence of tetrominoes (sometimes called "tetrads" in older versions)&#8212;shapes composed of four square blocks each&#8212;fall down the playing field (a rectangular vertical shaft, called the "well" or "matrix"). The objective of the game is to manipulate these tetrominoes, by moving each one sideways and rotating it by 90 degree units, with the aim of creating a horizontal line of blocks without gaps. When such a line is created, it disappears, and any block above the deleted line will fall. With every ten lines that are cleared, the game enters a new level. As the game progresses, each level causes the tetrominoes to fall faster, and the game ends when the stack of tetrominoes reaches the top of the playing field and no new tetrominoes are able to enter. In certain versions, the game can also end if the player is able to get all the way to level 15.

All of the tetrominoes are capable of single and double clears. I, J, and L are able to clear triples. Only the I tetromino has the capacity to clear four lines simultaneously, and this is referred to as a "tetris". (This may vary depending on the rotation and compensation rules of each specific Tetris implementation. For instance, in the Super Rotation System used in most recent implementations, called "Easy Spin" in Tetris Worlds, certain rare situations allow T, S and Z to 'snap' into tight spots and clear triples.)</desc>
    <releasedate>19891101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Fallingblocks, Puzzle, Realtime, Singlescreen, Tilearrangement</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Tetris 2 (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Tetris 2</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Tetris 2 (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <desc>The mesmerizing fun of Tetris returns - and the challenge escalates to new heights! Test your dexterity, tease your brain and rack up points with Tetris 2. Your split-second decisions lead you to a new dimension in puzzle solving action! Play alone or challenge a friend in simultaneous, split-screen action. Line-up three blocks of the same color and vroosh! - they explode! Get rid of special Flash Blocks and wipe out matching color pieces in one move. A tougher Tetris with more shapes, more components, 30 levels - and unlimited solutions. If you loved the international game sensation Tetris, you'll be wild for the newest dimension in puzzle fun: Tetris 2!</desc>
    <releasedate>19931002T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Fallingblocks, Puzzle, Realtime, Singlescreen, Tilearrangement</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <kidgame>true</kidgame>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Vice - Project Doom (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Vice - Project Doom</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Vice - Project Doom (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <desc>Vice: Project Doom is a game that features side-scrolling platform sequences, overhead driving modes and rail-shooter stages. In driving stages Hart's vehicle can accelerate or slow down and fire his weapon straight ahead. During side-scrolling sequences, Hart can jump, duck, climb or use his selected weapon. Weapons that can be selected include a Katana sword, a pistol and a grenade-type weapon. These weapons feature limited ammunition with the exception of the katana. Power-ups include ammunition, coins, and health. In rail-shooting stages, similar to Operation Wolf, Hart can shoot enemies with his gun or throw grenades and pick up items by shooting at them.</desc>
    <releasedate>19911101T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Aicom</developer>
    <publisher>Sammy Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Horizontal, Platform, Racing, Shooter, Sideways, Topdown, Vertical</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Zelda II - The Adventure of Link (USA).zip</path>
    <name>Zelda II: The Adventure of Link</name>
    <cover/>
    <image>./screenshots/Zelda II - The Adventure of Link (USA).png</image>
    <marquee/>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <desc>The land of Hyrule is in chaos.  As Link, you'll be sent on a treacherous journey to return six precious Crystals to their origins in six stone statues.  Only by defeating the guardians of the six palaces will you gain passage to the seventh palace, take on the ultimate challenge that awaits you, and wake the Princess Zelda from her sleeping spell.  On your way, helpful villagers you encounter will offer clues and secret messages invaluable in your quest.  As you guide Link through the levels of Hyrule, close-ups and overviews will enhance your video vision.  Are you up to the challenge?</desc>
    <releasedate>19881201T000000T000000T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nintendo</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Fantasy, Horizontal, Rpg, Sideways, Wanderer</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
</gameList>
